Chapter 1192: Slim Chances

Han Li took a glance at the rumbling lightning region behind him, then sped away in another direction.

Right at this moment, he suddenly raised an eyebrow and stopped in his tracks, following which his Reincarnation Palace mask appeared on his face.

Immediately thereafter, he was ecstatic to discover that he had received a response on the advertisement that he had posted in search of time-attribute law materials.

He hurriedly made a hand seal, and a projection of an elegant figure emerged from his mask.

To his surprise, it was none other than Wyrm 3.

"Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3? What brings you here? Could it be that you're in possession of the time-attribute law materials that I seek?" Han Li asked.

"I certainly do. Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Han," Wyrm 3 said with a faint smile, then flipped a hand over to produce a length of azure wood that was around half a foot in length.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, what you have there is perfect for my needs. How many Immortal Origin Stones would you like for it?" Han Li asked.

The length of wood was identical in appearance to the one that Patriarch Miro had tried to bestow upon him, and it was clearly the same type of material.

Out of his five time-attribute law treasures, the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree was the only one that was still sorely lacking in time law threads compared with the rest, so this was precisely what he needed.

Han Li was both elated and befuddled to see this. He had been very vague about the time-attribute law items that he was searching for in the advertisement that he had released, yet somehow, Wyrm 3 had been able to present one that perfectly fit his needs.

"You can have it for free if you'd like, Fellow Daoist Han. I didn't get a chance to thank you for your help in the Tai Sui Immortal Manor," Wyrm 3 replied as she made a hand seal, and the length of wood instantly appeared in the item teleportation array in front of Han Li.

He was rather taken aback by this, and he didn't immediately reach out for the length of wood.

"We both got what we wanted in the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, so you don't owe me anything. I can't accept such a precious item free of charge, so please state a price, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

"In that case, I'll state a condition. Once the Nine Origins Temple mission commences, I want you to do me a favor as compensation for this item. What do you say?" Wyrm 3 asked with a faint smile.

"What exactly is it that you would like me to do for you?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Han, it won't be anything difficult or perilous. However, I can't divulge to you exactly what it is for the moment," Wyrm 3 replied with a shake of her head.

"Alright, I can accept that arrangement. By the way, when is the Nine Origins Temple mission going to commence?" Han Li asked as he stowed the length of wood away.

"It shouldn't be too much longer, perhaps around a hundred more years at most," Wyrm 3 replied, and Han Li was quite relieved to hear this.

It seemed like Xiaobai would be able to take part in the mission.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I don't know where you are right now, but at the moment, the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region is a very tumultuous place, so I advise you not to go there for now. Instead, you should find a secluded place to cultivate, and I'll notify you when it's time to act," Wyrm 3 cautioned.

Han Li nodded in response, and the two of them chatted for a while longer before their communication concluded, following which Han Li pulled out that length of wood again with an ecstatic look on his face.

With this length of wood, he would be able to balance out the five types of time law powers in his body, thereby all but ensuring a successful breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage. However, such a breakthrough was undoubtedly going to cause a massive commotion, so he had to find a good place to go into seclusion.

With that in mind, Han Li turned and made his way back into the primordial land.

Even though the primordial land was rife with powerful demon beasts, it was still going to be far safer than the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

Having just come from Eight Plains Mountain, Han Li had become very familiar with this section of the primordial land, and he quickly found a relatively safe place to go into seclusion.

He had chosen an undulating mountain range that was home to many bodies of water, as well as an abundance of underground earth flames. As a result, the entire mountain range was filled with dense mist, making it very difficult to see inside.

Han Li carefully examined the area around the mountain range, and only ensuring that there was nothing amiss did he carve out a temporary cave abode at the foot of a mountain before setting up several layers of restrictions.

This was a very well-rehearsed process, and it took him only less than half a day to complete.

Han Li entered the Flower Branch domain, and at the moment, the space of accelerated time wasn't active due to limitations in the Immortal Origin Stones in his possession and the time law powers in the Eon Divine Lamp.

"Master, how did the refinement of your flying swords go?" Xiaobai asked.

"It went quite well," Han Li replied.

"That's great! How about we go to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region right away to rescue Boss?" Xiaobai eagerly proposed.

"Now's not a good time. At my current cultivation base, our chances of successfully rescuing Jin Tong are still quite slim. However, the good news is that I've just obtained a treasure that'll be very helpful for my cultivation, so I'm planning to go into seclusion to attempt a breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage," Han Li replied.

"If you can get to the Great Encompassment Stage, we'll be able to rescue Boss for sure! But will we have enough time for you to make your breakthrough? His Majesty only gave me two hundred years," Xiaobai said as a concerned look appeared on his face.

"Even if I manage to reach the Great Encompassment Stage, I still wouldn't dare to say a successful rescue mission is guaranteed. In any case, we'll just have to do our best," Han Li mused.

He then cast his gaze toward a white fireball elsewhere in the Flower Branch domain, then made a hand seal to send a streak of golden light flying into the ball of fire.

The white fireball quickly faded away to reveal the Essence Fire Child, which flew over to Han Li's side and began making a bunch of unintelligible sounds.

After these years of diligent cultivation, the essential fire law powers in his body had become significantly stronger.

"I'm going to be making an attempt to reach the Great Encompassment Stage. Even though I've set up some defensive restrictions outside, I'll still have the trouble the two of you to stand on lookout duty outside as a safety precaution," Han Li said.

"You can count on me, Master!" Xiaobai declared, and the Essence Fire Child also made a series of reassuring gestures, following which both of them flew out of the domain.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he activated the Celestial Time Array and the Heavenly Wheel Sundial, accelerating the flow of time in the Flower Branch domain.

He didn't know how long it was going to take for him to reach the Great Encompassment Stage, so he had to make as much time for himself as possible.

After doing all of that, he flew into the bamboo pavilion, then sat down and pulled out the length of wood given to him by Wyrm 3.

He channeled the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, conjuring up the golden ring to encircle the length of wood, which instantly disintegrated into countless specks of golden light that fused into the golden ring before being converted into over fifty time law threads, all of which wrapped themselves around the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree.

The Time Severing Torch still had more time law threads around it than all of the other time-attribute law treasures, but there was certainly much more balance than before.

The five time-attribute law treasures lit up in unison and began rapidly revolving around Han Li.

A sense of enlightenment instantly welled up in his heart, and his Great Encompassment Stage bottleneck began to loosen.

It's just as Master said, balance is the most important thing when cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra! Han Li thought to himself with an ecstatic expression, then laid out all of the things that he had prepared for this very breakthrough, particularly the True Profound Pill.

The pill was only to be consumed at the end of a Great Encompassment Stage breakthrough, so it had been preserved in the wake of his failed breakthrough attempt.

Han Li sat down to meditate for half a day, priming himself into the best condition before channeling the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

Radiant, golden light began to emanate from his body, and a burst of tremendous time law powers erupted out of the pavilion, while all of the nearby world's origin qi slowly converged toward him.

......

There Was an ocean outside the Ancient Cloud Continent of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region called the Eastern Flow Sea.

The Eastern Flow Sea was frozen all year round, but there was one area of it that currently remained unfrozen.

In this area of the sea was a deepsea chasm that reached all the way down to the seabed.

At the bottom of the chasm was an unremarkable-looking gray stone plaque, which was connected to the floating mountain secret area of the once powerful Blaze Dragon Dao.

The secret area produced bountiful harvests of spirit medicines, making it an important source of resources for the sect, and Han Li had previously been stationed here once upon a time. However, with the fall of the Blaze Dragon Dao, this secret area had also been claimed by the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace.

Inside the secret area was a white stone plaza on a floating mountain, and an unkempt gray-robed man was leaning against the railing at the edge of the plaza with a white jade wine flagon in his hand, looking as if he had only just woken up.

His eyes were bloodshot, and he was looking at the mountains floating in the air before him with a sullen expression.

He was once one of the Blaze Dragon Dao's thirty-six deputy dao lords with a bright future ahead, yet during the crisis that had befallen the sect, he was just a little slow to join the traitors, resulting in his gradual ostracization over time.

It only took about a century before he was banished to this place to manage this floating mountain secret area, and it was certainly a far cry from former heights that he had reached.

Chapter 1193: Signs of Turmoil

However, he then thought about how those traitors were currently serving as the lapdogs of the Immortal Palace, and that was quite a pleasing thought for him as he burst into hearty laughter.

Two of his direct disciples had also been banished to this place with him, and they exchanged a glance with one another as one of them mused through voice transmission, "Looks like Master's having one of his episodes again..."

"Indeed. It was only through an ancestral connection that I was able to become his direct disciple, yet now, I'm trapped in this place with him. When will we ever be able to make anything of ourselves like this?" the other disciple sighed.

The two of them then cast their eyes downward in a dejected manner to look into the abyss below.

The scenery here was certainly quite exquisite, but it inevitably became a boring sight over time.

Right at this moment, the sound of a blowing horn suddenly rang out from deep within the abyss.

The two disciples' brows furrowed slightly as they hurriedly turned to the gray-robed man, only to discover that the latter was paying ho heed to the sound of the horn as he continued downing wine.

The two disciples could only exchange a wry smile upon seeing this, following which they leaped down into the abyss below.

However, they weren't able to get very far before they spotted a series of figures rising up from the mist below as quickly as they could. As it turned out, it was thousands of outer sect disciples responsible for collecting spirit medicines in the valley, and a chorus of panicked cries could be heard ringing out amid agonized howls.

"The white ghosts are coming!"

The two disciples' expressions changed slightly upon hearing this, and one of them yelled, "What's there to be afraid of? Just use the array to hold them back!"

"It's not working! The white ghosts have gone crazy!" someone yelled.

One of the disciples grabbed onto a panicked disciple as he snapped, "Tell me what happened!"

"The white ghosts have gone crazy! Not only have they rushed out of the mist, they don't even fear the array anymore! Too many of them to count came rushing upward from the abyss, destroying the array with their sheer numbers!" the disciple explained in a panicked manner.

Before the two disciples could ask any more questions, bursts of rumbling suddenly began to ring out from down below as a massive horde of shadowy figures rose up from the abyss.

An uneasy look appeared in the eyes of one of the two disciples upon seeing this, and he hurriedly yelled, "Get into formation!"

However, everyone was too panicked to heed his call.

Right at this moment, a thunderous voice rang out from up above.

"Anyone who retreats even a step further will be executed where they stand!"

The gray-robed man then descended from the sky, and it was as if he had reclaimed his former majesty and glory.

His mid-Golden Immortal Stage aura instantly spread over the entire secret area as he harrumphed coldly, "It's just an uprising of white ghosts. A similar thing happened many years ago, and at the time, there was only an ordinary elder stationed here, yet even he was able to weather the storm, so what's there to be afraid of? Hurry up and get into formation!"

His words had a remarkable calming effect, and the thousands of fleeing disciples instantly composed themselves before arranging themselves into a series of different arrays.

As soon as the arrays took shape, countless ghosts came bursting out of the mist, then began climbing up the floating mountains.

"Kill them!" the gray-robed man ordered in a cold voice, and a string of resounding booms instantly rang out across the entire secret area.

One of the arrays was releasing volleys of fiery meteors that plunged into the abyss, while giant ice spikes were raining down from another.

All types of immortal treasures and abilities were also unleashed upon the ascending white ghosts, and the entire secret area was plunged into complete chaos.

Countless white ghosts were struck down before falling into the abyss, but more white ghosts took their place as they continued to swarm upward with no regard for their own lives.

Something's not right...

The gray-robed man's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, and he immediately released his spiritual sense to examine what was happening deep in the abyss.

However, his spiritual sense was only able to descend for several tens of thousands of feet before it was seemingly obstructed by something, preventing it from descending any further.

More and more white ghosts continued to rush up from below, and right as they were about to reach the disciples above, the gray-robed man swept a sleeve through the air, upon which a massive, azure ring appeared behind him.

A storm of sword projections then came hurtling out of the azure ring at his behest, felling hordes of white ghosts by the second.

However, even as more and more white ghosts perished, the gray-robed man only felt more and more uneasy.

These white ghosts didn't look as if they were launching a voluntary attack. Instead, it looked much more like they were fleeing from something, but what was there in the abyss aside from them?

Right at this moment, a peculiar aura rose up from the abyss below, and a cloud of gray mist began spreading upward at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Numerous muscular, azure apes could be seen jumping out of the gray mist in pursuit of the white ghosts, and they were far more powerful than the white ghosts, leading to a completely one-sided slaughter.

They quickly took over the floating mountains down below, then began glowering up at the humans above with fierce animosity in their eyes.

The two disciples hurriedly fled back to the gray-robed man's side, then asked in a fearful manner, "What are those things, Master?"

The gray-robed man didn't know what they were, either, so he didn't say anything.

Right at this moment, an enormous tornado of black mist rose up from down below, carrying three imposing figures to the fore.

Just a single glance at the three figures was enough to shake the gray-robed man to the core. Their auras were so immense that he was almost unable to work up the courage to look directly at them, and he could only roughly approximate that their cultivation bases were above the late-High Zenith Stage.

One of the three figures was a deathly pale man who resembled a drowned corpse that had just been fished out of the water, and he was holding a white feline creature with a pair of enormous eyes.

This man was none other than Gui Mu, one of the Great Encompassment cultivators that Han Li had encountered in the Gray Realm.

"It looks like we're in a secret area, but judging from the abundance of the world's origin qi in the air, this is definitely the Immortal Realm," Gui Mu mused as he took a glance at his surroundings, paying no heed to the thousands of Blaze Dragon Dao and Immortal Palace cultivators present.

The gray-robed man mustered up some courage, then asked, "Who are you people?"

Gui Mu took a glance at him, then turned to the two figures beside him as he instructed, "Kill them all and eradicate their souls. We need to empty out this place so that more of our brethren can come through."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the two figures beside him vanished into thin air, and the azure apes down below also sprang up toward the human cultivators above amid a chorus of ferocious snarls.

With that, a horrific slaughter ensued.

......

In the Origin Encirclement Immortal Region.

Recently, a piece of astonishing news had made its rounds throughout the immortal region's eight continents.

The palace master of the immortal region, a Great Encompassment cultivator by the title of Daoist Master Tihu, had suddenly gone insane one day for seemingly no cause, slaughtering all of the over one hundred and thirty immortal officials of the entire immortal palace.

An unfathomably powerful immortal envoy stationed in the immortal region had arrived on the scene to try and stop him, but they were also killed.

The entire immortal region fell into complete chaos thereafter, while Daoist Master Tihu vanished without a trace.

A mere seven days later, his name appeared very high up on the Immortal Slaying List, with a very handsome reward offered for his capture or demise.

Following the event, some rumors began to spread, proclaiming that Daoist Master Tihu hadn't suddenly gone insane. Instead, he had been a spy lurking in the Origin Encirclement Immortal Palace all along, and that he was actually a deputy palace master of the Reincarnation Palace.

It was said that following the completion of his, he fled back to the Reincarnation Palace, and that was why it had been so difficult for the Heavenly Court to track him down.

......

In the Southern Jin Immortal Region.

A secret area that had been lost for countless years suddenly emerged without any warning, sparking fierce competition between the Immortal Palace and the immortal region's four most powerful sects.

Originally, they had already agreed upon a scheme for how the spoils reaped in the secret area were to be distributed among them, but after they entered the secret area, two of the sects' leading elders and core disciples were killed, with all of the evidence pointing to the other two sects as the perpetrators.

Hence, a fierce battle ensued between the four sects.

The battle was deemed to have severely affected the stability of the immortal region, but right as the Immortal Palace was about to intervene, the four sects suddenly collectively turned on the Immortal Palace.

As it turned out, during their battle, they had discovered some hidden signs, leading to the realization that this had been a ruse from the Immortal Palace all along to spark infighting among the four sects.

Under the collective might of the four sects, the Southern Jin Immortal Palace was toppled, and the palace master was forced to flee.

Chapter 1194: Reaching the Great Encompassment Stage

Greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, Nine Origins Temple.

There was an undulating mountain range comprised of hundreds of mountains of different shapes and sizes, and among them was one that wasn't particularly tall, but stood out for its stunning scenery.

The mountain was partially concealed in the clouds with only a section of its lush surface exposed, and there were three majestic waterfalls flowing their way down the mountain like three bands of shimmering rainbow light, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

The sound of ape cries could be heard ringing out incessantly on the mountain, while cranes soared through the air overhead, giving the entire place the appearance of an immortal paradise.

On the mountain summit was a ring-shaped observation deck that extended out of the mountain, upon which stood a middle-aged daoist priest in a dark green daoist robe.

The man had a very upright posture and a square face that didn't bear the most remarkable facial features, but there was an ethereal, glowing quality about him that made it apparent that he was no mortal.

Despite the splendid scenery currently laid out before the daoist priest, his brows were slightly furrowed with concern.

Right at this moment, a thin, azure-robed elderly man arrived on the plaza on the mountain summit, then extended a respectful salute as he greeted, "Disciple Qing Xu pays his respects to Senior Martial Uncle Chun Jun."

The middle-aged daoist priest was known as Daoist Master Chun Jun in the immortal region, and he was the final disciple of the Nine Origins Temple's founding patriarch, so he was a very senior figure both in the sect and in the entire immortal region.

Most importantly, he was also a late-Great Encompassment cultivator, and he was temporarily serving as the abbot of the Nine Origins Temple.

"How did your investigation go?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"I have determined that the Heaven Controlling Vial has indeed reappeared, and that it's currently in the possession of a man by the name of Han Li," the elderly man replied.

"Han Li?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"He's a cultivator who ascended to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region from a lower realm, and he previously stayed in the Blaze Dragon Dao for a very long time," Qing Xu reported.

"All ascended cultivators are generally quite remarkable. Are there any records of him at the Ascension Platforms?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"I did manage to find some records, but... At the time, he was received by a Stone Ditch Palace cultivator by the name of Gao Sheng, but he intentionally withheld a great deal of information, seemingly intending to recruit Han Li to join the Stone Ditch Palace. However, Han Li didn't become a member of the Stone Ditch Palace. Instead, he disappeared on the way there," Qing Xu replied.

"Oh? What happened?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"I wasn't able to find out exactly what happened. All I know is that from that point, he disappeared for three hundred years, and he only reappeared in the Heavenly Court's line of sight during the fall of the Blaze Dragon Dao. From there, he's traveled to many immortal regions and engaged in frequent conflicts with the Heavenly Court, but has been able to get away every single time.

“His most notable feat was storming into the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Palace on his own to wipe out a large number of cultivators, including Palace Master Dongfang Bai," Qing Xu replied.

"What's his cultivation base?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"He's at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage," Qing Xu replied.

"Just as I thought, all ascended cultivators are remarkable figures. The fact that he possessed the courage and power to eradicate an entire immortal palace on his own is certainly nothing to scoff at. I'm assuming She Chan also perished by his hands as well, is that right?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"Prior to the return of Junior Martial Niece Lan Yan, she did report back that She Chan had perished by his hands. After that, Junior Martial Sister Miao Fa had gone after Han Li in person, but he was able to escape again due to Chi Meng's untimely intervention. From there, he's disappeared once again, and we are currently unaware of his whereabouts," Qing Xu replied.

Daoist Master Chun Jun's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "Recovering the Heaven Controlling Vial is an extremely important matter for our Nine Origins Temple, so this matter must be taken seriously."

"At the moment, Junior Martial Sister Miao Fa is still searching for him, and a third of all of our Nine Origins Temple's spies have been sent out for that cause as well, so it should only be a matter of time before we track him down," Qing Xu replied.

"Right now, many signs of unrest are beginning to arise in the Immortal Realm. The immortal regions under our jurisdiction have also been far from peaceful, particularly the Heavenly Star Immortal Region and the Shared Fate Immortal Region. Even my two senior martial brothers have been forced to travel to those immortal regions to quell the unrest there.

“With Miao Fa also absent, there are only three holy envoys left in the palace, and half of the eight saints are also out on various missions. At a time like this, we must be extra vigilant to ensure that nothing disturbs the patriarchs from their seclusion," Daoist Master Chun Jun sighed.

"Rest assured, Senior Martial Uncle, no one would dare to cause trouble in our Golden Origin Immortal Region," Qing Xu replied.

"By the way, how is that Gold Devouring Immortal doing?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"Initially, she was very lively and difficult to deal with, but she's become a lot more docile now. It seems like she's already grown accustomed to living in our temple," Qing Xu replied with a faint smile.

"Our master examined her last time and told us that she's no ordinary Gold Devouring Immortal, and it's clear that he’s taken a liking to her. Hence, there's a chance that he won't offer her up as a gift during the Bodhi Banquet, so I'll have to trouble you to prepare a few backup gifts," Daoist Master Chun Jun said, and Qing Xu gave an affirmative response.

......

In the primordial land.

High up in the sky above a misty mountain range, bolts of five-colored lightning were flashing and rumbling incessantly.

The clouds in the sky were being stirred up by a burst of tremendous force, forming a massive tornado of cloud and mist that funneled its way straight into a mountain in the mountain range.

Inside a cave abode that had only been recently carved out into the mountain, a handsome young boy and a silver fire raven were both looking around in alarm as immense torrents of the world's origin qi converged from all directions to surge into a door of silver light before them.

Xiaobai turned to the silver fire raven with a stunned expression, and the latter also took on its human form before nodding excitedly at Xiaobai.

"He's about to make a breakthrough after just twenty years! This is incredible!" Xiaobai exclaimed as he clapped his hands together in a joyful manner.

An unfathomably vast volume of the world's origin qi was gushing into the door of silver light, releasing such powerful energy fluctuations that the two of them had been forced to retreat far away.

Meanwhile, the enormous influx of the world's origin qi was testing the entire Flower Branch domain to its limits, and all of the spirit bamboo trees in the entire domain were absorbing the world's origin qi with all their might before distributing it throughout the domain through their root systems.

The newly constructed bamboo pavilion had grown three feet taller, as if it were a living being, and many of the spirit plants in the spirit medicine garden were also enjoying a period of rapid growth thanks to the extreme overabundance of spiritual qi.

Even the Twin Birth Tree, which had always been growing very slowly, was displaying a very encouraging rate of growth.

All of the water in the pond in front of the former bamboo pavilion was bubbling and churning incessantly, and the surface of the pond was filled with forty-nine golden lotus flowers that were in full bloom.

All of these changes had been brought by only a tiny portion of the world's origin qi that had entered the domain, while the majority of it was surging into the bamboo pavilion, which was trembling and swaying violently, but somehow managed to remain standing.

At this moment, the entire pavilion was glowing radiantly, and Han Li was seated inside with his entire body enshrouded in a layer of five-colored light.

All of his golden meridians were clearly visible through his translucent, jade-like skin, while his nascent soul was also seated with its legs crossed in his dantian.

The world's origin qi surging into the pavilion was rapidly flowing into his body, and while only twenty years had passed for Xiaobai, over two thousand years had already transpired for Han Li thanks to the Celestial Time Array.

Following the past two thousand years of tireless cultivation, he was finally able to establish a state of perfect equilibrium between his five time-attribute law treasures, and that was the moment that he successfully reached the Great Encompassment Stage.

All of a sudden, his eyes sprang open, and two beams of blinding golden light shot out of his pupils, while all of the lingering world's origin qi around him was sucked into his body at once.

All of his immortal acupoints were glowing radiantly, while a faint river of light suddenly appeared in the air above the bamboo pavilion.

Han Li slowly rose to his feet as he took a deep breath, and his senses had become unprecedentedly sharp, allowing him to observe every single one of the minute details in the space around him.

Chapter 1195: Oneness Tier

Han Li made his way out of the pavilion to look up at the river of light in the sky, which looked as if it had been formed by countless stars.

As he gazed upon the starry river, he suddenly felt as if the specks of starlight within it had begun to move, flashing through the river like clusters of shooting stars.

A peculiar sensation welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he could sense bursts of time law power fluctuations emanating from the river.

He swept his gaze over the surrounding area, only to discover that everything seemed to have fallen completely still under the umbrella of these time law power fluctuations.

Intrigued, Han Li made a hand seal to channel the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and his five time-attribute law treasures also appeared around him one after another.

The five law treasures then flew into the river of light overhead, and the time law treasures within them flew out before fusing with the river of light.

The river of light instantly began to glow with dazzling, golden radiance that descended from above to inundate the entire Flower Branch domain, basking the entire space in a layer of time law power fluctuations.

Han Li was rather alarmed to see this, thinking that all of his time law threads had vanished without a trace, and he hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a huge time spirit domain to encompass the entire Flower Branch domain.

He then attempted to summon his time law threads back to himself through the spirit domain, but to no avail.

Meanwhile, as soon as his spirit domain appeared, numerous translucent dao runes had begun flying out of his five time-attribute law treasures to fuse with the space within the spirit domain.

Bursts of formidable energy fluctuations began to spread through the spirit domain, and the Mantra Treasured Axis rose up from behind to transform into a round full moon in the sky.

The full moon was giving off rays of golden light that shone down upon the entire spirit domain, and the light was just as bright as the sun on a hot summer's day, but it gave off no heat at all.

At the same time, the Illusory Dawn Hourglass descended to the ground, where it transformed into a golden sea of sand that filled the entire spirit domain.

A peculiar sensation welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

It seemed that something about his time-attribute law treasures had changed in the wake of his breakthrough.

Even after it had risen up into the air, the Mantra Treasured Axis remained rather illusory in appearance. However, specks of golden light were fusing into it from all directions, and its connection with the spirit domain was becoming deeper and deeper, as if they were about to fuse as one.

Is my spirit domain evolving to the Creation Tier?

A stunned look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but the surprises didn't end there.

All of a sudden, the Clear Time Vial fell down onto the sea of golden sand, and the golden liquid within came flowing out.

Not only did the golden liquid not seep into the Illusory Dawn Sand, it continued to accumulate rapidly, and before long, it had formed a shimmering, golden river.

The river was able to manipulate the landscape, shifting the sand on the ground to create mountains and valleys.

Immediately thereafter, the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree also descended onto the ground below, where it transformed into lush forests that spread rapidly in all directions.

Just like the full moon overhead, all of these manifestations began to slowly fuse with the spirit domain.

At this point, it had become abundantly clear to Han Li what was happening, and he leaped up into the air before sitting down with his legs crossed in a suspended fashion.

From there, he channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with all his might, releasing his time law powers and immortal spiritual power to fill the entire spirit domain.

As the time law powers flowed out of his body, the rate at which his time-attribute law treasures fused with his spirit domain began to speed up, but it was still agonizingly slow.

At this rate, he had no idea how long it was going to take to complete the endeavor. Additionally, he only had enough Immortal Origin Stones to maintain the Celestial Time Array for a century at most, which equated to ten thousands years.

Having already taken two thousand years to make his breakthrough, he only had eight thousand years left, and it was nothing short of delusional to expect to be able to completely stabilize a Creation Tier spirit domain during that time.

There's just not enough time to do everything in one go... Perhaps I should try completing fusion on one of them first, Han Li thought to himself, and with that, he made a decision, sweeping a sleeve toward the lush forest formed by the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree.

All of the time law powers and immortal spiritual power in the air immediately flowed toward the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree, and the rate of fusion of the other four time-attribute law treasures instantly slowed, while the exact opposite could be seen in the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree.

It's working!

He had chosen the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree as opposed to the Mantra Treasured Axis, the latter of which he was most familiar with, as he didn't have much confidence in the final outcome.

As time passed, Han Li continued to release his immortal spiritual power and time law powers to accelerate the maturation of his spirit domain.

Before long, another two thousand years had passed by, equating to only twenty years in the outside world.

Twenty years ago, Xiaobai had already sensed that Han Li had successfully made a breakthrough, and he was starting to grow rather concerned by the fact that Han Li was still in seclusion.

"Surely he should've come out by now! What's taking him so long? Could it be that something's gone wrong? No, there's no way that could happen to Master. He must be working on something else, but we don't have much time left..."

Xiaobai paced back and forth in an agitated manner, and he could only voice his concerns to the Essence Fire Raven.

Through their spiritual connection, he could sense that Han Li was fine, so he wasn't concerned for Han Li's safety. Instead, he was much more concerned about the two hundred years that he had been given running out.

The Essence Fire Raven could only shake its head in a resigned manner in response to Xiaobai's concerned queries, and Xiaobai was struck by the urge to enter the Flower Branch domain to check on Han Li on multiple occasions, but had to hold himself back for fear of disturbing Han Li's cultivation.

......

Inside the domain, Han Li was staring intently at the space down below, where the golden forest had already taken on a very substantial form.

With that, his spirit domain had reached the Creation Tier.

It only took two thousand years!

Han Li was quite pleased with this outcome.

Stabilizing a Creation Tier spirit domain was a very time-consuming task, and it could easily take tens, even hundreds of thousands of years for someone else.

Han Li speculated that the reasons why he had been able to complete this process so quickly were twofold. Firstly, the cultivation art that he was using was extremely advanced, and secondly, his five time-attribute law treasures contained the powers of the five elements to begin with.

All things in this world came from the five elements, so when it came to creation, things that contained the power of the five elements enjoyed an innate advantage.

Han Li swept his gaze over the manifestations of his other time-attribute law treasures as he murmured to himself, "There's not enough time for now, so I'll just have to create all of you at some later date."

Right as he was about to withdraw his spirit domain, a strange sound suddenly rang out from elsewhere within the Flower Branch domain.

Immediately thereafter, a streak of azure light rose up into the air from the spirit medicine garden, then raced over to Han Li before plunging into the golden forest in his spirit domain.

Han Li focused his gaze on the object to discover that it was a strange-looking tree.

Is that... the Twin Birth Tree?

Indeed, it was none other than the Twin Birth Tree that he had harvested from the ruins of the True Mantra Sect.

He recalled that the Twin Birth Tree had been growing extremely slowly, but this one had clearly already reached full maturity.

As soon as the tree fell into the forest, it immediately took root in the ground, and azure light began to radiate from it, forming what appeared to have been an azure forest.

The azure forest began to overlap with the golden one, and it looked as if they were about to fuse together.

A physical object is now fusing with my spirit domain? Isn't that something that's only supposed to happen at the Oneness Tier?

Oneness Tier spirit domains transcended beyond Creation and Spiritform Tier spirit domains as they could integrate things that contained the same type of law powers as itself, thereby giving the spirit domain a physical form, allowing it to completely dominate spirit domains of the previous two tiers.

In a Oneness Tier spirit domain, the cultivator was essentially one with the heavens, presiding over the spirit domain like a supreme ruler, granting them virtual invincibility against enemies.

Chapter 1196: Stumped

Han Li waited patiently for the Twin Birth Tree to completely fuse with his Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree, but right at this moment, the Celestial Time Array suddenly shuddered violently, and the light that it was radiating filled the entire Flower Branch domain, completely outshining his spirit domain.

Han Li's brows instantly furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Have I run out of Immortal Origin Stones?

Right at this moment, a burst of radiant, golden light rose up from the center of the array, then began racing toward Han Li.

Enveloped within the golden light was none other than the Heavenly Wheel Sundial.

He was worried that the sundial would interfere with the evolution of his spirit domain, so he made a grabbing motion toward it, attempting to intercept it in its tracks, but the sundial abruptly veered away from its original course, flying up toward the Mantra Treasured Axis hanging in the sky.

A resounding boom rang out as the Heavenly Wheel Sundial exploded upon making contact with the Mantra Treasured Axis, but strangely enough, the sundial only disintegrated in physical form following its explosion, while the metal-attribute time law powers within it transformed into a burst of golden light that fused with the Mantra Treasured Axis.

The golden light began to wrap itself around the Mantra Treasured Axis, and the latter began to take on a more substantial form while glowing brighter and brighter.

Given what had just happened with the Twin Birth Tree, Han Li was already somewhat prepared for this outcome, but he was still ecstatic, nonetheless.

Never he had he imagined that this stint of seclusion would be so bountiful.

However, what was rather perplexing to him was the fusion of the Twin Birth Tree had been facilitated on the basis of the successful creation of the forest formed by the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree, while the Mantra Treasured Axis hadn't reached the Creation Tier yet, so how was it fusing with the Heavenly Wheel Sundial?

Could it be that his spirit domain had skipped the Creation Tier altogether?

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed that his spirit domain had begun rippling very minutely.

Immediately thereafter, a dull thump rang out, and the Mantra Treasured Axis above him shuddered violently before giving off a burst of tremendous suction force.

Han Li hurriedly raised a hand to interrupt the fusion between his Mantra Treasured Axis and the Heavenly Wheel Sundial, but the process had reached a critical juncture, so if he were to intervene now, it was sure to cause severe damage to both objects involved.

However, he had no other choice.

The fusion between the two objects was undoubtedly going to require an immense amount of time law powers, something that his Mantra Treasured Axis wouldn't be able to provide in its current state.

The time law powers in his body had already been exhausted to support the fusion between the Twin Birth Tree and the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree, so he was unable to provide any support to the Mantra Treasured Axis.

His concern was that the Mantra Treasured Axis would forcibly absorb the power of his time spirit domain to reciprocate itself.

Sure enough, the suction force coming from the Mantra Treasured Axis was becoming stronger and stronger, while his spirit domain had begun trembling violently, and rays of golden light were splitting off from it before rising up toward the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li immediately reached out with both hands, forming a pair of massive hand projections that grabbed up toward the Mantra Treasured Axis.

The space up above began to ripple from the force exerted by the pair of hand projections, compressing toward the Mantra Treasured Axis in an attempt to sever its connection to his spirit domain, but his efforts proved to be completely futile.

Before the hand projections could close themselves around the Mantra Treasured Axis, they were kept at bay by the rays of golden light emanating from it.

These rays of light contained extremely pure time law powers that even Han Li wasn't able to overcome, and he could only watch as his spirit domain began to disintegrate bit by bit.

Of course, he wasn't just going to passively allow everything to unfold. The Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree down below began to sway violently at his behest, releasing a burst of immense time law powers that rose up into the air.

At the same time, a layer of golden sand rose up from the ground, while the winding river down below also ascended into the heavens.

Simultaneously, a fiery meteor shower came raining down from above, and the entire spirit domain was plunged into a state of chaos as the four bursts of time law powers clashed against the full moon formed by the Mantra Treasured Axis.

A resounding boom rang out, accompanied by an explosion of golden light as waves of golden ripples swept through the entire spirit domain.

A burst of time law power fluctuations surged out of the Celestial Time Array as well, but not only did the two not clash against one another, they fused together to enshroud the entire spirit domain in a burst of peculiar power.

Immediately thereafter, his spirit domain rapidly shrank down until it was only encompassing an area with a radius of several hundred feet around Han Li.

He felt as if the space outside the spirit domain had completely fallen still. The forest was no longer swaying, the mist was no longer rising, and even the seemed to have stopped blowing.

At the same time, the suction force released by the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Heavenly Wheel Sundial overhead had also faded away, and it seemed that the two were beginning to fuse in a far more placid and stable manner.

Han Li was rather perplexed by this, and he couldn't make sense of what had just happened.

He made a hand seal to try and withdraw his spirit domain, only to discover that it refused to heed his command.

An alarmed look appeared on his face as he rose up into the air, attempting to leave the Flower Branch domain, only to find himself trapped within the confines of his own spirit domain.

This is certainly troublesome...

Clearly, the fusion of the Heavenly Wheel Sundial and the Mantra Treasured Axis had triggered some type of change in the Celestial Time Array and his spirit domain, resulting in his entrapment.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he quickly thought of a way out. Seeing as he was trapped here due to his loss of control over his spirit domain, he should be able to get out of this predicament by regaining control of the spirit domain.

However, that was not going to be a simple process. His Mantra Treasured Axis was currently in the process of evolving to the Oneness Tier, and if he wanted his spirit domain to return to normal, that was an issue that he would have to address.

The problem was that he didn't have sufficient time law powers to support the Mantra Treasured Axis through this process.

Thankfully, this space had stabilized itself for now, so as long as he continued to cultivate the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to accumulate more time law powers, he would eventually be able to complete the process.

With that in mind, a dismayed look appeared on his face. Assuming that the Celestial Time Array was still operating as normal, he only had around six thousand years left, but he could easily be trapped in his spirit domain for tens of thousands of years.

In any case, he had no choice but to embark on this path.

Having made up his mind, he immediately sat down with his legs crossed and continued to cultivate.

......

Several thousand years flew by in a flash.

Han Li's spirit domain was filled with a vast abundance of time law powers, but at the moment, Han Li was looking up at the golden moon in the sky with a perplexed expression.

Even the Mantra Treasured Axis has already reached the Oneness Tier, so why...

At this point, the fusion between the Heavenly Wheel Sundial and the Mantra Treasured Axis was already complete, yet he was still unable to leave his spirit domain.

Is it still not enough?

......

Several thousand more years passed by in the blink of an eye.

The Immortal Origin Stones in the Celestial Time Array should've already been used up long ago, and the Mantra Treasured Axis had also reached the Oneness Tier, so the spirit domain should've returned to normal, but Han Li was still trapped here.

Over the past several thousand years, he had been cultivating diligently, and more and more changes had appeared in his spirit domain.

Outlines of mountain ranges had already begun to appear on the ground below, and they were also looking more substantial, not as much as the lush forest that grew upon them, but they had clearly also reached the Creation Tier.

However, the river of time remained illusory and hollow, clearly yet to reach the Creation Tier like the mountains.

"Why?!" Han Li roared in a frustrated manner as he leaped up and threw a punch at his own spirit domain.

A massive, golden fist projection erupted out of his fist, crashing into the spirit domain with an earth-shattering boom.

However, the golden light barrier above only rippled violently for a moment before settling down again.

After venting his frustrations through his fist, Han Li was feeling a little less agitated, and he sat back down again. There was no point in wallowing in frustration, so he may as well take this time to continue cultivating.

Perhaps I'll be freed once all of my other time-attribute law treasures also reach the Creation Tier, Han Li thought to himself.

Chapter 1197: Breaking Out of Purgatory

Over ninety thousand years flew by in a flash.

Everything in the Flower Branch domain remained completely unchanged, a perfectly still snapshot in time.

Han Li remained seated in his spirit domain, looking rather haggard and unkempt.

The situation that he was in was far more troublesome than he had anticipated. As early as twenty thousand years ago, all of his time-attribute law treasures had already reached the Creation Tier, elevating the entire spirit domain to the Creation Tier.

Among them, the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree had even gone a step further, reaching the Oneness Tier.

This state of imbalance proved to be very difficult to resolve, and Han Li remained trapped in his spirit domain.

This is it!

Han Li raised his head slightly while sweeping a sleeve through the air, and the Eon Divine Lamp flew out of his grasp before passing through the Mantra Treasured Axis to reach the very top of the spirit domain.

Countless stars formed by the Time Severing Torch were hanging in the sky, and as soon as the Eon Divine Lamp rose up into the air, all of the stars began to rapidly converge, condensing into a single golden fireball that descended into the Eon Divine Lamp.

The Eon Divine Lamp began to glow radiantly as all of the runes on its surface lit up before flying out one after another, vanishing into the spirit domain.

Immediately thereafter, the lamp began to take on an insubstantial form, then disintegrated into countless specks of fire that also vanished into the spirit domain.

Han Li looked up and was greeted by the sight of a lone moon nestled in a bed of radiant stars, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

He began channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with all his might while carefully keeping track of everything that was happening in his spirit domain.

The entire spirit domain was teeming with life, thanks to the exuberant, green glow emanating from the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree Forest, but the river of time remained insubstantial in form, giving it the appearance of an illusion hovering on top of the mountains below.

Han Li knew that once he collected a suitable water and earth-attribute time law treasure and refined them into the spirit domain, then a perfect equilibrium would be achieved, elevating his spirit domain to the Oneness Tier.

Let me see just how much longer you can trap me here!

A look of steely resolve appeared on Han Li's face as he raised both hands to the heavens.

The full moon above his head instantly began to radiate dazzling, golden light, while the ground incessantly as countless branches and vines came extending out of the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree forest.

However, the golden light was unable to spread beyond the confines of the spirit domain, while the roots of the Twin Birth Tree were also unable to spread out of the spirit domain.

As soon as they emerged from the spirit domain to extend into the earth of the outside world, they would immediately wither away into nothingness.

Han Li was already accustomed to this as he had already attempted the same thing many times before.

His hope was that if he could extend his power out of the spirit domain to damage the Celestial Time Array, then perhaps he would be able to break out of this predicament.

Only attacks that were imbued with immense time law powers had any hope of bursting through the spirit domain, and all of his time-attribute law treasures had already fused with the spirit domain, so he could only use the power of the spirit domain to try and achieve this objective.

The problem was that the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree didn't excel in offensive prowess, which was why he had invested the time to elevate the Time Severing Torch to the Creation Torch, following which he infused the Eon Divine Lamp into it.

The countless specks of fiery starlight in the sky came plummeting down from above at his behest, and as they descended, they transformed into a barrage of giant fireballs that crashed down with awe-inspiring power.

A burst of violent rumbling rang out as the entire spirit domain was plunged into complete chaos, and the mountain range formed by the Illusory Dawn Sand was instantly razed to the ground, reduced to a sea of golden sand.

The ground beneath the spirit domain was also severely ravaged, sending powerful shockwaves that spread all the way to the bamboo pavilion.

An array core that had been set up there was instantly damaged, causing the entire Celestial Time Array to cease operating.

Immediately thereafter, a symbol that belonged to the Heavenly Wheel Sundial on the Mantra Treasured Axis up above dimmed as a result, and the time law powers emanating from it also rapidly abated.

The spirit domain instantly reverted back to its original size to encompass the entire Flower Branch domain, and Han Li was finally free.

A mixture of elation and remorse welled up in his heart at his newfound freedom.

If he hadn't been so greedy and triggered the process to elevate his spirit domain to the Creation Tier, then he wouldn't have been trapped here for so long. At this point, Xiaobai had surely already been summoned back to the primordial land, and the Reincarnation Palace mission against the Nine Origins Temple had to have been an event of the distant past.

In any case, the damage was already done, so there was no point in crying over spilled milk. Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to withdraw his spirit domain, then packed up the Celestial Time Array.

He made his way over to the bamboo pavilion, then leaned down to pick up an Immortal Origin Stone from the array core.

How could this be?

Han Li was bewildered to discover that the Immortal Origin Stone was still glowing, albeit only very faintly, indicating that there was still some residual immortal spiritual power left within it.

Right at this moment, Xiaobai suddenly came bursting into the bamboo pavilion, and as soon as he caught sight of Han Li, he immediately began complaining, "What have you been doing in here, Master? I was worried, so I came to check on you, but the door was sealed shut!"

A puzzled look then appeared on his face at the sight of Han Li's haggard appearance.

"You didn't go back to the primordial land?" Han Li asked in a perplexed manner.

"Why would I go back to the primordial land? What happened to you, Master?" Xiaobai asked in a wary manner, thinking that Han Li had perhaps suffered qi deviation during his seclusion, thereby affecting his mental faculties.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he gave Xiaobai a brief recount of what he had experienced during his time in seclusion.

"So you were in here for two thousand years, then another two thousand years, then over ninety thousand years... That's over a hundred thousand years! It doesn't make any sense!" Xiaobai exclaimed.

"How many years have passed in the outside world?" Han Li asked.

"Only fifty years," Xiaobai replied.

Han Li was rooted to the spot in disbelief upon hearing this, and his dumbstruck display only served as further evidence in Xiaobai's eyes that he wasn't in a sound state of mind.

Right at this moment, he suddenly noticed Han Li's aura, and his eyes instantly lit up as he exclaimed in an ecstatic manner, "Master! You've reached the Great Encompassment Stage!"

Han Li was snapped back to his senses by Xiaobai's yell of elation, and he murmured to himself, "No wonder there's still some immortal spiritual power left in these Immortal Origin Stones. It all makes sense now..."

"What are you talking about, Master? I'm getting really confused," Xiaobai whined.

"Originally, the Celestial Time Array was only able to accelerate the flow of time by a hundredfold, so the first four thousand years that I spent in my spirit domain equated to forty years in the outside world.

“However, for some reason, once the Heavenly Wheel Sundial began fusing with my Mantra Treasured Axis, the rate of time acceleration was significantly increased to around ten thousand fold, which means that only ten years passed in the outside world during the final one hundred thousand years of my seclusion," Han Li explained.

Xiaobai was struggling to make sense of all of this, but one thing that he did manage to understand was that Han Li had cultivated for a hundred thousand years during the final decade that he had spent in here.

"That's incredible!" Xiaobai exclaimed.

"It certainly turned out well, but I was almost trapped in there indefinitely," Han Li said with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"In any case, the outcome is good, and that's all that matters," Xiaobai said with a smile, and Han Li nodded in response.

If he could somehow replicate this set of special circumstances, then that would be unfathomably beneficial to his future cultivation.

"Where's the Essence Fire Child?" Han Li asked.

"It's still outside on lookout duty. I decided to come in once I noticed that the restriction in the Flower Branch domain had been lifted," Xiaobai replied.

"Sorry to make the two of you worry," Han Li sighed.

"How does it feel to have reached the Great Encompassment Stage?" Xiaobai asked with a smile.

"There were some mishaps in my earlier cultivation, so my spirit domain is yet to be fully consolidated. Seeing as we still have some time, I'll stay in here for a while longer to consolidate my cultivation base," Han Li said.

"No problem! I'll go tell the Essence Fire Child. It's really worried about you as well," Xiaobai replied, and Han Li nodded in response with a faint smile.

Following Xiaobai's departure, Han Li released his spirit domain once again to encompass the entire Flower Branch domain, then snapped his fingers to conjure up all of his time-attribute law treasure manifestations.

As he walked through the spirit domain, he was able to bend and shift the environment to his will with just his thoughts, and after taking some more time to familiarize himself with his spirit domain, he felt a little more confident about his chances of staging a successful rescue of Jin Tong.

Chapter 1198: Myriad Treasure Festival

Over ten years flew by in a flash.

Greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, Gilded City.

Gilded City was situated in the northwestern part of the Greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, and it was one of the immortal region's largest cities, ranking alongside the likes of Nine Origins City, Golden Origin City, and Hundred Creations City, home to the Nine Origins Temple, the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, and the Hundred Creations Mountain, respectively.

In contrast with the other three major cities, Gilded City wasn't ruled over by any superpower, so it was a relatively free place.

The city attracted many cultivators who wished to be free from the oppression of the Nine Origins Temple, the Hundred Creations Mountain, and the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, and they had formed an alliance called the Sun Moon Alliance.

The top-end power of the Sun Moon Alliance was inferior to that of the Nine Origins Temple and the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, but it had immense potential and was very friendly to some lesser powers and vagrant cultivators. As a result, more and more smaller powers had joined the sect over time, significantly bolstering its overall strength.

Inside a booth in a lavish, nine-story restaurant in the city, three figures were seated at a table, having some wine together, and one of them was none other than Han Li.

He was joined by Weeping Soul and Xiaobai, and all three of them were of course in disguise.

Even though the Reincarnation Mission hadn't yet commenced, Han Li had some other matters to attend to, so he had arrived in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region early.

Now that he was at the Great Encompassment Stage, he had become far more confident and wasn't as timid as before.

In another pleasing turn of events, Weeping Soul had finally awakened and also reached the Great Encompassment Stage.

"I didn't think that there would be a place in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region free from the influence of the Nine Origins Temple and the Golden Origin Immortal Palace," Xiaobai remarked as he took large swigs out of a green cup, clearly very fond of the wine inside.

"Don't get complacent. Gilded City may be under the jurisdiction of the Sun Moon Alliance, but I'm sure there must be Nine Origins Temple and Golden Origin Immortal Palace spies here, so we still have to proceed with caution," Han Li warned.

"It's fine, we have nothing to worry about with Big Sister Weeping Soul on our side. She can detect animosity from a mile away, so no one will be able to sneak up on us," Xiaobai said with a wide smile, and Han Li also turned to Weeping Soul with a faint smile.

Not only had Weeping Soul's powers taken a significant stride following her progression to the Great Encompassment Stage, her sensory abilities had also been further enhanced, allowing her to detect the presence of animosity.

Han Li had conducted an experiment to discover that even he couldn't mask his animosity from Weeping Soul, despite his tremendous spiritual sense.

Of course, it was possible for him to mask his animosity from Weeping Soul by enveloping his body in his own time law powers, but anyone who tried to approach them with their entire body enveloped in law powers would be a huge red flag in itself, and their intentions would be made abundantly clear.

"The law powers that I've cultivated are related to souls, so I'm naturally more sensitive in this regard, but don't place too much trust into this ability of mine. It's possible for other cultivators of similar law powers to get past my detection by using certain soul fluctuation concealment techniques," Weeping Soul said.

"Cultivators of such law powers are very rare, so it's unlikely for us to encounter one. On top of that, I'm sure you'll be able to detect the presence of such cultivators, so if such an encounter does arise, then we'll just have to be extra careful," Han Li replied with a faint smile, seemingly very confident in Weeping Soul.

"That's right, I have full trust in Big Sister Weeping Soul!" Xiaobai chimed in with a wide smile.

"I'll do my best," Weeping Soul said with a faint smile of her own.

Han Li cast his gaze out the window of the booth as a slightly troubled look appeared on his face.

He had already been in Gilded City for some time, and during this time, he had explored many avenues to try and find out information about the Nine Origins Temple and Jin Tong.

However, given the turmoil in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, the Nine Origins Temple was exercising an even stricter policy of secrecy than normal, making it impossible for Han Li to uncover any useful information.

"Don't worry, Master, there's still loads of time left until the Bodhi Banquet, so I'm sure Boss is fine," Xiaobai reassured.

Han Li nodded in response, then cast his gaze out the window again.

Right at this moment, the sound of a gong strike rang out from afar, and Han Li's eyes instantly lit up as he cast his gaze toward a giant shop in the distance, where the sound had come from.

The shop stretched for close to ten kilometers, and it was entirely constructed from a sky blue material that was riddled with countless specks of starry light, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

Placed on either side of the shop's entrance was a jade Qilin statue, and standing beside the statues were units of bodily refinement cultivators clad in suits of blue armor, all of whom had opened over a hundred profound acupoints.

Judging from the faint light emanating from their suits of armor, they were clearly all graded immortal treasures, serving as further testament to the power and prestige of the establishment.

Above the entrance of the shop hung a huge plaque that read "Sun Moon Pavilion" in elegant, flowing characters that were giving off an immense aura, indicating that their inscriber had to have been someone of an extremely lofty cultivation base.

At this moment, many streaks of light were converging toward the entrance of the Sun Moon Pavilion from all directions before fading away to reveal a growing group of cultivators, all of whom were quite advanced in cultivation base.

There was no lack of High Zenith cultivators among them, and all of them were chatting among themselves in an excited manner.

"This is what I've been waiting for! The Myriad Treasure Festival happens once every ten thousand years. I've heard that there are always many exceptional treasures presented during the Sun Moon Pavilion auction."

"The Sun Moon Pavilion has been constantly reaching new heights of late. I've heard that they're planning to compete with the Hundred Creations Mountain during this Myriad Treasure Festival, so they'll definitely have prepared some outstanding treasures. Our budget is rather tight, so we may not be able to buy anything, but it'll certainly be an exciting event to behold."

"I've saved up as many Immortal Origin Stones as I could. Hopefully, I can purchase a pill or two that can help me make a breakthrough."

"I'm planning to purchase a good immortal treasure so I can hunt for more powerful beasts in the primordial land."

......

"Let's go, the auction is about to begin," Han Li said as he rose to his feet in the booth.

Xiaobai immediately sprang up from his chair with an excited look on his face.

"Xiaobai, your aura is being concealed by the Reincarnation Palace mask, but it may not be able to fully conceal the aura of your Ink-Eyed Pixiu bloodline. There are going to many powerful cultivators at the auction, so it's best for you to remain hidden," Han Li suddenly said, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, sweeping the dumbstruck Xiaobai into the Flower Branch domain before he had a chance to protest.

"Let's go," Han Li said to Weeping Soul, and the two of them emerged from the restaurant.

In addition to trying to find information about the Nine Origins Temple, Han Li's second objective for coming to Gilded City was to attend this auction.

In order to enhance its own reputation and status, the Hundred Creations Mountain hosted a celebratory event once every ten thousand years with all of its branches in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region in participation, and this event was referred to as the Myriad Treasure Festival.

All of the other major trading houses in the greater Golden Immortal Stage would take this opportunity to hold auctions of their own, hoping to profit from the event.

The Sun Moon Alliance was almost on par with the Hundred Creations Mountain in terms of power, and it was also operating an enormous trading house, so it was naturally not going to remain a passive bystander.

With the steady growth of the Sun Moon Alliance, competition between the two superpowers during the Myriad Treasure Festivals had become more and more fierce over time.

The greater Golden Origin Immortal Region was one of the largest immortal regions of the True Immortal Realm, and it was also home top-tier sects like the Nine Origins Temple and the Hundred Creations Mountain, so there were countless precious treasures and materials constantly flowing into the immortal region from smaller immortal regions, and everything that appeared during the Myriad Treasure Festival was the cream of the crop.

Back when Han Li first left Eight Plains Mountain, the primary concern on his mind was finding the final time-attribute law material to establish equilibrium in his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and he was very relieved to have heard about the Myriad Treasure Festival from the Reincarnation Palace.

His original plan was to purchase the final time-attribute law material during the festival at all costs, but that was no longer necessary as he had obtained it from Wyrm 3.

Even so, he was still very much looking forward to the festival.

After all, he was going to be venturing into the Nine Origins Temple soon, so he had to make some preparations.

On top of that, Weeping Soul was also missing a suitable immortal treasure to use, so this was the ideal opportunity to find something for her as well.

The problem was that even though the biggest auction of all was going to be held at the Hundred Creations Mountain main branch, given the Hundred Creations Mountain's close ties with the Nine Origins Temple and the Heavenly Court, Han Li naturally didn't dare to go there, and that was why he had settled for the Sun Moon Pavilion auction.

Han Li and Weeping Soul made their way into the Sun Moon Pavilion, and in order to avoid attracting attention, they had both suppressed their cultivation bases to the late-High Zenith Stage. However, they didn't suppress it any further than that as keeping too low a profile during events like auctions came with its own drawbacks.

They were approached by a beautiful Golden Immortal Stage woman with a pair of blue eyebrows that matched her blue dress, and she greeted, "Welcome, seniors. My name is Lan Mei, and I am an administrative disciple of the Sun Moon Pavilion. Please allow me to serve as your guide."

"Lead the way," Han Li said.

"Given your cultivation bases, both of you are entitled to VIP seating. Please come with me," Lan Mei said as she led the way ahead.

"Do you have a list of the treasures that are going to appear during the auction?" Han Li asked.

"Yes, I have them here," Lan Mei said as she offered a pair of blue jade slips to Han Li and Weeping Soul.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this.

"This is generally strictly confidential information, is it not? Keeping the auction items a secret can pique the interest of the auction-goers and generate more buzz, so I'm surprised the Sun Moon Pavilion is readily handing out this information."

He had only raised the question just in case, and he wasn't expecting an affirmative response.

"The leader of our Sun Moon Alliance says that integrity and sincerity are the keys to business, and that there's no need to engage in such tacky maneuvers. That is the policy that our Sun Moon Alliance has always abided by," Lan Mei replied with a faint smile, and it was clear that she harbored a great deal of admiration for the alliance leader.

Chapter 1199: Extensive List

"That's very admirable of him," Han Li said, then injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip to discover that it contained over ten thousand auction items, along with their starting prices.

However, the order of the auction wasn't clearly laid out, but that was understandable. After all, having all of the information presented too comprehensively would ruin the fun.

With Han Li's tremendous spiritual sense, he was able to quickly memorize all of the auction items, and he had made a mental list of all of the auction items of interest.

"Where have you come from, and what are you planning to buy, Seniors? Are you preparing for Great Encompassment Stage breakthroughs?" Lan Mei asked.

"Both of us are vagrant cultivators who travel from place to place with no real home to speak of. As for what we're planning to buy, there's nothing specific that we have in mind, so we'll just have to see," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

Lan Mei didn't pry any further, offering a bright smile as she said, "Our Sun Moon Pavilion is taking this auction very seriously, and we've prepared many exceptional items to suit a wide range of needs."

Han Li nodded in response, then asked some more questions about the auction, all of which Lan Mei was able to answer in a satisfactory manner.

Weeping Soul was rather displeased to see Han Li chatting so amicably with Lan Mei, and she pouted slightly in chagrin as she stoically ignored the two of them.

Before long, the two of them had been led to an independent room.

The room was only around twenty to thirty feet in size, and inside was a long bench and a white stone table, upon the latter of which were placed cups of spirit tea and bowls of immortal fruits.

The furnishings were quite minimalistic, but the entire place was very tidy, and there was a faint, soothing fragrance in the air.

The room was closed off on all sides with only a window on one wall, through which a giant plaza that was over ten kilometers in size could be seen. The plaza was stacked with countless seats, the majority of which had already been occupied.

There were also other VIP booths hovering in the air above the plaza alongside this one, and Han Li turned to Lan Mei as he said, "Alright, you can go now."

"If you need anything, just ring this bell," Lan Mei replied as she set a small bell onto the table, then departed from the booth.

Following her departure, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up an azure light barrier that encompassed the entire room, following which he turned to Weeping Soul as he asked, "Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?"

"You were clearly thoroughly enjoying speaking to her, so a third wheel like me should just keep her mouth shut," Weeping Soul replied with more than a hint of passive-aggression in her voice.

"What are you talking about? I was just asking her some questions about the auction," Han Li said in an amused manner.

Weeping Soul's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, but she was clearly still not happy.

"Alright, we don't have time for this. The auction is about to begin, did any of the treasures in the jade slip catch your eye?" Han Li asked.

A hesitant look appeared on Weeping Soul's face upon hearing this, and she pointed out a pair of immortal treasures on the jade slip to Han Li as she replied, "I'm interested in these, but both of them have very high starting prices."

After examining the pair of immortal treasures that Weeping Soul had pointed out, Han Li said, "These two immortal treasures are indeed very suitable for you. Don't worry about the cost."

He had expended close to twenty million Immortal Origin Stones to power the Celestial Time Array, leaving roughly fifty million Immortal Origin Stones left. These two immortal treasures were definitely going to be very expensive, but the law powers that they contained were rather uncommon, so there most likely wasn't going to be much interest in them.

Having reached the Great Encompassment Stage, he wasn't going to be able to make any further breakthroughs in the near future. Hence, he had no use for the space of accelerated time, so he could dedicate these Immortal Origin Stones to another use.

"Thank you, Master!" Weeping Soul exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

Right at this moment, an expression of intent was transmitted into Han Li's mind from the Essence Fire Child in the Flower Branch domain, requesting some fire-attribute materials to replenish itself.

Han Li quickly transmitted an affirmative response to this request.

There were many materials on the auction list that fit the Essence Fire Child's needs, and they weren't very expensive, so he could easily purchase some.

Xiaobai was also yelling and whining in the Flower Branch domain, but instead of asking Han Li to purchase him any treasures, he was demanding to be let out to watch the auction.

Han Li could only inject a wisp of his spiritual sense into the Flower Branch domain to project the scene of the auction taking place outside.

Right at this moment, three loud gong strikes rang out, indicating the official commencement of the auction.

A portly elderly man with a wide face and a pair of large ears appeared on the auction platform amid a flash of red light.

Despite his unremarkable appearance, he was a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator, so he was certainly qualified to serve as the auctioneer.

"Today marks the commencement of our greater Golden Origin Immortal Region's highly anticipated Myriad Treasure Festival! Welcome to our Sun Moon Pavilion. I hope all of you can depart at the end of the auction with bountiful returns. Alright, that's enough from me, without further ado, here is the first auction item," the elderly man declared, and several armorclad guards carried a jade box onto the auction platform.

Inside the jade box was a millstone-sized yellow crystal with countless rays of yellow light swirling around it, giving off immense earth law power fluctuations.

The gravitational force near the auction platform was increased by several thousandfold as a result, making the jade box very difficult to carry for the armorclad guards.

"This Earth Emperor Crystal comes from the Vast Earth Immortal Region. It arose at an unfathomable depth beneath the ground and has been absorbing the essential energy of the earth for countless years, granting it more than enough powers to be used to refine even a fourth tier earth-attribute immortal treasure.

“The starting price is five million Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least a hundred thousand Immortal Origin Stones," the elderly man auctioneer introduced in a placid manner, making no attempt to praise the treasure, but that only made him seem more trustworthy and reliable.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the plaza immediately became abuzz with excited chatter.

Han Li's eyes also lit up slightly at the sight of the Earth Emperor Crystal.

Even though he had already spotted the item on the jade slip, it didn't have the same impact as seeing the actual item.

Earth Emperor Crystals were a supreme earth-attribute material equivalent to Heavenly Vajra Diamonds among metal-attribute materials, and it was the most sought after material for all cultivators of earth law powers.

On top of that, this Earth Emperor Crystal could be used to refine fourth tier immortal treasures.

Fifth tier immortal treasures weren't exactly common, but they weren't all that rare, either. Generally speaking, all Great Encompassment cultivators would be able to secure one with some effort or by incurring some financial cost. After all, as long as an immortal treasure was refined from decent materials, it could eventually be nurtured to the fifth tier over time.

This was what Han Li had done with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

However, that was not the case for fourth tier immortal treasures. There were extremely stringent material and skill requirements when it came to refining fourth tier immortal treasures, and it was said that completing refinement of such a treasure would even incur a treasure tribulation, the exact details of which weren't very clear to Han Li, but what he did know was that even though they were only separated by a single tier, fourth tier immortal treasures were vastly more powerful than their fifth tier counterparts.

Hence, fourth tier immortal treasures were extremely rare in the True Immortal Realm, even among True Immortal cultivators, so the value of this Earth Emperor Crystal could not be understated.

As expected of the Myriad Treasure Festival for such a precious material to be presented as the opening item.

Han Li had no need for the Earth Emperor Crystal, but many of the other auction-goers had begun eagerly bidding for it.

In the blink of an eye, the price elevated to beyond the ten million mark, and it was ultimately secured by a cultivator in a VIP booth for twelve million Immortal Origin Stones.

"The next item is a fifth tier fire dao pill..."

One extraordinary item after another was brought onto the stage, and the atmosphere in the auction venue was quickly heating up.

Even though the prices were very steep, many cultivators were willing to pay exorbitant sums for the items that they needed. After all, if they were to miss this opportunity, it was unclear when another chance would arise again.

Close to a day flew by in a flash, and Han Li hadn't placed a single bid during this time.

"Our next item is a fifth tier immortal treasure by the name of the Infernal Ghost Claw. It was forged from the claw of a Great Encompassment Stage Infernal Ghost Beast from the Infernal Sea Immortal Region, combined with countless malicious souls, eighteen types of ghostly blood and thirty-six types of ghostly qi before being forged in infernal flames for a million years.

“It contains tremendous yin ghost law powers and possesses extremely formidable penetrative and corrosive abilities."

The item in question was a black, nine-fingered claw that was around ten feet in size with a vast cloud of black qi swirling around it.

Chapter 1200: Bidding War

Han Li's eyes instantly lit up slightly at the sight of the black claw, and Weeping Soul also sat up a little straighter.

This Infernal Ghost Claw was one of the two immortal treasures that she desired.

The auctioneer cast an incantation seal into the black claw, and a dense whirlwind of black runes instantly flew out from within, sending a gust of fierce yin wind erupting out of the giant claw.

Even though restrictions had been set up near the auction platform, a burst of bone-chilling yin power still swept over the entire venue, and some of the auction-goers with lesser cultivation bases were left trembling in their seats.

The auctioneer changed an incantation, and the black claw instantly swelled to the size of a house before grabbing onto a huge, black rock that was several hundred feet tall beside the platform.

According to the rules of the Sun Moon Pavilion, a demonstration had to be held for all offensive immortal treasures presented in the auction to allow auction-goers to witness their power. The black rock was a material that was renowned for its resilience, making it the perfect subject for such demonstrations.

Several immortal treasures had already been tested on the giant rock, so it was riddled with pits and bumps, but was still overall intact.

A faint thud rang out as the black claw fell upon the huge rock, and the latter was instantly split into around a dozen pieces, with plumes of green smoke rising up from the cross-sections, indicating severe corrosion.

Many of the auction-goers couldn't help but gasp upon seeing this, while Weeping Soul's eyes lit up with excitement.

In contrast, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. Given the Infernal Ghost Claw's immense offensive prowess, it was undoubtedly the most powerful immortal treasure to have been presented thus far, so its final price was almost certainly going to be an astronomical one.

With fifty million Immortal Origin Stones in his possession, securing this treasure was not an issue, but it would leave him very short on funds for the rest of the auction.

"I'm not a cultivator of yin ghost law powers, so I can only unleash less than a tenth of this treasure's power. In the hands of someone who can make full use of it, this Infernal Ghost Claw is sure to be unimaginably powerful. Without further ado, let the bidding begin. The starting price is eight million Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least five hundred thousand Immortal Origin Stones," the auctioneer declared.

"8,600,000!"

"9,200,000"

"Ten million!"

......

Swayed by the demonstration of its power, many of the auction-goers were bidding for the Infernal Ghost Claw, even though cultivators of yin ghost law powers were very rare.

Han Li chose not to take part in the bidding for now. He was determined to secure the treasure, so he just had to make sure to place the final bid.

Before long, the price was raised to fifteen million Immortal Origin Stones, and most of the bidders had already dropped out of the bidding war.

"Sixteen million!"

Han Li finally placed his first bid.

"16,500,000!"

An elderly voice rang out from a nearby VIP booth.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the VIP booth in question.

Even though all of the booths were enshrouded in powerful restrictions, they weren't able to keep out his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Han Li had opened virtually all of his profound acupoints in the Asura Blood Gate, including some in his eyes, thereby significantly enhancing the power of his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

During the initial stages of cultivating the Infernal Devilish Eyes, one's pupils would release purple light that grew brighter as one's mastery of the ability deepened.

However, once the Infernal Devilish Eyes were cultivated to a certain level, the purple light would gradually fade and turn to black, and a pair of pure black pupils were the telltale sign of full mastery of the Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Han Li was currently not far away from this level of mastery.

Inside the other booth was a gray-robed elderly man at the early-Great Encompassment Stage. He was holding a white cane that looked as if it were crafted from human bone, and he was oblivious to Han Li's intrusive gaze.

There was a nervous look on his face, indicating that this was as deep as his pockets could go.

"I can sense some tension and agitation in his soul fluctuations, so he must be close to reaching his limit," Weeping Soul said.

Han Li took a surprised glance at Weeping Soul, then placed another bid, raising the price to eighteen million.

The gray-robed elderly man heaved a long sigh and dropped out of the bidding war.

With that, the entire venue fell silent.

The Infernal Ghost Claw was indeed an extremely powerful treasure, but this price was already beyond what it was worth.

Both Han Li and Weeping Soul were very pleased to see this, and the auctioneer was also very happy with this price.

Right as he was about to make a final enquiry for further bids, a cold voice rang out from another VIP booth.

"Nineteen million!"

Weeping Soul's face immediately fell upon hearing this, and Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward the booth in question.

Sitting inside the booth were six black-robed figures with hoods over their heads to completely conceal their faces.

Furthermore, there was a layer of rippling, black light flowing over all of their hoods, and the black light was able to keep even Han Li's Infernal Devilish Eyes at bay.

All six of them were currently seated in silence, and it was unclear who the bidder was.

Right at this moment, one of the smaller figures of the six raised their head slightly, seemingly having detected Han Li's probing, and they swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a cloud of dense, red mist in the booth, completely keeping out Han Li's Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"Twenty million!" Han Li declared while simultaneously giving Weeping Soul a look, and she immediately understood his intentions, closing her eyes to examine the soul fluctuations of the six figures in the other booth.

However, she then quickly reopened her eyes and said in a defeated manner, "It's not working. The bidder is also a cultivator of soul-related law powers, and they're able to conceal their soul fluctuations from me."

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon hearing this.

"Twenty-two million!" the voice from the other booth snapped, seemingly growing a little annoyed by Han Li's persistence.

"Let's just leave it, Master, it's too expensive," Weeping Soul said, but the reluctance in her voice was very apparent.

Han Li gave Weeping Soul a reassuring look, then made another bid.

"Twenty-five million!"

A stir ran through the entire venue as everyone turned to Han Li's booth, but their prying eyes were kept out by the restrictions that he had set up earlier.

"Twenty-seven million!" the cold voice retaliated after a brief silence.

"Thirty million!" Han Li countered, much to the astonishment of all of the other auction-goers.

Thirty million Immortal Origin Stones was far too steep a price to pay for the Infernal Ghost Claw, but he had already promised to secure it for Weeping Soul, so he couldn't back down.

On top of that, the Infernal Ghost Claw really was perfectly suited to Weeping Soul's law powers, so it was a worthy investment.

A tall and thin figure in the other booth cast a cold gaze toward Han Li's booth for a moment, then gave a cold harrumph and placed no further bids.

On the auction platform, the ecstatic auctioneer quickly made a final enquiry for further bids, then declared the Infernal Ghost Claw as sold.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief, but at the same time, he was rather concerned by his remaining balance of only twenty million Immortal Origin Stones.

The other immortal treasure that Weeping Soul had her sights set on wasn't inferior to the Infernal Ghost Claw, so that was most likely also going to be very expensive, and he also had to purchase materials for the Essence Fire Child on top of that.

Before long, Lan Mei was sent to deliver the Infernal Ghost Claw to his booth.

Han Li issued the Immortal Origin Stones, while Weeping Soul gleefully sucked the Infernal Ghost Claw into her body for refinement.

"Lan Mei, is it possible for me to sell treasure to your Sun Moon Pavilion?" Han Li asked.

"Of course! What would you like to sell, Senior?" Lan Mei asked.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon around a dozen head-sized blue crystals, all of which were flashing with radiant lightning.

Tremendous lightning law power fluctuations erupted out of the blue crystals, causing Lan Mei to tremble uncontrollably, while her complexion also turned deathly pale.

Han Li immediately conjured up a golden lightning barrier upon seeing this, containing most of the lightning law power fluctuations, and only then was Lan Mei able to steady herself.

After giving the blue crystals a close examination, a stunned look appeared on her face as she concluded, "These are Lightning Shock Stones!"

"That's correct. How much can I sell them for?" Han Li asked.

Lightning Shock Stones were a type of premium lighting-attribute material. It was inferior to the Earth Emperor Cyrstal and the Heavenly Vajra Diamond, but certainly not by much.

He had stumbled upon these Lightning Shock Stones in the heart of the Five Light Lightning Region while refining his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

"By my estimates, every single one of these Lightning Shock Stones is over a million Immortal Origin Stones in value. I can't handle such a large transaction myself, so please wait a moment while I fetch an administrative elder," Lan Mei said before hurriedly departing.

Han Li was in no hurry, and he cast his gaze down toward the plaza below, then shifted his attention to the booth from before.

Given the powerful concealment abilities of their black cloaks, the six figures in the booth clearly had something to hide.

There would've been no need for them to do this had they just been normal vagrant cultivators, so could it be that they were from the Nine Origins Temple, the Hundred Creations Mountain, or the Golden Origin Immortal Palace?

All of a sudden, a concerning thought sprang into his mind.

Could it be that they have something to do with me?

Chapter 1201: Suspicions

"What's wrong, Master? You seem a little unsettled," Weeping Soul asked.

"Weeping Soul, keep an eye on the six people in that both. Ideally, find out who they are and why they've come here," Han Li communicated through voice transmission.

Weeping Soul didn't know why she was being asked to do this, but she still did as she told.

Right at this moment, a woman dressed in a green daoist robe entered the booth with Lan Mei.

The woman was a Great Encompassment cultivator, and she was quite youthful in appearance. Her complexion was as rosy as a lotus flower, and there was a floral fragrance emanating from her body, indicating that she was a plant spirit rather than a human.

The woman's eyes lit up slightly at the sight of the Lightning Shock Stones in the booth, following which she turned to Han Li as she said, "Greetings, Fellow Daoist Shi. I am an administrative elder of the Sun Moon Pavilion, you can refer to me as Lotus Maiden."

"It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Lotus Maiden. Can the Sun Moon Pavilion afford these Lightning Shock Stones of mine?" Han Li asked.

"Of course. Even if you had tens of thousands of Lightning Shock Stones, our Sun Moon Pavilion would still be able to take them off your hands," Lotus Maiden replied with a faint smile.

"In that case, please give me an appraisal," Han Li said.

Lotus Maiden quickly swept her gaze over the Lightning Shock Stones, then said, "These Lightning Shock Stones are all of a very high caliber. I'm willing to offer 1.5 million Immortal Origin Stones for each one. There are thirteen in total, so that amounts of 19.5 million, which I can round up to twenty million for you. What do you say?"

Han Li was only expecting to be able to sell these Lightning Shock Stones for around fifteen million, so he naturally raised no objections to this.

"That's perfectly fine by me. I also have some other materials that I would like to sell," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air to produce a collection of miscellaneous materials.

He had been trying to sell these materials in the Reincarnation Palace for many years to no avail, so this was a perfect opportunity to get rid of them.

"This is a rather chaotic collection of items, but there are a few decent things here. How about this? I'll take everything off your hands for four million Immortal Origin Stones," Lotus Maiden offered.

Han Li nodded in agreement, making no effort to barter.

Perhaps he could earn a little more by selling everything individually, but getting rid of everything at once spared him a great deal of trouble.

With that, Han Li was able to recover twenty-four million Immortal Origin Stones, placing him in a much better mood.

Lotus Maiden promptly departed with Lan Mei, following which Weeping Soul turned to Han Li, clearly ready to report her findings.

"How did it go?" Han Li aked through voice transmission.

"I wasn't able to gather much information through their conversation just now, but I've managed to identify one of them," Weeping Soul replied.

"Who is it?" Han Li asked.

"Lan Yan, the woman that we encountered earlier in the Tai Sui Immortal Manor," Weeping Soul replied.

"Lan Yan? Are you sure?" Han Li asked as a surprised look appeared on his face.

"I'm certain of it. I was too fixated on the bidder just now, so I didn't examine the soul fluctuations of the others, but now that I've had a chance to look at them, one of them is definitely Lan Yan," Weeping Soul replied in a confident manner.

Han Li had full trust in Weeping Soul's sensory abilities, so he quickly accepted this verdict.

Lan Yan was a cultivator of the Nine Origins Temple, so her five companions were most likely also from the Nine Origins Temple. What were they doing here?

Han Li was silent for a moment, then instructed, "Continue keeping tabs on them and notify me if anything interesting comes up."

Weeping Soul immediately returned to the task at hand, while Han Li turned his attention back to the auction.

Some more time passed by before an auction item that caught Han Li's eye was presented.

"The next item is the beast core of a peak-High Zenith Stage Three-Legged Golden Crow. It contains boundless fire-attribute power and can be used to refine immortal treasures or to complement one's cultivation. The starting price is three million Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least a hundred thousand Immortal Origin Stones."

This was one of the items that Han Li was planning to purchase for the Essence Fire Child.

It was undoubtedly a precious item, but it was made to appear quite lackluster compared with the other treasures, so there were barely any bidders, and Han Li was able to secure the item for five million Immortal Origin Stones before tossing it into the Flower Branch domain.

The Essence Fire Child instantly took on its fire raven form, then pounced joyfully onto the beast core before devouring it.

Right at this moment, the next auction item was brought out, and it was a rectangular, black jade box with many talismans plastered over it, but there was still a burst of bone-chilling ghostly power seeping out from within the box even through the masses of talismans.

Both Han Li and Weeping Soul sat up a little straighter upon seeing this.

The auctioneer chanted an incantation, and the seal on the jade box was broken to reveal a short, black flute inside. The flute appeared to have been fashioned from a length of leg bone, and there was a skull attached to one end of it.

A burst of formidable ghostly power erupted out of the flute alongside a horrific shrieking sound that cut straight into the listener's soul, striking many of the auction-goers with a sense of immense discomfort.

The auctioneer hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air, and a white light barrier rose up over the auction platform to contain the power of the flute,

"Our next item is the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute, which is a fourth tier immortal treasure personally refined by the founding father of the Myriad Ghost Sect of the Infernal Sea Immortal Region, Nili the Enlightened.

“However, following the defeat that he suffered at the hands of Celestial Maiden Murong of the Supreme Sword Sect during their battle on the Infernal Sea, the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute was damaged and reduced to a fifth tier immortal treasure, but it's far more powerful than the average fifth tier immortal treasure.

“The flute specializes in attacking the soul, so I won't be able to give a demonstration of its powers here. The starting price is ten million Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by increments of at least five hundred thousand Immortal Origin Stones," the auctioneer declared.

Han Li was rather concerned after hearing this.

The information on the jade slip had indeed stated that the flute was an immortal treasure that attacked the soul, but it failed to mention that the flute was once a fourth tier immortal treasure.

With that in mind, it was most likely going to end up far more expensive than the Infernal Ghost Claw, so even the forty-five million Immortal Origin Stones in his possession may not be enough to secure it.

As these thoughts were running through his mind, the bidding had already begun, and it didn't take long for the price to be raised to twenty million.

"Twenty-five million!" Han Li declared, raising the price by five million in one go.

With his limited funds, he had to make impactful bids in the hope of scaring off other bidders.

Sure enough, the entire venue was cast into a stunned silence by his bid, and no further bids were placed.

However, it didn't take long before the silence was broken by the very same person who had competed with him for the Infernal Ghost Claw earlier.

"Twenty-eight million!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he was just about to place another bid when an arrogant voice rang out from another VIP booth.

"Thirty million!"

Han Li cast his gaze toward that booth to discover a blue-robed young man sitting inside.

"Thirty-three million!" Han Li yelled.

"Thirty-four million!" the blue-robed man countered as he took a displeased glance in the direction of Han Li's booth.

"Thirty-six million!"

The cold voice rang out once again, seemingly determined to come out on top.

The blue-robed man placed no further bids.

"Forty million!" Han Li declared, creating another massive stir.

Han Li's purchase of the Infernal Ghost Claw for thirty million Immortal Origin Stones was still fresh in everyone's minds, so all of the auction-goers were very curious about Han Li's status and wealth.

Han Li paid no heed to all of the auction-goers as his gaze remained fixed on the booth that Lan Yan was in.

The booth remained silent, yet right as Han Li was beginning to think that the bidding war was over, the cold voice rang out once again.

"Forty-five million!"

Han Li heaved a long sigh, and a wry smile appeared on his face as he said to Weeping Soul, "Looks like we won't be able to secure this Soul Scattering Ghost Flute, after all."

However, Weeping Soul's eyes were closed at this moment, and she didn't appear to have heard Han Li at all.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this, but he didn't interrupt her.

The auctioneer quickly made a final enquiry for further bids before declaring the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute sold.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul opened her eyes with an elated expression as she said, "Master, I've gathered a piece of important information from their conversation just now."

"What is it?" Han Li asked.

"Take a look for yourself, Master," Weeping Soul said as she cast an incantation seal into Han Li's glabella, and a ball of black light appeared in his mind, then gently unfurled to reveal an image of the interior of the other booth.

"Your wealth is truly astounding, Senior Jin," one of the black-robed figures said in a sycophantic manner.

"This amount of Immortal Origin Stones is still well within my means," the tall and thin figure replied in a pleased voice.

"Alright, we've already spent far too much time here. If we let that Gold Devouring Immortal get away again, all of us will have to bear the consequences," a petite figure interjected, and it seemed to be a woman, but for some reason, her voice was rather muffled and unclear.

The other figures in the booth seemed to be quite fearful of her, and all of them hurriedly gave affirmative responses.

That was the conclusion of the scene, and Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly in a contemplative manner.

These were presumably Nine Origins Temple cultivators trying to capture a Gold Devouring Immortal. Could it be that Jin Tong had managed to escape from the Nine Origins Temple?

Chapter 1202: Tailing in Secret

"Master, do you think that the Gold Devouring Immortal they're referring to is Jin Tong?" Weeping Soul asked.

"What was that? Did I hear Boss's name?" Xiaobai immediately yelled from within the Flower Branch domain upon hearing this.

"It's definitely possible. Jin Tong is a very smart girl, so there's a chance that she was able to escape from the Nine Origins Temple," Han Li mused.

However, if Jin Tong were nearby, then why was he unable to sense her at all through their spiritual connection?

It then occurred to him that now that Jin Tong had reached the Great Encompassment Stage, perhaps her soul power had been elevated to the point that it had refined the spiritual mark that he had planted in her body.

"Master, those people are leaving," Weeping Soul suddenly said, and sure enough, Han Li turned to discover the six figures filing out of their booth.

"Let's follow them," Han Li said as he rose to his feet.

The auction hadn't even reached the halfway mark yet, so there were definitely still many more treasures to come, but a higher priority had arisen.

Only after the six of them were far away did Han Li and Weeping Soul leave their booth to trail along after them.

After emerging from the Sun Moon Pavilion, the six figures flew away into the distance, while Han Li and Weeping Soul continued to follow from afar.

Upon Xiaobai's insistence, Han Li relented and released him from the Flower Branch domain, and before long, the six figures arrived on the border of Gilded City, where they drew to a temporary halt.

This place was very far away from the heart of the city, and most of the residents in this area were mortals and low-grade cultivators.

One of the cloaked figures stepped forward, then flipped their hand over to produce a blue crystal ball, within which was a swirling vortex of blue light.

Right at this moment, a faint glimmer of golden light flashed through the vortex, and the figure declared, "He's right here!"

It was Lan Yan's voice.

"We've finally managed to track him down!" the petite figure said in an exultant manner, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a flurry of silver array flags that vanished into the nearby space.

The space up ahead shuddered slightly, and a transparent, hemispherical light barrier appeared, encompassing a large area within it.

There were countless silver patterns on the light barrier, forming what appeared to have been an extremely profound restriction.

The light barrier only appeared for an instant before fading away, so it didn't attract any attention.

"There's no way that Gold Devouring Immortal will be able to get away now!" another cloaked figure chuckled.

"Cut the chit-chat!" the petite figure harrumphed coldly as she flew forward and abruptly vanished into thin air, leaving only a patch of rippling space behind her.

Her five companions quickly followed suit, and only after all six of them had disappeared did Han Li's trio appear nearby.

The three of them were enshrouded in a layer of azure light that resembled an azure cloak, which completely concealed their auras.

Han Li pointed a finger forward, releasing a beam of golden light that vanished into the space up ahead, and rays of silver light instantly appeared before him, forming a series of runes to keep the beam of golden light at bay.

The two were in opposition for a moment before both faded away.

"This is a very powerful spatial restriction. It won't be difficult to break it, but I don't think I'll be able to do so without being detected," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows.

"If it's a spatial restriction, then leave it to me. Get in my stomach for now," Xiaobai said with a smile as he took on his Pixiu form, then devoured Han Li and Weeping Soul whole before chanting an incantation to conjure up a layer of rippling white light over his own body.

Cloaked within the layer of white light, Xiaobai's body slowly fused into the surrounding space, transforming into a white shadow that drifted forward through the air.

A series of white runes instantly appeared in the space up ahead to halt him in his tracks, but he was able to pass through them without any trouble, and once the white shadow had crossed over to the other side, it quickly reformed into Xiaobai's body.

From there, he opened his mouth to release Han Li and Weeping Soul, the former of which turned to him with a surprised expression as he exclaimed, "I didn't know you possessed the ability to bypass spatial restrictions."

"Us Ink-Eyed Pixiu's have innate spaces in our bodies, so our bloodline is imbued with some spatial power," Xiaobai explained in a smug manner as he reverted back to his human form.

Han Li nodded in response, then cast his gaze forward, only to discover that the six cloaked figures were nowhere to be seen.

"Master, they've concealed themselves and are currently over there. We've been able to remain hidden from them thanks to Xiaobai's Heaven Moving Talisman, but we could still be discovered if we get too close," Weeping Soul said as she pointed a finger in a certain direction.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and he immediately spotted the six figures as well, all of whom were converging around a small courtyard on a secluded street up ahead.

"Let's go," Han Li said, and the three of them immediately set off again.

Han Li had concealed their auras, while Weeping Soul was using a secret technique to suppress their soul auras, and only then did they approach the courtyard.

However, before they had a chance to close in, a resounding boom rang out within the courtyard.

A burst of radiant, golden light erupted in all directions, forming a vortex of golden light that proliferated outward in all directions to raze the entire courtyard to the ground.

Han Li's trio immediately stopped in their tracks before ducking behind a large tree for cover.

From there, Han Li watched as the six cloaked figures flew out into the surrounding area to form an encirclement around what was once the courtyard.

As the golden light continued to spread outward, Han Li suddenly detected a familiar aura within it, and he murmured to himself, "It's him, not Jin Tong..."

"Who is it, Master?" Xiaobai asked in a puzzled manner, and as soon as his voice trailed off, the smoke settled to reveal a golden-robed young man.

It was none other than the Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, Qu Lin.

"You sure are persistent, I'll give you that," Qu Lin sighed in an exasperated manner.

"There's no need for violence, Fellow Daoist. We really are only here to invite you to attend the Bodhi Banquet. Just return with us to the Heavenly Court, and you'll see that we're telling the truth."

Han Li turned to discover that it was a black-robed woman who had spoken, and Weeping Soul's brows furrowed slightly in befuddlement upon hearing this.

"They're from the Heavenly Court? Weren't they supposed to be cultivators of the Nine Origins Temple?"

Han Li was also very perplexed.

"You think I'll fall for that again? Placing my trust in the Heavenly Court is how I ended up in the Eon Pagoda!" Qu Lin scoffed.

"There must've been some misunderstanding in the past," the black-robed woman said in an emotionless manner.

"Don't treat me like an idiot! I want nothing to do with any of you, so you can all go now," Qu Lin harrumphed coldly.

"Fine! We tried to be civilized, but you clearly insist on forcing our hand," the black-robed woman replied in a cold voice, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a cloud of crimson mist above Qu Lin.

At the same time, countless tiny specks of red light began to appear over the ground, and a colony of red fire ants burrowed their way out of the earth, reducing everything in their wake to molten lava.

"It's her!" Han Li exclaimed in a surprised manner upon seeing this.

"Who is she, Master? An old romantic partner of yours?" Xiaobai asked.

"Quit spouting nonsense!" Han Li snapped as he gave Xiaobai a firm flick to the forehead. "Her name is Chi Meng, and she's a Great Encompassment cultivator with mastery over the laws of fire. Do not take her lightly!"

Xiaobai massaged his own head as he continued to observe the unfolding confrontation.

The fire ants had surrounded the entire area, but they stopped around a hundred feet short of Qu Lin, and it was unclear whether they had stopped under Chi Meng's instructions, or if they had stopped out of their innate fear of Gold Devouring Beetles.

"Hurry up and get him! We've already wasted more than enough time!" a tall man with an elderly voice snapped, and it was clear that he had a rather short temper.

With that, all of the cloaked figures aside from Lan Yan sprang into action.

The tall man was the first to strike, sweeping a sleeve through the air to release seven or eight almighty ghostly monarchs that pounced at Qu Lin in unison.

"So he's the cultivator of soul-related law powers that I detected earlier. His powers are similar to mine, but he's not blessed with the innate attributes that I possess as a Xing Beast, so he's gone down an inferior path to mine," Weeping Soul said in a smug manner.

Qu Lin wasn't fazed in the slightest as he took a step forward, and his foot landed with the sound of a falling mountain.

A burst of golden light erupted in all directions from beneath his feet, scattering all of the fire ants that were converging toward him.

At the same time, he threw a punch forward, and a burst of fiery, golden light erupted out of his fist to engulf all of the ghostly monarchs, tearing them to shreds amid a chorus of ghastly howls.

Immediately thereafter, a vast expanse of scorching fire came crashing down from the crimson cloud above, instantly inundating his entire body, and at the same time, a giant, golden sword that was over a thousand feet in length came plunging down from the heavens, splitting the crimson flames before striking Qu Lin.

Chapter 1203: Battle Between Great Encompassment Cultivators

The sword struck Qu Lin on the shoulder, drawing blood and forcing him down to one knee.

He gave a muffled groan, but he was able to stand up under the weight of the giant sword, and the wound on his shoulder was already beginning to heal.

The wielder of the sword was a short, black-robed man, and he gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, then forced his sword with even greater force.

Qu Lin shuddered under the weight of his sword, but managed to remain on his feet on this occasion.

"Is that all you've got?" he sneered.

"I've always heard that Gold Devouring Immortals possess indestructible bodies, but it seems like you're nothing special," Chi Meng jeered as she swept a sleeve through the air, and a large swathe of fire ants quickly crawled onto Qu Lin's body, leaving behind charred black trails on his skin.

A burst of strange, golden ripples erupted out of Qu Lin's body to shake off all of the fire ants, and the giant sword on his shoulder also shuddered violently before being sent flying back.

Immediately thereafter, he stomped a foot down onto the ground, launching himself up into the air like a speeding arrow with the intention of fleeing the encirclement.

However, as he did so, the sky above suddenly darkened, and a massive ghost formed by black mist emerged from the clouds overhead to swallow him whole.

As soon as he entered the ghost's mouth, Qu Lin was immediately struck by a rush of dizziness, and before he had a chance to react, a series of semi-transparent, gray chains converged from all directions before passing directly through his body.

The gray mist swirling around the chains surged into his body, striking him with a bone-chilling sensation, and it was as if all of his immortal spiritual power had been frozen solid.

The attacks from the other black-robed figures fell upon him immediately thereafter, and even though he was caught off guard by this turn of events, he was able to withstand the barrage of attacks just fine.

"His body really is as powerful as the rumors suggest, but once I've destroyed his spiritual sense, he'll be reduced to a mindless husk that's completely at our mercy!" the tall black-robed man said, then pulled out a black flute that he brought to his lips.

A sense of foreboding immediately welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

In the next instant, the tall man blew into the flute, and all of the runes on it lit up as a burst of peculiar soundwaves proliferated through the air in all directions.

Qu Lin's calm expression instantly became distorted with pain as soon as the soundwaves reached him.

He felt as if an invisible saw had suddenly appeared in his consciousness, and it was rapidly swinging back and forth, attempting to slice his soul and consciousness into two.

Qu Lin regarded his own soul to be above average in power even among Great Encompassment cultivators, yet it was made to appear extremely fragile in the face of the flute's power.

The sound produced by the flute was gradually becoming higher and higher in pitch at the tall man's behest, and the saw transformed into countless sharp spikes that began drilling into Qu Lin's soul, causing him to let loose an involuntary howl of agony.

Even though Han Li was already mentally prepared, the three of them were also affected by the sound of the flute.

As a cultivator of similar law powers to the tall man, Weeping Soul was the least susceptible of the three, while Han Li was also able to ward off the flute's debilitating effects decently well thanks to his tremendous spiritual sense.

However, Xiaobai had only inherited the power of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu for a short time, and even though he was forcing himself not to make any sounds, the trembling of his body clearly indicated his discomfort.

A concerned look appeared on Weeping Soul's face upon seeing this, and a vertical eye surfaced on her glabella, following which two beams of red light emerged from within before shooting into Han Li and Xiaobai's glabellas to lessen their discomfort.

Right at this moment, Chi Meng's voice suddenly rang out.

"If I had known that you would serve yourself up to me on a silver platter, then I wouldn't have gone to so much trouble to look for you, Han Li."

In the blink of an eye, she was already hovering above their heads.

Seeing as their cover had already been blown, Han Li emerged from hiding with Xiaobai and Weeping Soul, and the three of them rose up into the air.

Weeping Soul had already released a dark red spirit domain to encompass all three of them, and a composed smile appeared on Han Li's face as he mused, "Sorry to have kept you waiting, Celestial Maiden Chi Meng."

"Fellow Daoist Han!" Lan Yan exclaimed upon catching sight of Han Li from afar.

Chi Meng took a moment to examine Han Li, and a hint of surprise appeared in her eyes upon detecting his aura.

Not much time had passed since their previous encounter, yet he had already managed to reach the Great Encompassment Stage during this time.

However, she then quickly regained her composure as she scoffed, "So what if you've reached the Great Encompassment Stage? You're still nothing more than a newborn chick that hasn't even severed a single corpse soul. I'm not letting you get away again!"

After reaching the early-Great Encompassment Stage, one could make further breakthroughs with each corpse soul that was severed, and upon severing all three corpse souls, one would become a Dao Ancestor.

Each corpse soul severance was an extremely perilous process, but a successful severance would grant one a significant boost in power unlike any previous breakthrough made below the Great Encompassment Stage.

With so many powerful allies on her side, Chi Meng was naturally fully confident in her ability to take down Han Li. The only thing that she had to be wary of was that strange secret technique that he had used to escape from her last time.

With that in mind, she swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a massive, spherical light barrier, which rapidly expanded to encompass the entire surrounding area in a radius of several hundred kilometers.

The surrounding air instantly became scorching hot, and eight fiery waterfalls came crashing down from the heavens, reducing the ground in Chi Meng's spirit domain to a lake of molten lava.

All of the bodies of water within the spirit domain quickly evaporated away, while the earth became so parched that countless massive trenches and cracks had appeared all over its surface.

Xiaobai immediately felt his own mouth run dry, and it was as if all of the surrounding world's origin qi had been incinerated by the scorching heat in the spirit domain.

"She seems like quite a pain to deal with," Xiaobai remarked.

"Looks like she wasn't using her full power at all during our last encounter," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Elder Xi Tang, I'll leave that Gold Devouring Immortal to you and Elder Jian Qiu. Everyone else, help me capture this man," Chi Meng ordered

The tall man with the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute and the wielder of the golden sword both gave an affirmative response, while the other two black-robed figures flew over to Chi Meng's side.

"Weeping Soul, go and help Qu Lin," Han Li instructed, and Weeping Soul nodded in response before turning to depart.

"You think you can just come and go as you please in my spirit domain?" Chi Meng snapped in a furious manner, and a fiery giant that was over a thousand feet tall slowly emerged from the lake of bubbling lava down below, wielding a massive, fiery sword as it stood in Weeping Soul's path.

Weeping Soul gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and she summoned her newly acquired Infernal Ghost Claw before sweeping it through the air, unleashing several black claw projections that tore the fiery giant to pieces.

A pleased look appeared on her face as she looked down at the Infernal Ghost Claw, while the dismembered fiery giant disintegrated back into molten lava that flowed into the lake.

"There's more where that came from!" Chi Meng scoffed as one fiery giant after another rose up from the lava lake at her behest, storming at Han Li's trio while swinging their massive swords through the air.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up his golden spirit domain, which overlapped with Chi Meng's fiery spirit domain, and the fiery giants were instantly slowed down to a crawl, allowing Weeping Soul to dismember them with ease before continuing onward to fly to Qu Lin's aid.

However, right at this moment, a molten wyrm suddenly flew out of one of the lava waterfalls, and it opened its cavernous mouth before biting down at Weeping Soul's head, only to also be dismembered by her Infernal Ghost Claw without being able to pose any resistance.

However, instead of disintegrating like the fiery giants, the dismembered pieces of the lava wyrm's body instantly fused back together amid a flash of crimson light, and it continued to bite down upon Weeping Soul.

Right at this moment, Han Li's voice rang out beside her ears.

"Don't worry about that thing, just keep going."

Weeping Soul did as she was told, paying no further heed to her fiery assailant as she charged directly onward.

Right as she was about to be devoured by the molten wyrm, the sound of flowing water suddenly rang out as a golden river rose up from the ground before flowing straight into the wyrm's mouth.

The wyrm was instantly stopped cold in its tracks as plumes of white mist rose up from its body, and Weeping Soul was able to ride the wave straight through its body to arrive by Qu Lin's side.

A look of mixed emotions flashed through Qu Lin's eyes at the sight of Han Li.

Meanwhile, Elder Xi Tang began playing his flute again, but on this occasion, all of the soundwaves that it released were condensed into a compact stream that solely targeted Weeping Soul instead of spreading in all directions.

A faint smile appeared on Weeping Soul's face, and not only was she not fearful in the slightest, she was wondering to herself how much her powers would be enhanced from devouring the tall man.

For some reason, a chill ran down Elder Xi Tang's spine at the sight of Weeping Soul's excited grin.

Chapter 1204: Sequence of Surprises

A hint of surprise flashed through Chi Meng's eyes at the sight of the golden river down below.

"So you've already managed to manifest a Creation Tier spirit domain. But so what? It's only a single river, and it doesn't even contain pure water-attribute law powers. What could you possibly be hoping to do with this?" Chi Meng chuckled, but her mocking laughter quickly died down.

All of a sudden, bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations spread through the air as an undulating mountain range, an azure forest, a radiant, golden moon, and countless specks of fiery starlight appeared within Han Li's spirit domain in rapid succession.

"This is impossible! How could you have manifested such a complete Creation Tier spirit domain at just the early-Great Encompassment Stage?" Chi Meng exclaimed in disbelief.

Spirit domain manifestation was never an easy process, and not only did it require a huge investment of time and effort, it also required access to an immense amount of resources and more than a modicum of luck.

Generally speaking, most cultivators with Creation Tier spirit domains would only be able to manifest a single piece of scenery or a single domain spirit, as was the case with Chi Meng's lava waterfalls and fiery giants, and it was extremely rare to see such a comprehensive Creation Tier spirit domain.

In light of this, Chi Meng was forced to reassess Han Li's power.

With that in mind, she turned to Lan Yan as she ordered, "Lan Yan, you come and help as well."

Lan Yan swayed slightly upon hearing this, seemingly a little hesitant.

"Don't forget about what you asked of me!" Chi Meng snapped in a cold voice.

A resigned look flashed through Lan Yan's eyes upon hearing this, and she reluctantly flew over to Chi Meng's side.

Right at this moment, Xiaobai suddenly found himself momentarily blinded by an unexpected flash of white light.

Immediately thereafter, Chi Meng flew over to his side at an astonishing speed, seemingly completely unaffected by Han Li's spirit domain, then conjured up a semi-transparent light barrier that encompassed both Han Li and Xiaobai.

An ecstatic look appeared on her face upon seeing this, and the nine translucent, crimson dragons on the semi-transparent light barrier instantly sprang to life at her behest, blasting flames out of their mouths toward Han Li's duo.

An agonized howl rang out, and Chi Meng's expression changed drastically as she hurriedly restrained the power of the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome, only to discover that the two black-robed figures accompanying her were currently trapped within the dome.

Their robes had been incinerated, and both of them had suffered severe burns.

"What happened?" Chi Meng exclaimed in a bewildered manner.

"You really thought I'd fall prey to that dome of yours again?"

Han Li's mocking voice rang out from nearby, following which he arrived before Chi Meng in the blink of an eye, then lashed out with an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

All she had time to do was raise an arm to protect herself before she was sent flying by Han Li's sword.

A jolt of numbness shot through her entire body, while a burst of sharp pain flared up along her arm, and she tumbled through the air for tens of thousands of feet before finally managing to steady herself.

However, before she had a chance to catch her breath, a shower of fiery, millstone-sized meteors came crashing down upon her.

She immediately attempted to take evasive measures, only to discover that a series of azure vines had wound themselves around her ankles, locking her firmly into place.

Her immediate reaction was naturally to free herself from the restraints, but her movements had suddenly become extremely sluggish, leaving her with insufficient time to make any hand seals.

In this dire situation, she let loose a loud cry as her aura erupted outward, forming a ring of scorching flames around her.

This was her nascent flame, and as soon as it was released, it immediately resonated with her fiery spirit domain, causing the lava waterfalls to converge toward her to clash against the meteor shower raining down from the sky.

The azure vines around her ankles were also forced back by her nascent flame, and she immediately rose up into the air to distance herself from the azure forest.

Only now did she finally come to realize that Han Li's time spirit domain had partially reached the Oneness Tier, and her heart immediately sank at this realization.

"What are you two just standing there for? Hurry up and release your spirit domains to counteract his spirit domain!" she snapped at the two black-robed figures as she withdrew her Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome.

The two of them were aware of the peril that they were in, and they exchanged a glance with each other before releasing their spirit domains in unison.

A layer of black light emerged over both of their bodies, then fused together to form a black light barrier that expanded outward to overlap with the spirit domains of Han Li and Chi Meng.

The entire landscape enshrouded within the black light barrier shuddered violently before sinking around ten feet into the ground, and Han Li and Xiaobai also sank down into the ground by the same margin.

Elsewhere, Weeping Soul was locked in battle against Elder Xi Tang, the latter of which had taken on a ghastly form with a layer of white bone over his face, and as he continued to play the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute, wisps of black mist began to rise up from the cracked earth, forming a massive city.

The city was riddled with thorns and spikes, and there were human heads hanging everywhere. The word "Fengdu" was inscribed upon it in antiquated text, and an extremely formidable baleful aura was constantly emanating from it. [1]

Elder Xi Tang was standing atop the city, and the sounds produced by his flute were becoming more and more unbearable to listen to by the second.

The gates of Fengdu slowly swung open, and dense, black mist surged out from within alongside countless fearsome ghostly creatures, all of which swarmed toward Weeping Soul in unison.

All of a sudden, a blanket of dark clouds appeared over the entire sky, while a layer of white frost spread over the ground.

Not only was Weeping Soul not fazed in the slightest, she couldn't help but lick her lips in excitement as she charged straight into the almighty ghostly army while swinging her Infernal Ghost Claw through the air, tearing swathes of ghostly creatures to shreds with every single swing.

As she became more familiar with the Infernal Ghost Claw, she was able to unleash more and more of its power, and none of the ghostly creatures in her path stood any chance.

Before the ghostly energy of the eradicated creatures had a chance to dissipate, they were sucked into Weeping Soul's body through her nostrils to further enhance her powers.

Meanwhile, Qu Lin was locked in battle against Elder Jian Qiu.

The latter swung his sword at the former's neck, and Qu Lin immediately lowered himself slightly before opening his mouth to bite down onto the golden longsword, which was undoubtedly a graded immortal treasure.

A loud crack rang out as the longsword was shattered, and a large chunk had been bitten out of it.

"How dare you!" Elder Jian Qiu roared in a furious manner, distraught over damage to his sword.

Qu Lin backed away with a cold expression while chewing on the chunk of sword in his mouth.

He took a glance in Han Li's direction with a look of mixed emotions. Never had he imagined that they would meet again under circumstances like these.

The joint spirit domain unleashed by the pair of black-robed figures had significantly increased the gravitational force in the area, counteracting much of the power of Han Li's spirit domain while also slowing his speed of movement.

Having had some time to catch her breath, Chi Meng sprang into action once again, combining the eight lava waterfalls in her spirit domain to form a massive vortex that began closing in Han Li.

Not only was the vortex giving off immense heat, it was also releasing tremendous suction force that threatened to draw Han Li in against his will.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the mountain range in his spirit domain rose up into the air at his behest before flying to his side.

As it flew through the air, it left layers of rippling time law power fluctuations in its wake to keep the fiery vortex at bay.

The two black-robed figures were standing directly beneath the mountain range, and they experienced a moment of sluggishness in their spiritual sense as the time law power fluctuations washed over them. By the time they returned to their senses, the mountain range had already fallen upon them.

The mountains had no substantial form, so they weren't all that heavy, but the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree growing upon them did have a substantial form, and their root systems extended out of the mountains to bind the pair of black-robed figures.

The roots pierced through their skin and into their bodies, causing them to cry out in pain before falling silent, and their combined spirit domain quickly faded away, leaving Chi Meng to look on with a grim and agitated expression.

She could see that Jian Qiu and Xi Tang were also struggling in their respective battles, and a furious look appeared on her face as she yelled, "I'll give you credit for backing me into a corner like this, but this is as far as you go!"

Immediately thereafter, she raised both hands to the sky, and in that instant, all of the surrounding world's origin was incinerated into nothingness, creating something akin to a vacuum around her.

Her flowing, red locks rose up into the air, while golden flames erupted out of her eyes, giving her the appearance of an ancient deity of fire with terrifying energy fluctuations surging out of her body.

With a casual wave of her hand, she released a golden flame that resembled a flower petal, sending it flying directly toward Han Li.

In response, Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts before throwing a punch in retaliation, unleashing a massive fist projection to clash against the fiery flower petal.

A resounding boom rang out as the golden flower petal passed through the fist projection without any trouble before continuing on toward Han Li.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he slashed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword through the air, unleashing an arc of golden lightning that struck the flower petal to scatter it into countless specks of golden fire.

Through the golden flames, Han Li could see that an enormous, fiery, golden flower had appeared behind Chi Meng, with its petals fanned out behind her like the canopy of a peacock.

[1]. Fengdu is the city of the dead in Taoism, Buddhism, and Confucianism.

[Back]

Chapter 1205: Retreat

"You can be proud of yourself for forcing me this far. Now, it's time for you to die!" Chi Meng declared in a cold voice.

Her eyes had transformed into two radiant orbs of red light that seemed to have boundless seas of fire burning within it, and in the next instant, countless golden flower petals detached themselves from the giant flower behind her to fill the entire sky.

The temperature around her spiked drastically, to the point that even the air itself was being incinerated, while the surrounding earth was rapidly melting away into more molten lava.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he condensed his own spirit domain to encompass an area of only several hundred feet around him, following which the moon above his head began to revolve at his behest, while a storm of golden sand rose up from the mountain range below.

Immediately thereafter, the forest on the mountains began to rustle incessantly, while the river of time and the specks of fiery starlight in the sky rose up and descended, respectively, converging toward one another.

The golden flower petals that were hurtling toward Han Li were able to burn through space, thereby granting them incredible speed, but as soon as they flew into his time spirit domain, they immediately slowed down to a crawl, following which they began to disintegrate bit by bit.

The short distance of only several hundred feet somehow proved to be an insurmountable obstacle for these golden flower petals, and with each agonizing inch that they managed to advance, a bit more of their power would be stripped away.

By the time the flower petals finally reached Han Li, all that remained of them were tiny specks of light that resembled feeble fireflies.

"Impossible!" Chi Meng exclaimed in incredulity.

From her perspective, it looked as if Han Li's spirit domain had slowly whittled away the power of her flames, but in reality, what had happened was that the flames had simply been reverted back in time to their initial form by the power of his Five Elemental Illusory World.

All external objects that entered the Five Elemental Illusory World would be rejected by the immense time law powers within, forced to revert back to their initial state.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he stepped forward to arrive before Chi Meng in the blink of an eye.

She was aware that as one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time were naturally superior to all other law powers, but never had she imagined that the gulf would be so severe. In the wake of this astonishing turn of events, she had already lost all will to fight and immediately turned to flee.

"Where do you think you're going?" Han Li sneered as he expanded his spirit domain once again to encompass Chi Meng, and the moon above his head swooped down from above to pursue her.

The moon was formed by the Mantra Treasured Axis, and the closer one's proximity to it was, the more severely they would be impacted by its time-slowing abilities. As the moon descended upon her, Chi Meng could feel herself getting slower and slower, and her agitation was growing by the second.

Left with no alternatives, she raised a finger to her own glabella, and a fiery mark appeared on the glabellas of the two black-robed figures trapped under the mountain range in Han Li's spirit domain.

A burst of violent power erupted out of the pair of fiery marks, and the two black-robed figures exploded into a pair of fireballs that expanded in all directions at an alarming rate.

Intense waves of heat swept through the air, instantly reducing the mountain to countless particles of golden sand, while much of the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree forest was also destroyed.

The damage sustained by the spirit domain was instantly reflected in Han Li, and he swayed unsteadily on his feet as blood trickled down from the corner of his lips.

Taking advantage of this brief delay, Chi Meng sped away into the distance as a streak of red light.

Meanwhile, the battle between Qu Lin and Jian Qiu had already concluded, with the former adopting his true Gold Devouring Beetle form to devour the latter.

Elder Xi Tang had also been defeated, with Weeping Soul's Infernal Ghost Claw pressed against his dantian and glabella.

Elder Xi Tang was an extremely formidable cultivator in his own right, and given the special nature of his law powers, the average Great Encompassment cultivator would've definitely been no match for him, but unfortunately, Weeping Soul was a perfect counter to his powers.

Right at his moment, Lan Yan suddenly began yelling from afar in a pleading voice, "Don't kill him! Please don't kill him!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he said, "Don't kill him for now, Weeping Soul. We can find out more information about the Heavenly Court from him."

Weeping Soul nodded in response, and the vertical eye reappeared on her glabella before releasing a beam of red light with the intention of immobilizing him, but to everyone's surprise, he had a very fiery and unyielding personality, and a ghostly creature abruptly sprang out of his right eyeball to bite down onto his head as he yelled, "You're not getting anything out of me!"

At the same time, a burst of black light appeared within his glabella, broadcasting his intention to self-detonate.

"Look out!" Han Li yelled, and Weeping Soul immediately sprang back in retreat.

In the next instant, an earth-shattering boom rang out as a pillar of black light rose up into the sky, then transformed into an enormous, black tornado that swept through the air in all directions.

The self-detonation of a Great Encompassment cultivator's dantian was akin to a cataclysmic natural disaster, and Han Li was traversing rapidly through the storm while connecting Xiaobai, Weeping Soul, Lan Yan, and Qu Lin to himself using ropes formed by immortal spiritual power in the process.

All of a sudden, countless arcs of silver lightning descended from the heavens to form a lightning array that encompassed all of them before vanishing in a flash.

......

There was a spacious area above an underground river in a certain valley outside Gilded City.

This was the destination of Han Li's lightning teleportation array, and as soon as they arrived, Qu Lin immediately cupped his fist to him in a grateful salute as he declared, "Thank you for saving my life, Fellow Daoist Han. I'll be sure to repay you if the opportunity arises."

"It's fine, I just so happened to have been passing through. Why were those Heavenly Court cultivators pursuing you?" Han Li asked.

"I'd like to find out myself. They simply began targeting me for no stated reason. In any case, this isn't the first time I've been hunted by the Heavenly Court, so this is nothing new for me," Qu Lin replied.

Han Li then turned to Lan Yan, who was looking very crestfallen, and asked, "Aren't you a disciple of the Nine Origins Temple, Lan Yan? What were you doing with those Heavenly Court cultivators?"

"I wanted to save my brother," Lan Yan replied with a sullen expression.

"Lan Yuanzi? What does this have to do with him?" Han Li asked.

"Right now, all that remains of my brother is a fragment of his soul. After returning to the temple, I tried everything I could to save him, but none of it worked. I found out that Elder Xi Tang was capable of resurrecting my brother, so I turned to him for help. They learned that I had met Qu Lin in the Eon Pagoda and was familiar with his aura, so they used me to track him, and that's why I was with them," Lan Yan explained.

A hint of killing intent flashed through Qu Lin's eyes upon hearing this.

"Do you know why those people were hunting Fellow Daoist Qu Lin?" Han Li asked.

"I do not. They were just using me as a tool, so of course they weren't going to tell me anything," Lan Yan sighed.

"Fellow Daoist Han, do you still recall Huai Yangzi and those other people that we encountered in the Eon Pagoda?" Qu Lin suddenly asked.

Han Li immediately realized what he was implying, and a peculiar look appeared on his face as he asked, "Are you suggesting that they want to capture you to extract your law threads?"

"Why speculate when we can just find out?" Weeping Soul suddenly interjected.

Everyone turned to her with perplexed expressions, and instead of offering an explanation, Weeping Soul reopened the vertical eye on her glabella, following which a beam of dark red light shot out from within.

Within the beam of light was a soul fragment that was struggling violently against a dark red chain, and it was identical in appearance to Elder Xi Tang.

"How did you manage to secure this soul fragment? He already detonated his own nascent soul and summoned that creature to devour his soul!" Qu Lin exclaimed.

"I have my ways," Weeping Soul replied in a smug manner.

Qu Lin didn't pry any further, but it was clear that he was still very curious.

"She's a Xing Beast that possesses innate yin soul law powers, so this is no difficult task for her," Han Li explained with a smile, and the look of despair on Lan Yan's face instantly turned to one of renewed hope upon hearing this.

Han Li noticed the change in her expression, but he didn't address it as he turned to Weeping Soul and said, "Take a look and see what you can find."

Weeping Soul nodded in response, and a translucent, crimson thread shot out of her glabella before piercing straight into Xi Tang's soul fragment, causing it to instantly fall still.

Chapter 1206: Exception

Moments later, Weeping Soul's brows furrowed slightly as the translucent, crimson thread flew back into her vertical eye, following which Xi Tang's soul fragment disintegrated into nothingness.

"What did you see?" Xiaobai asked.

"He erased most of his own memories during his self-detonation, and the memories that are left are all very fragmented. However, the parts about Qu Lin are still quite clear, and it seems like Qu Lin isn't their only target," Weeping Soul replied.

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked.

"According to his memories, it seems like the Heavenly Court is currently searching for cultivators with special law powers to capture. As a Gold Devouring Immortal, Qu Lin possesses the very rare devouring law powers, and that's why they were onto him," Weeping Soul explained.

"Does he know why they're going after cultivators like this?" Han Li asked.

"I wasn't able to find the answer in his memories, so he was most likely just following orders as well," Weeping Soul replied.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Weeping Soul flipped a hand over to produce a black storage bracelet, which she refined momentarily before searching around inside to find the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute.

"Looks like you were meant to be mine," Weeping Soul murmured to herself as she examined the flute with a joyful expression.

All of a sudden, Lan Yan fell to her knees and said, "Fellow Daoist Han, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul, I have something to ask of you."

Weeping Soul was rather startled by this, but Han Li already knew what request Lan Yan was going to make.

"You want Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul to help you save Lan Yuanzi, right?" he asked.

"Please help me, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul... I'll do anything..." Lan Yan implored in a trembling voice as she kowtowed to the ground.

Weeping Soul's brows furrowed slightly as he turned to Han Li, who gave her a slight nod.

"I can help you, but I've never done anything like this before, so I can't guarantee success," Weeping Soul said.

Lan Yan raised her head to look at Weeping Soul with a hesitant expression, but a look of resolve then appeared in her eyes as she said, "As long as you're willing to help me, I'll be eternally grateful to you. As for whether you succeed or not, I'll leave that to fate."

"Alright, in that case, I can help you, but if my master needs anything from you in the future, you know what to do, right?" Weeping Soul replied.

"I'll do anything. Even if he wants my life, I'll give it up without any hesitation," Lan Yan promised in a solemn manner.

"Do you have any plans at the moment, Fellow Daoist Qu Lin?" Han Li asked.

"I came to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region because I had sensed the aura of another Gold Devouring Immortal here. Even though there's been a slight hiccup, I'm still going to stick to my original plan and travel to Nine Origins City," Qu Lin replied.

"In that case, we have the same destination in mind. How about we go there together?" Han Li proposed.

A contemplative look appeared on Qu Lin's face upon hearing this, and Han Li made no effort to try and hurry him.

Given how cautious Qu Lin, the more he tried to convince him, the more suspicious he would become.

"Why invite him to travel with us? He doesn't look like a very good person to me," Xiaobai asked through voice transmission.

"The other Gold Devouring Immortal that he's referring to has to be Jin Tong, so if he's with us, it'll be far easier for us to track Jin Tong down," Han Li replied.

"Oh, so it's for Boss's sake. In that case, it's fine," Xiaobai replied with a nod.

"It would certainly be safer for all of us to travel together, but wouldn't it be more likely for us to be exposed traveling in a group like this? Also, Chi Meng now has a way to track me, are you not worried that you'll get swept up in my mess?" Qu Lin asked.

"Your concerns are unnecessary, Fellow Daoist Qu. If you agree to accompany me, then all you need to do is hide in my domain treasure, and I assure you that Chi Meng won't be able to track you," Han Li replied with a smile.

"In that case, I'll be in your care, Fellow Daoist Han," Qu Lin said.

"There are many arrays in my domain, so I'll have to ask you to stay in the bamboo pavilion inside and not go anywhere outside of that," Han Li said.

"That's fine by me," Qu Lin replied with a nod.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, which led straight into the second floor of the newly constructed bamboo pavilion near the spirit medicine garden.

Qu Lin cupped his fist in a grateful salute, then stepped inside.

Upon entering the room, he looked around to discover that the area was abundant with spiritual qi, and there seemed to be restrictions set up around the pavilion.

These restrictions naturally weren't enough to contain him, but he wouldn't be able to break the restrictions without alerting Han Li, and given the power that Han Li had displayed, he wasn't confident in his chances in a battle.

With that in mind, he made his way over to the bed in the room and sat down with his legs crossed to meditate.

After closing the door of silver light, Han Li turned to Weeping Soul and asked, "Can you help Lan Yuanzi's soul in its current incomplete state?"

"I have a soul-nurturing secret technique that should work, but it's going to take a long time. Once his soul is fully restored, he can find another body to possess," Weeping Soul replied.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul," Lan Yan said as tears of joy welled up in her eyes.

"If you want to thank someone, then thank my master," Weeping Soul replied.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han," Lan Yan hurriedly said as she extended a grateful bow.

Han Li was just about to respond when he suddenly sensed something, and he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up the door of silver light once again, this one leading into the original bamboo pavilion in the Flower Branch domain.

"You can go in the domain with them, Weeping Soul. I'll leave Lan Yuanzi's soul to you," Han Li said.

Weeping Soul nodded in response before stepping through the door of light, followed by Lan Yan and Xiaobai.

Following their departure, Han Li closed the door of silver light, then put on his Reincarnation Palace mask, which projected a screen of crimson light in front of him.

An elegant figure appeared on the screen of light, and it was none other than Wyrm 3.

"You've finally gotten in touch with me, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"My apologies, I've been really busy lately... Oh? Could it be that you've already reached the Great Encompassment Stage?" Wyrm 3 asked in a surprised manner.

"How could you tell?" Han Li asked.

"I was taught a technique by a senior of mine that allows me to roughly gauge one's cultivation base according to certain signs," Wyrm 3 explained with a smile. "Where are you right now, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li was a little hesitant to respond, given the warning that Wyrm 3 had previously issued to him, but after a brief hesitation, he decided to tell the truth.

"I've already entered the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region because I have some things to do here."

Wyrm 3 could sense Han Li's apprehension, and she smiled as she reassured, "That's fine. The situation in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region has changed, so it's fine for you to be here."

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this. It sounded like she was also in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

"Has the mission finally begun?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. Where are you in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region right now? Would you be able to reach Nine Origins City in thirty years?" Wyrm 3 asked.

Han Li took a moment to calculate the distance between Gilded City and Nine Origins City, then nodded as he replied, "That shouldn't be a problem."

"Good. Also, now that you've reached the Great Encompassment Stage, you can have this," Wyrm 3 said as she made a hand seal, and a black mask appeared in the item teleportation array in front of Han Li.

The mask was identical in style to the mask that Han Li was currently wearing, and the alias was still the same as well.

"In our Reincarnation Palace, we have a hierarchy of masks that goes blue, azure, red, and black, in ascending order. Only those with black masks are considered to be true core members of our Reincarnation Palace," Wyrm 3 explained.

"Does that mean the Reincarnation Palace wants to instate me as a core member?" Han Li asked as he picked up the mask.

"That's right. Our palace master has heard much about you, and he's been meaning to summon you for an audience, but he's been too busy. However, he's always had the intention of instating you as a core member. Only those who possess exceptional aptitude and have made significant contributions to our Reincarnation Palace get the chance to be instated as core members, so this is an important matter.

“Given that you were able to reach the Great Encompassment Stage in such a short time, you're definitely not lacking in aptitude, but you are a little lacking in the contributions department. Our palace master was originally planning to promote you after the Nine Origins Temple mission, but given all of the powerful cultivators in the Nine Origins Temple, there's a chance that a crimson mask won't be able to conceal your aura properly, so he made an exception and instructed me to bring you this black mask early.

“With a black mask, your safety should be assured, and you'll officially be promoted after the mission," Wyrm 3 explained.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

The master of the Reincarnation Palace was an extremely renowned figure, and given that he was able to create a monolithic entity capable of opposing the Heavenly Court, there was a very good chance that he was a Dao Ancestor.

The thought of someone like that keeping tabs on him was a rather disconcerting thought for Han Li.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, and please pass on my gratitude to the palace master," Han Li said as he examined the black mask with his spiritual sense, upon which his expression instantly lit up slightly.

Even though the black mask was clearly in his grasp, it was completely undetectable to his spiritual sense.

Sure enough, the black mask's aura concealment properties were far better than those of the crimson mask, and it was truly worthy of the core members of the Reincarnation Palace.

Chapter 1207: Black Mask

"Don't mention it. You and I are both members of the Reincarnation Palace, and I was the one who recruited you, so it's only right that I provide you with some guidance as you move up the ranks. By the way, once you get to Nine Origins City, come to the Cloud Peak Inn in the outer city. That's a secret outlet of our Reincarnation Palace, so it's a safe place for you to stay," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

However, Han Li didn't appear to have heard her, and he was still examining the mask in his hands in silence.

Wyrm 3 faltered slightly upon seeing this, then asked, "Do you have any questions, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li was silent for a moment longer, then said, "Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, surely it's about time that you divulged more details pertaining to the mission to me."

Back when he was still at the High Zenith Palace, he didn't dare to ask too many questions about the mission for fear of being swept up into the conflict between the Heavenly Court and the Reincarnation Palace, but now that he had reached the Great Encompassment Stage, he was feeling bolder and ready to learn more.

"I don't know much about this mission myself, so I'm afraid that I have nothing to tell you even if I wanted to," Wyrm 3 sighed in an apologetic manner.

"We've known each other for quite some time already, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3. I don't know your exact status in the Reincarnation Palace, but I can tell that you're quite high up in the hierarchy. To be frank, I think you know more about the mission that you're letting on. Seeing as we're going to be working together, I suggest you be more candid with me," Han Li said in a meaningful voice.

"I truly have no information to share, Fellow Daoist Han. This is an extremely important mission that's being personally overseen by the most powerful members of our Reincarnation Palace, and I'm serving as nothing more than a messenger," Wyrm 3 replied with a wry smile.

Han Li could see that she seemed to be telling the truth, but just to make sure, he decided to enlist Weeping Soul's help.

"Is she telling the truth, Weeping Soul?" he asked through voice transmission.

"This is only a projection, so I'm unable to detect her soul fluctuations, but judging from her expression, it doesn't seem like she's lying," Weeping Soul replied, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Wyrm 3 could see that Han Li wasn't very pleased with this answer, and she said, "I may not know much about the mission, but I have gathered some information that I'm sure you'd like to hear."

"Oh? What is it?" Han Li asked.

"Jin Tong is currently still in the Nine Origins Temple, and she's safe for now. Her captors are planning to offer her up to the Time Dao Ancestor during the Bodhi Banquet, so they won't do anything to harm her. In fact, they'll most likely even help her advance in her cultivation so that she makes for a more appealing gift," Wyrm 3 said.

He had already learned the Nine Origins Temple's objective for capturing Jin Tong, but it was still a relief to have the matter confirmed by Wyrm 3.

"The higher-ups seem to want you to do something before they reveal to you Jin Tong's location and the way to save her, but I haven't been told exactly what it is that they want you to do," Wyrm 3 continued.

"Thank you for gathering this information for me, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

At the same time, he couldn't help but wonder exactly what it was that the Reincarnation Palace wanted him to do.

"Right now, you're a core member of our Reincarnation Palace. We do tend to be a rather mysterious organization, but we definitely won't try to plot against our own members, so you can rest assured, Fellow Daoist Han," Wyrm 3 said.

"Of course. Otherwise, I wouldn't have joined," Han Li replied with a nod.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before concluding their communication, following which Han Li called Xiaobai and Weeping Soul out of the Flower Branch domain.

After that, he replaced the crimson mask on his face with his black mask, and a burst of black light instantly emerged from the mask to envelop his entire body.

Weeping Soul and Xiaobai were stunned to discover that they were no longer able to detect Han Li's aura with their spiritual sense, as if he had vanished into thin air.

"The concealment effect of this black mask is even better than my Heaven Moving Talisman!" Xiaobai praised.

Han Li was also quite pleased with the abilities of the black mask, and he used it to adopt a disguise, transforming into a tall and imposing man with a thick beard.

"Let me borrow some of your power, Weeping Soul," Han Li said as he laid a hand onto Weeping Soul's shoulder, devouring some of her power through the palm of his hand.

After absorbing some of Weeping Soul's power, he closed his eyes momentarily, and a layer of black light that gave off a ghostly aura quickly appeared over his body.

It was identical to Weeping Soul's soul, and anyone would be fooled into thinking that he was a cultivator of ghostly arts.

An incredulous look appeared on Xiaobai's face upon seeing this, and Weeping Soul was also astonished.

Not only had Han Li's physical form changed, even the aura emanating from his soul had been altered by the black mask.

"This mask can absorb the energy of others to use as as disguise, making for a far more convincing disguise than just the alteration of one's physical appearance," Han Li explained.

"You'll be a lot safer now with this mask at your disposal, Master. Are we going to Nine Origins City from here? Xiaobai and I don't have concealment abilities of this caliber, so we'll just stay in the Flower Branch domain so we don't attract any trouble," Weeping Soul said.

"Keep an eye on Qu Lin and Lan Yan for me. Qu Lin's physical constitution is extremely formidable, but the souls of Gold Devouring Immortals are relatively weak, so your powers are perfect to keep him in check," Han Li instructed.

"You can count on me, Master," Weeping Soul replied, and Xiaobai was already eager to show that he was up to the task.

Han Li sent the two of them back into the Flower Branch domain, then quickly returned to Gilded City through one of its western entrances.

The city was as serene as ever, and many of the cultivators in the city were discussing the Sun Moon Pavilion auction.

It was clear that the Sun Moon Alliance had suppressed the disturbance caused by the battle just now, and that came as a relief to Han Li.

From there, he set off toward the eastern part of the city.

The central region of the city was riddled with shops, most of which were primarily golden in color, making for a very opulent sight to behold.

Gilded City was an enormous place, and Han Li flew for close to half a day before arriving in front of a golden palace in the eastern part of the city.

Hanging above the entrance of the city was a plaque that read "Sun Moon Boathouse", and there were many people entering and exiting the establishment.

Han Li stepped inside, arriving in a half that was several thousand feet in size, with everyone making their way deeper into the hall.

At the very rear of the hall were dozens of entrances, above each of which was a name of a place in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

Nine Origins City, Golden Origin City, and Hundred Creation City were among these names, and those three entrances were also the most popular ones.

Han Li began making his way toward the Nine Origins City passageway.

The Sun Moon Boathouse was a transportation business under the Sun Moon Alliance. The alliance had invented a special type of flying boat called the Sun Moon Flying Boat, which could draw upon the power of celestial bodies to fly at incredible speeds, making them perfect for transporting goods and customers between all of the important cities of the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

Not only were Sun Moon Flying Boats extraordinarily fast, they were far cheaper to access than teleportation arrays, making them very popular among the less financially privileged.

There were teleportation arrays leading to Nine Origins City from Gilded City, but all of them were under the control of the Heavenly Court. Given all of the unrest in the Immortal Realm, the Heavenly Court was being extra vigilant in its examination of teleportation arrays, so even with this black mask, Han Li didn't want to take the risk.

On top of that, a Sun Moon Flying Boat was more than fast enough to get him to Nine Origins City within thirty years.

Han Li stepped into the Nine Origins City entrance, and after passing through a long corridor, he arrived in a hall that was over three hundred feet in size.

There were many chairs in the hall, some of which were already occupied, and there were also two blue-robed Sun Moon Alliance cultivators present.

Han Li was approached by a blue-robed, middle-aged man upon entry, who cupped his fist in a salute as he asked, "Are you traveling to Nine Origins City, Fellow Daoist?"

"That's right," Han Li replied with a nod.

He had suppressed his own cultivation base to the Golden Immortal Stage in order to not attract attention.

"You came at the perfect time, Fellow Daoist. The boat to Nin Origins City departs once a month, and the next one is scheduled to depart tomorrow," the man said with a faint smile.

"That is indeed great timing. How much will it cost?" Han Li asked.

Before the Sun Moon Alliance cultivator had a chance to reply, Han Li was approached by a group of four cultivators, one of whom proposed, "Would you be interested in purchasing a ticket for a large room with us, Fellow Daoist? We can save a lot of Immortal Origin Stones by splitting the costs among the five of us."

All four of them were at the Golden Immortal Stage, and they were led by a gray-robed elderly man.

He was accompanied by a black-robed young man who appeared to have been twenty years of age at most, a red-robed young man with a voluptuous figure and beautiful facial features, and an elegant woman in a white nun robe.

Despite her attire, the woman in white had a head of long hair and a white longsword strapped to her back, both of which were rather unbefitting of a nun.

Han Li was immediately rooted to the spot at the sight of the four cultivators because he recognized all of them aside from the black-robed young man!

Chapter 1208: Traveling Together

The gray-robed elderly man and the red-robed woman were two of the people that he had encountered in the Five Light Lightning Region, namely Sun Chongshan and Celestial Maiden Miao.

Back then, Sun Chongshan had left behind the woman and another man to flee for his life, so there should've been bad blood between them, making it rather curious that they were together again.

As for the white-robed nun, she was quite similar in appearance to Yu Menghan, the human woman that he had encountered back in the Spirit Domain Realm, and his gaze lingered on her for a little longer due to this sense of familiarity.

However, he was unable to confirm her identity as it had been far too long since their previous encounter.

The white-robed nun seemed to have noticed Han Li's gaze, and her brows furrowed slightly as she turned away.

Han Li immediately snapped out of his reverie as he asked, "What's a large room?"

"The rooms on the boat are split up into large, small, and medium classifications. A ticket for a large room costs three thousand Immortal Origin Stones, then two thousand for a medium, and one thousand for a small room. It'll be a little crowded for the five of us to stay in a large room, but it'll save us quite a bit of Immortal Origin Stones each. What do you say?" Sun Chongshan explained.

Han Li took a glance at the Sun Moon Alliance cultivator to see that he was displaying no intention of stopping the arrangement that Sun Chongshan was trying to make.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li shook his head as he replied, "Thank you for the kind offer, but I prefer to stay alone."

A look of disappointment flashed through Sun Chongshan's eyes upon hearing this, but he didn't try to convince Han Li any further as he departed with the other three cultivators.

Han Li took a glance at the four cultivators, then purchased a ticket for a small room from the Sun Moon Alliance cultivator.

With only one day left, he wasn't in the mood to go out exploring the city, so he sat down in the hall to meditate.

He had expended a great deal of energy during the battle against Chi Meng and the others, so this was a good opportunity for him to rest and recuperate.

While meditating, Han Li was simultaneously keeping tabs on the four cultivators, particularly the white-robed nun, who resembled Yu Menghan in both appearance and aura.

Could it really be her?

Back when Han Li left the Spirit Domain Realm, she hadn't even reached the Nascent Soul Tier yet, and her aptitude didn't appear to have been anything special, either, so how was it possible that she had reached the Golden Immortal Stage in such a short time?

Of course, Liu Le'er had made far more progress in the same span of time, having already progressed to the Great Encompassment Stage, but she possessed a true spirit bloodline and had the support of the entire Heavenly Fox Tribe, so that really wasn't a fair comparison.

The white-robed nun appeared to have only been a vagrant cultivator, having to save on a ticket that only cost one thousand Immortal Origin Stones, so there was no way that she was particularly wealthy. With all of that in mind, Han Li concluded that it had to have just been someone similar in appearance.

Sun Chongshan continued to chat with other cultivators, hoping to convince someone to purchase a joint ticket with them.

However, most of the people entering the hall had already purchased tickets, and only after approaching close to ten people did he finally find someone willing to share a room with them, namely a Golden Immortal Stage middle-aged man.

Judging from his ragged clothes and coarse skin, he was clearly a vagrant cultivator.

With five people gathered, the group found a place to sit and await the departure of the Sun Moon Flying Boat.

Close to a day flew by in the blink of an eye, and the time of departure finally arrived.

"Please come us, fellow daoists," the two Sun Moon Alliance cultivators instructed as they made their way deeper into the hall, and everyone followed along.

At the back of the hall was a door, beyond which was a corridor that led to a massive plaza.

There was a giant flying boat that was three thousand to four thousand feet tall and seven thousand to eight thousand feet in length resting on the plaza. The boat was ovular in shape, resembling an enormous egg, and it was bright blue in color with countless blue and white runes engraved upon it to form a series of arrays.

Han Li could see that all of the arrays on the boat were star arrays that weren't inferior to the ones that he had seen in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

At the bottom of the flying boat was an entrance for passengers, and the boat itself had ten levels, that were segmented into rooms of different sizes, maximizing every inch of space.

Han Li quickly tracked down his room using his ticket, and the interior was very small, only around ten feet in size, with only a bed and a small table and chair inside.

He closed the door and sat down onto the bed, then began examining the surrounding area with his spiritual sense.

The walls of the room all had restrictions to separate them, but they may as well have been non-existent in the face of Han Li's spiritual sense.

To his surprise, Sun Chongshan's group of five just so happened to have been in the room right next to his.

Their room was far larger than Han Li's, but there was also a bed, a table, and a chair inside.

Despite its larger size, it was naturally rather cramped with five people staying in it at once.

"It's a little cramped, but we'll just have to make do," Sun Chongshan said.

Both the white-robed nun and Celestial Maiden Miao's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the cramped space.

"Let's leave the bed to Celestial Maiden Yu and Celestial Maiden Miao. The three of us can just sit on the floor," the black-robed young man said.

Celestial Maiden Yu!

Han Li's heart eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this.

However, the middle-aged vagrant cultivator completely ignored this arrangement and sat down onto the bed before anyone else had a chance to.

The black-robed young man's expression instantly darkened upon seeing this.

"You can try to appease the girls by offering them the bed, but I have no obligation to do as you say," the man sneered, then laid down onto the bed.

The black-robed young man was furious. He enjoyed a very lofty status in his clan and had never been disrespected like this. He clenched his fists tightly, yet right as he was about to lash out, the man laying on the bed suddenly turned to him with a cold glare of a venomous snake.

The black-robed young man instantly shuddered, and his fury faded away as if a bucket of cold water had just been poured over his head, leaving him rooted to the spot.

"Let's be civilized now. Seeing as Fellow Daoist Lin is feeling weary, he can take a rest on the bed, while the rest of us sit on the floor," Sun Chongshan hurriedly mediated.

The black-robed young man gave a cold harrumph upon hearing this, but it was clear that he was glad that the conflict had been deescalated.

The middle-aged man gave him a cold sneer, then closed his eyes to rest.

A hint of burning resentment flashed through the black-robed young man's eyes, only to be immediately suppressed.

Before long, everyone had sat down in the room, and peace and quiet was restored.

......

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he observed the conflict that had just taken place.

It was a rather interesting group of people staying in that room, and perhaps something noteworthy would happen in there over the course of the journey.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to set up several layers of restrictions in the room, and shortly thereafter, the Sun Moon Flying Boat rose up into the air.

Through a small window in the room, Han Li could see that the flying boat was rapidly ascending, rising up high above Gilded City before speeding away as a streak of blue light.

The city down below was left behind in the blink of an eye, and Han Li was very pleased to see the incredible speed on display.

The Sun Moon Flying Boat was no slower than his own speed of flight, and at this rate, it would definitely be able to reach Nine Origins City within thirty years.

He swept a sleeve through the air once again to release several golden Dao Warriors to guard the room, following which he entered his Flower Branch domain.

"Have you already set off for Nine Origins City, Master?" Weeping Soul asked as she approached him, and Xiaobai strode over to join them as well.

Han Li nodded in response and told them about the Sun Moon Flying Boat.

"Where are Qu Lin and Lan Yan?" Han Li suddenly asked.

He was unable to detect their auras.

"Qu Lin was snooping around the Flower Branch domain just now, so I used a secret technique to catch him off guard and put him to sleep. Lan Yan hasn't done anything out of line, but as a safety precaution, I put her to sleep as well," Weeping Soul replied as she pointed at a pavilion in the distance, and Han Li extended his spiritual sense toward the pavilion to discover the two of them laying unconscious inside.

"That's not a bad idea," he said with a nod of approval.

He had entered the Flower Branch domain with the plan of continuing to cultivate using the space of accelerated time, so even if Weeping Soul hadn't done anything, he would've sealed the six senses of Qu Lin and Lan Yan anyway.

With that in mind, he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up several layers of restrictions around the pavilion that the two of them were staying in as an additional layer of security, then made his way over to the Celestial Time Array.

A corner of the array was already broken, leaving the entire array in a dysfunctional state.

Han Li had no choice but to damage the array in order to free himself from his own spirit domain last time.

Thankfully, he still had some materials left, so repairing the array wasn't going to be a difficult task.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a small pile of materials appeared on the ground, and he began working on repairing the array.

Chapter 1209: Space of Accelerated Time

After close to half a day of toil, the Celestial Time Array was repaired, and Han Li brought out his Immortal Origin Stones to power the array.

After that, he sat down beside the array with his legs crossed, and after a brief hesitation, he released his spirit domain to encompass the array, but he limited the size of the spirit domain to only around two hundred to three hundred feet in diameter. After all, the larger the spirit domain, the more energy it required to maintain.

Weeping Soul was standing nearby, and she was also encompassed within the spirit domain.

A hint of surprise appeared on her face, and she was clearly unsure of why Han Li had released his spirit domain, but she didn't say anything.

Han Li summoned his time-attribute law treasures one after another, and the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Time Severing Torch flew up into the air to transform into a moon and a sun, respectively, while the Illusory Dawn Hourglass descended to form a sea of golden sand. The Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree transformed into a sprawling forest over the golden sand, while the Clear Time Vial became a golden river.

In the blink of an eye, it was as if his spirit domain had become an actual world, and only the sea of sand and golden river were still looking a little insubstantial.

Right at this moment, the golden moon formed by the Mantra Treasured Axis suddenly descended to hover above the Celestial Time Array.

The latter instantly lit up and began to operate at a far faster rate than before, while the Mantra Treasured Axis was also glowing radiantly while revolving rapidly, but in the reverse direction, and the two were resonating with one another.

At the same time, golden sand began swirling within the spirit domain, while the golden river churned violently. The golden sun radiated fiery heat, while the forest down below also began to rustle and sway incessantly.

The spirit domain had once again escaped Han Li's control, but given the experience from last time, he remained calm and allowed the spirit domain to resonate with the Celestial Time Array.

A resounding boom abruptly rang out as a burst of blinding golden light erupted out of the Mantra Treasured Axis, forming a wave of golden light that swept through the entire spirit domain.

The Celestial Time Array itself also released a burst of time law power fluctuations, and the two immediately fused together.

The five bursts of conflicting time law powers in the spirit domain quickly subsided as peace was restored, but the flow of time within the spirit domain had been accelerated to around ten thousand times its normal rate.

Weeping Soul was quickly able to detect this change in the flow of time, and a stunned look appeared on her face, following which she turned to look at Han Li with an admiring expression.

The hundredfold space of accelerated time that Han Li had set up last time had already been quite extraordinary in her eyes, and this was nothing short of a miracle to her.

Master really is blessed by the heavens, she thought to herself as she sat down to refine the Infernal Ghost Claw and the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute.

These two immortal treasures possessed tremendous power. In particular, once she completely refined the Soul Scattering Bone Flute, she would be able to easily scatter the souls of others.

Unfortunately for Elder Xi Tang, he hadn't yet had a chance to refine the immortal treasure before he encountered Weeping Soul. Otherwise, he definitely wouldn't have been defeated so easily.

Meanwhile, Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief, having just proved to himself that the ten-thousandfold space of accelerated time was something that was replicable, rather than just a one-off occurrence.

However, just like last time, he was unable to control his own spirit domain in this state, so he had to find a more reliable way to deactivate the space of accelerated time. Otherwise, he would have to damage the Celestial Time Array every time he wanted to leave.

He closed his eyes and channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, sensing the flow of time law powers in the surrounding spirit domain.

This space of accelerated time was a product of a fusion between his spirit domain and the Celestial Time Array, so if he wanted to deactivate it, then he would have to focus his efforts on those two things.

He didn't know much about the Celestial Time Array, so he would have to focus his attention solely on the spirit domain to see if he could somehow wrest back control of it.

He had tried the same thing the last time he was trapped in this space, but at the time, he had been very agitated and quickly gave up, resorting to breaking out of the space of accelerated time through brute force.

On this occasion, he was far calmer than before, and he was meticulously examining the changes in the time law powers in the spirit domain.

Five hundred to six hundred years flew by in a flash.

On this day, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open as an elated look appeared on his face.

Over these past few centuries, he had noticed some things that had escaped his attention in the past.

Firstly, he had developed a decent understanding of how this space of accelerated time had come into existence.

The formation of the space of accelerated time relied on the power of the Heavenly Wheel Sundial. Even though the sundial had already vanished, the time law powers and abilities that it possessed weren't lost. Instead, it had merely fused as one with the Mantra Treasured Axis, so the current Mantra Treasured Axis was essentially equivalent to the Heavenly Wheel Sundial.

That was why the Mantra Treasured Axis could resonate with the Celestial Time Array to create this space.

Additionally, some type of peculiar interaction seemed to have taken place between his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra and the Celestial Time Array, resulting in the rate of time acceleration reaching ten-thousandfold.

Another interesting discovery that he had made was related to the energy that the Celestial Time Array consumed. Originally, it required Immortal Origin Stones and time law powers to function, and this remained the same, but the time law powers were no longer coming from the Eon Divine Lamp because the lamp had already fused with the Time Severing Torch.

Hence, the time law powers supporting the space of accelerated time were coming from his spirit domain.

With the incorporation of the Eon Divine Lamp, the Heavenly Wheel Sundial, and the Twin Birth Tree, Han Li's spirit domain contained tremendous time law powers, more than enough to power the Celestial Time Array.

On top of that, even if the time law powers in his spirit domain were to be used up, it would be able to recover over time.

Han Li had always been concerned that the time law powers in the Eon Divine Lamp would be exhausted by the Celestial Time Array, but that was now no longer a concern.

However, due to the fact that the Heavenly Wheel Sundial and the Eon Divine Lamp had been incorporated into his spirit domain, there were some other limitations that he had to deal with.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the golden sun formed by the Time Severing Torch descended from the sky to arrive before him.

Peering into the golden sun, he could see over a hundred and eighty Time Dao Runes, but several of them had already gone dim.

Once all of the Time Dao Runes faded, the spirit domain would deactivate on its own, so that provided Han Li with a method to deactivate the space of accelerated time.

However, this was far too passive and unreliable, and he wouldn't have control over when the spirit domain was deactivated, so it was not a truly viable solution.

The golden sun flew back up into the sky at his behest, following which he raised a hand, and five beams of golden light shot out of his fingertips.

The golden light contained countless golden runes that were giving off five bursts of incredibly formidable time law powers, and he chanted an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, upon which the five beams of golden light formed five golden rings.

The time law powers emanating from them instantly became several times more potent, and each of them vanished into one of the time-attribute law treasure manifestations in the spirit domain.

The golden moon, the golden sun, the lush forest, the turbulent river, and the golden sand all lit up in unison, and the entire spirit domain began to struggle against the restrictive forces outside.

The spirit domain instantly began to tremble, but it remained firmly intact.

Weeping Soul was roused from her cultivation upon sensing the disturbance, but she didn't say anything to interrupt Han Li upon seeing the look of concentration on his face.

The entire spirit domain began to churn violently, but the restrictive forces outside remained insurmountable. Instead of the spirit domain breaking, the Celestial Time Array was beginning to flash erratically, as if it could fail at any moment.

Han Li hurriedly stopped what he was doing as he heaved a faint sigh.

Looks like brute force alone won't do the trick, after all.

At this rate, the Celestial Time Array was going to be ruined before he could break the restrictive forces outside the spirit domain.

That would allow him to undo the space of accelerated time, but he wanted to search for alternative solutions that were more sustainable.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he examined the surrounding spirit domain, and he wasn't discouraged by his failure.

Over these past few centuries of observation, he wasn't able to identify why the spirit domain had been restricted, but he had developed some ideas on how to dispel the restrictions.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, which enveloped the Immortal Origin Stones near the Celestial Time Array before stowing them away into his storage tool.

Immediately thereafter, he suppressed his own immortal spiritual power and time law powers, doing everything in his power to sever his connection to his spirit domain.

The spirit domain was formed by his immortal spiritual power, so surely it would fade away on its own after losing its power source.

The spirit domain immediately began flashing erratically as if it were about to fail, and Han Li's eyes lit up with excitement upon seeing this.

However, right at this moment, a burst of tremendous devouring force erupted out of the spirit domain, forcibly drawing the immortal spiritual power out of Han Li's body against his will.

The flashing spirit domain instantly stabilized itself again, and having lost its powers source in the form of the Immortal Origins Stones, the Celestial Time Array had begun rapidly devouring the immortal spiritual power in the spirit domain, thereby further compounding Han Li's rate of immortal spiritual power expenditure.

His eyes narrowed slightly as he allowed the immortal spiritual power to surge out of his body.

He wanted to see if the spirit domain would be able to continue operating once his immortal spiritual power was completely exhausted.

Having reached the Great Encompassment Stage, he now possessed tremendous reserves of immortal spiritual power, and only after close to half a day did his immortal spiritual power finally begin to run out.

However, the spirit domain and the Celestial Time Array were still rapidly absorbing his immortal spiritual power without displaying any signs of stopping.

Chapter 1210: 180,000 Years

It didn't take long before the immortal spiritual power in Han Li's body was completely sucked dry, but the devouring force didn't fade, turning to target his immense bloodline power instead.

He gritted his teeth tightly as he continued to persevere, but even after his immortal spiritual power had been completely exhausted, the devouring force released by the spirit domain was only becoming stronger, seemingly intent on sucking him completely dry.

This isn't going to work!

Han Li was just about to give up and release the Immortal Origin Stones again when a burst of devouring force that was several times more powerful than before suddenly converged toward him from all directions, instantly rendering him completely immobile, unable to even lift a finger.

An alarmed look appeared on his face as he tried to struggle against the devouring force with all his might, but to no avail.

His bloodline power was still being rapidly devoured, and a sense of feebleness was beginning to arise in his body, while his mind was also dipping into unconsciousness.

Weeping Soul didn't know what was happening, but she could sense that something was very wrong, and she yelled out in alarm as she hurriedly approached Han Li.

However, right at this moment, a burst of powerful golden light erupted out of his body in a formidable wave, sending Weeping Soul flying back through the air.

Countless more waves of golden light continued to sweep out of Han Li's body, while he seemed to have entered a half-asleep state.

All of a sudden, the waves of golden light formed a golden ball that was around ten feet tall around him.

Countless golden runes were swirling over the golden ball to keep out the spirit domain's devouring force, and the outflow of bloodline power instantly ceased, snapping Han Li back into a fully conscious state.

He took a moment to compose himself, then looked around at the surrounding golden ball as a surprised look flashed through his eyes.

In the next instant, a burst of incredibly profound law intent entered his mind from the golden ball.

The cultivation art of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra flowed through his mind character by character, sentence by sentence, and all of pieces of guidance that Patriarch Miro had offered to him also arose, along with the many insights that he had gleaned himself from his cultivation of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

All of these fused together as he extended his right hand forward, almost in a trance-like state, and a thick beam of golden light erupted out of the palm of his hand, contained within which was a multitude of time law threads.

He had gained many more time law threads during his ascension to the Great Encompassment Stage, and he currently possessed over three hundred and thirty time law threads.

The golden converged toward a single spot with all of the time law threads entangled within, and a burst of tremendous time law powers erupted forth from within.

All of the golden light and time law threads instantly vanished, replaced by a golden ball that was roughly the size of a human head. It resembled a miniature sun that was giving off boundless time law power fluctuations, and in the next instant, the golden ball abruptly fused into the surrounding spirit domain.

The entire spirit domain began to tremble and sway violently, and countless cracks appeared over its surface like a shattered mirror.

The spirit domain quickly fell away, and the Celestial Time Array also ceased operating, while Han Li reappeared in the Flower Branch space.

The golden ball around him had also vanished, and he fell onto his backside with a loud thump while gasping for air.

His complexion was incredibly pale, but his eyes were glowing with elation.

That golden ball just now seemed to have been the supposed final form of law power manifestation, known as a law orb.

Patriarch Miro had once told him about the states that law powers could exist in, namely law threads, law rings, and law orbs.

Only after truly mastering a type of law powers to a highly advanced level could one create a law orb.

Somehow, his near-death experience had granted him this unexpected blessing.

"Are you alright, Master? You scared me to death just now!" Weeping Soul exclaimed as she flew over to his side and helped him into an upright position.

Han Li gave her a nod of reassurance, then took some pills to aid in his recovery.

Weeping Soul could see that Han Li was a little feeble, so she remained by his side to keep a lookout while he recuperated.

The world's origin qi within the Flower Branch domain converged toward Han Li, while bursts of the world's origin qi also flowed into the domain from outside.

Not only that, but energy of all types of other attributes were also flowing into his body from the domain, including fire, lightning, wood, and even devilish and ghostly qi.

As a Great Encompassment cultivator, his control over the energy of heaven and earth had become countless times more proficient than before.

As the name suggested, the powers of a Great Encompassment cultivator encompassed everything around them, granting them an unrivaled level of control over their environment.

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li slowly opened his eyes, having recovered all his lost energy.

Great Encompassment cultivators were able to recover from their injuries extremely quickly thanks to their ability to draw upon all types of energy from heaven and earth.

On top of that, the Twin Birth Tree seemed to possess healing properties that had been inherited by the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree, thereby further enhancing Han Li's recovery abilities.

"What happened just now, Master? Are you alright now?" Weeping Soul asked in a concerned manner.

"I'm fine. The space of accelerated time that I set up wasn't perfect, so I suffered some backlash from it just now, but I've already made a full recovery."

Han Li didn't have a comprehensive understanding of the space of accelerated time himself, so he could only give Weeping Soul a rather ambiguous explanation.

"That's good to hear," Weeping Soul said with a sigh of relief.

Han Li cast his gaze toward a certain direction in the Flower Branch domain, then made a grabbing motion to release two bursts of golden light, sweeping up the cultivating Xiaobai and the Essence Fire Child before carrying them to his side.

His control over his own power had become so proficient that the two of them continued to cultivate, unaware of the fact that they had been moved.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li released his time spirit domain once again, which integrated itself with the Celestial Time Array to create the ten-thousandfold space of accelerated time.

Encompassed within the spirit domain, Xiaobai instantly snapped to his senses before looking around with a surprised expression.

Meanwhile, the Essence Fire Child continued to refine the demon core of the Three-Legged Golden Crow in an oblivious state.

"The flow of time in this space is ten thousand times faster than that of the outside world, so all of you can cultivate in here from now on," Han Li said.

"Does that mean ten thousand years in here is only the equivalent of one year in the outside world?" Xiaobai exclaimed.

"Let's go cultivate over there so we don't disturb Master," Weeping Soul said as she ushered Xiaobai away to the side, while Han Li closed his eyes and took a moment to compose himself before channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

Now that the issue regarding his space of accelerated time had been resolved, he could focus on his cultivation.

With the Reincarnation Palace mission looming so close, he had to take full advantage of this time to enhance his own powers as much as possible.

Unfortunately, he didn't have any pills in his possession that could aid him in this process, so he could only cultivate by absorbing the world's origin qi. Thankfully, he had already opened almost all of the one thousand eight hundred profound acupoints over his body, so opening immortal acupoints was going to be far easier for him than for others.

Bursts of radiant, golden light surged out of his body, forming a ball of golden light the size of a house, and it was pulsing incessantly in a rhythmic fashion like a giant, beating heart.

With each pulse, immense bursts of the world's origin qi would converge from all directions to be funneled into it.

180,000 years flew by in a flash.

All of a sudden, the space of accelerated time began flashing before rapidly dimming.

The ball of golden light shuddered before instantly fading away to reveal Han Li with over four hundred and sixty immortal acupoints glowing all over his body.

Even without the assistance of pills, he had managed to open a hundred immortal acupoints over the past 180,000 years of cultivation.

He looked up into the air and made a beckoning motion, and the moon formed by the Mantra Treasured Axis descended from above right as the final Time Dao Rune on its surface was fading away.

Just as he had anticipated, with all of the Time Dao Runes snuffed out, the space of accelerated time would unravel on its own.

Having opened a hundred immortal acupoints during this bout of seclusion, he had attained two hundred Time Dao Runes, bringing the total to over one thousand eight hundred Time Dao Runes, which had supported the space of accelerated time for 180,000 years.

This meant that each Time Dao Runes could grant him about a hundred years of cultivation.

It seemed like he was going to have to make it a priority to accumulate more Time Dao Runes.

At the same time, Weeping Soul and Xiaobai also awakened from their cultivation.

Xiaobai had already completely refined his father's bloodline power, making his Ink-Eyed Pixiu aura completely restrained and undetectable, so he appeared no different from a pure human.

His aura had almost reached the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, and a surprised look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon sensing, but it then quickly occurred to him that this was really no cause for surprise.

Xiaobai was the only descendant of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu, who had been very close with Bai Ze, so the latter was sure to have granted him a multitude of cultivation resources.

For the average Great Encompassment cultivator, 180,000 years of cultivation really wasn't much at all, yet Xiaobai had managed to make significant progress during this time.

Weeping Soul's aura had also become a lot stronger, but her improvement was severely lacking compared with Xiaobai. Having said that, the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute had already fused as one with her aura, indicating that it had already been completely refined.

Even though it currently wasn't being played, a series of ghostly notes could be seen flashing around it, presenting a mesmerizing sight to behold.

As soon as Han Li's gaze fell upon the flute, a chorus of ghostly howls instantly began ringing out inside his mind.

He hurriedly averted his eyes in an alarmed manner while channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique to quell the unrest in his soul.

The Essence Fire Child had also awakened, and not only had it regained all of its lost power, it had become a lot more powerful, with the flames over its body giving off boundless light and heat.

Chapter 1211: Natural Disaster

"Well done, I can see that all of you have made great progress," Han Li said with a nod of approval.

"We all have you to thank for creating such an exceptional cultivation environment for us, Master," Weeping Soul said with a warm smile.

"Why did you suddenly stop, Master?" Xiaobai asked.

He was at a crucial juncture in the cultivation of a secret technique just now, so he felt a little frustrated to have been interrupted.

"A ten-thousandfold space of accelerated time is not just something that I can set up anytime that I please. We're not going to have access to it in the near future," Han Li said.

His Time Dao Runes needed time to recover, and there were also barely any Immortal Origin Stones left next to the Celestial Time Array.

Even though he had managed to obtain Elder Xi Tang's storage tool, there had been barely any Immortal Origin Stones left in it as he had spent everything on the Soul Scattering Ghost Flute.

If he wanted to set up the space of accelerated time again, not only did he have to wait for his Time Dao Runes to recover, he would also have to accumulate a large sum of Immortal Origin Stones as well.

"It's going to be very slow progress cultivating with the flow of time back to normal," Xiaobai sighed.

"Quite whining! You should be grateful that our master went to so much effort to set up this space of accelerated time for us!" Weeping Soul scolded as she gave Xiaobai a knock on the head with her Soul Scattering Ghost Flute.

A ghostly shriek instantly pierced into his mind, causing him to shudder involuntarily.

"Ow!"

Xiaobai felt as if he had just had a bite taken out of his soul by a malicious ghost, causing him to yelp in pain.

His immediate reaction was to pounce on Weeping Soul in retaliation, but he didn't dare to do so for fear of her Soul Scattering Ghost Flute.

"Alright, stop messing around. I won't be able to set up the space of accelerated time again anytime soon, but you can still cultivate in the Flower Branch domain. I'll go see what's happening outside," Han Li said as he departed from the Flower Branch domain.

Upon arriving outside, Han Li discovered that the Dao Warriors were still in the room, and nothing was out of the ordinary.

He took a glance out the window, and he was greeted by the sight of a glowing, golden mountain range, with much of the plant life on the mountains also displaying a golden coloration.

This landmark alone wasn't enough to tell him the flying boat's current location, so he made his way out of his room before returning shortly thereafter.

He had just gone out to enquire about the whereabouts of the flying boat, upon which he was informed that over half the journey was already complete, and barring any mishaps, they were set to arrive in Nine Origins City in around ten more years.

Without the space of accelerated time, there was no point in entering the Flower Branch domain, and he could keep an eye on things by staying outside, so he remained in his room instead of returning to the domain.

He sat down with his legs crossed on the bed, then flipped a hand over to produce a stack of jade slips and books.

These scriptures contained information that he had gathered in Gilded City about the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region and Nine Origins City, and none of it was of particular importance, but it was still never a bad idea to be armed with more knowledge.

Han Li was just about to begin reading through the scriptures when a thought suddenly occurred to him.

How's that nun doing?

He had forgotten all about her during the close to two hundred thousand years he had spent in the Flower Branch domain.

He activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and his gaze easily penetrated through the restrictions in the walls, allowing him to peer into the neighboring room.

Everyone in the room was seated in silence, and it appeared that all was well.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face, and he was considering confirming with the nun herself to see if she actually was Yu Menghan so he wouldn't have to keep guessing.

Right at this moment, a loud commotion rang out from outside.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as a series of blue runes appeared over one of the walls of his room, forming a simple, blue array.

A calm and reassuring voice rang out within the array.

"A wave of level five Golden Astral Wind is currently approaching the flying boat, but do not be concerned as the boat's protective restrictions will be enough to weather the storm. Having said that, please stay in your rooms during this time for your own safety."

Just like the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region, the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region was also extremely abundant with metal-attribute spiritual energy, and it was precisely because of this that a type of natural disaster called Golden Astral Wind would occasionally arise due to disturbances in the metal-attribute spiritual energy.

Golden Astral Wind was classified in terms of levels, with level one being the lowest, while level nine was the highest.

Level five Golden Astral Wind was already quite formidable, but according to the voice in the array, the passengers didn't have anything to worry about.

Not long after this warning was issued, a burst of thunderous rumbling began to ring out in the distance.

Han Li looked out through the window to see a golden light on the horizon, and it was rapidly approaching while giving off a thunderous rumbling, expanding to form a boundless golden storm in the blink of an eye.

Everything swept up by the golden storm was quickly razed to the ground, and as the storm drew closer, a thick, blue light barrier appeared over the surface of the Sun Moon Flying Boat to fully encompass it.

Countless starry patterns were flashing over the blue light barrier, giving it an indestructible appearance similar to that of a True Extreme Film.

The protective barrier had only just taken shape when the golden storm arrived, and the entire sky instantly darkened as the Sun Moon Flying Boat shuddered violently before being thrown violently to the side.

Right at this moment, the runes inscribed onto the surface of the flying boat began to glow radiantly, and it was quickly able to stabilize itself before continuing onward, but at a far slower speed than before.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to be startled by such a minor disturbance, and he released his spiritual sense to assess the situation within the Golden Astral Wind.

All of a sudden, Weeping Soul flew out of the Flower Branch domain with a wary expression as she asked, "Did something happen, Master? I suddenly felt a wave of panicked emotions sweep over the flying boat."

An alarmed look then appeared on her face as she caught sight of the golden storm raging outside.

"This is a special type of natural disaster, and the passengers are a little alarmed to have encountered it," Han Li explained.

"I see," Weeping Soul replied with a relieved expression.

"Now that you're here, I have a request for you. There's a female cultivator in the neighboring room that bears a striking resemblance to a friend of mine from a lower realm. However, it's been many years since we last parted ways, so I can't be certain of her identity. Would you be able to check for me?" Han Li asked.

"Of course. Which one is it?" Weeping Soul asked.

"The white-robed nun in that room over there," Han Li replied as he pointed at the room in question.

Weeping Soul released his spiritual sense into the room for a moment, following which a displeased pout appeared on her face as she accused, "She's quite the beauty. Could it be that she's a lover of yours?"

"She's just a friend, and I'm not very familiar with her. Otherwise, I would've been able to verify her identity myself," Han Li replied with an amused smile.

"Alright, I'll take a look for you," Weeping Soul said with a nod, but right as she was about to spring into action, a look of surprise suddenly appeared on her face.

"What's wrong?" Han Li asked.

"The people in that room are all very strange. There's one of them in particular that's very interesting," Weeping Soul replied with a faint smile.

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked.

"Something's about to happen. If you're interested, you should take a look," Weeping Soul replied with a mysterious smile.

Han Li was rather intrigued to hear this, and he peered into the neighboring room with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

The five cultivators in the neighboring room had all stopped cultivating to look at the golden storm raging outside with fearful looks on their faces.

They were all Golden Immortals, so direct exposure to the storm would've spelled instant death for them.

The storm was only becoming more and more ferocious, and golden blades of wind were striking the blue protective barrier of the Sun Moon Flying Boat one after another.

The blue light barrier was able to keep the blades of golden wind at bay, but the commotion from the repeated impacts was so loud that some of the weaker cultivators among the passengers on the boat felt as if their eardrums were about to split open.

The five cultivators in the neighboring room had set up around a dozen layers of restrictions and even summoned defensive immortal treasures to protect themselves, but that didn't do much to ward off the debilitating commotion, and all they could do was grit their teeth and bear the pain.

All of a sudden, Sun Chongshan threw up a mouthful of blood as his aura was thrown into a state of disarray.

"Are you alright, Fellow Daoist Sun?" the red-robed woman hurriedly asked in a concerned manner.

A concerned look also appeared on the black-robed young man's face, while the yellow-robed man on the bed also took a glance at Sun Chongshan, but it was one of derision.

As for the white-robed nun, she remained as expressionless as ever.

"I'm fine. I sustained some damage to my internal organs during a recent battle that I've still yet to recover from, and those injuries have been slightly reaggravated," Sun Chongshan replied.

He then took a pill before continuing, "This storm isn't going to pass anytime soon, and if things continue like this, all of us are most likely going to suffer internal injuries sooner or later. I have a spatial immortal treasure that should be able to provide us with adequate shelter to weather the storm."

Chapter 1212: Three-Legged Cauldron

"That's great! I'm sure we'd all be very thankful if you could share that spatial treasure with us," the red-robed woman immediately said, and the black-robed young man nodded eagerly in agreement.

"You seem a little hesitant, Fellow Daoist Sun. Could it be that there are some difficulties involved in using this treasure?" the yellow-robed man asked.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Lian. The immortal treasure in question is a fifth tier immortal treasure that has sustained some damage, so the five of us will have to combine our powers to use it, and it'll be quite taxing on all of us. Would the four of you be willing to help me?" Sun Chongshan asked.

A hint of greed flashed through the yellow-robed man's eyes upon hearing this, and he readily agreed, "Of course. Anything would be better than having to suffer passively like this."

The red-robed woman and the black-robed young man also nodded in agreement, but the white-robed nun remained silent.

"What do you say, Celestial Maiden Yu?" Sun Chongshan asked.

There was a hesitant look on her face, but as more and more golden blades of wind crashed into the flying boat, the commotion was only getting louder and louder, to the point that she was struggling to breathe, so she finally acquiesced in the end.

"If this immortal treasure of yours can shelter us, then I'm willing to do my part as well," the white-robed nun replied, and Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this.

Her voice was identical to Yu Menghan's, and on top of that, Sun Chongshan had just revealed her surname by referring to her as Celestial Maiden Yu.

In light of all of this, Han Li was now almost certain that this woman was none other than Yu Menghan.

"Alright, then let's begin," Sun Chongshan said in an elated manner as he opened his mouth to release a three-legged, dark red cauldron.

The cauldron was rather antiquated in appearance, and one half of it was etched with crude, yet extremely life-like designs of all types of living creatures, while the other half was riddled with ancient characters, all of which were glowing faintly.

Unfortunately, one of its legs had been snapped off, leaving it in an incomplete state.

All of a sudden, Han Li's gaze fell upon the ancient text on the cauldron, and a look of surprise and excitement appeared on his face.

"What is it, Master?" Weeping Soul asked, but Han Li didn't appear to have heard her at all.

Sun Chongshan opened his mouth to release a burst of golden light that vanished into the cauldron in a flash, and at the same time, he cast a rapid flurry of incantation seals into it.

A burst of dark red light instantly appeared over the cauldron, and the light began to spread outward, but at a very slow rate.

"Help me, fellow daoists! Inject your immortal spiritual power into the cauldron!" Sun Chongshan yelled in an urgent manner, and everyone else immediately released their immortal spiritual power.

A burst of tremendous devouring force erupted out of the cauldron, and in the blink of an eye, all five cultivators in the room had roughly a third of their immortal spiritual power sucked away.

Thankfully, the rate at which the cauldron devoured their immortal spiritual power slowed down immediately thereafter, and the dark red light radiating from it filled the entire room to encompass the five cultivators inside.

The sound of the thunderous commotion outside completely faded away, allowing everyone to heave a collective sigh of relief.

Sun Chongshan turned to his four companions with a warm smile, yet before he had a chance to say anything, a dark green sword suddenly pierced through his lower abdomen, following which bursts of green light rose up from it to ensnare his entire body.

Sun Chongshan's skin instantly turned green, and he fell to the ground in a lifeless manner with a loud thump.

Immediately thereafter, the yellow-robed man appeared beside the three-legged cauldron before drawing it into his grasp.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and only now did everyone else react to what had just happened.

"Lian Yan! What the hell are you doing?!" the black-robed young man roared in a furious voice, while the white-robed nun and the red-robed woman were both also looking on with enraged expressions.

A cold sneer appeared on Lian Yan's face, and he paid no heed to the three of them as he prepared to stow the cauldron away.

However, right at this moment, the dark red light that had filled the entire room suddenly swept up the five cultivators before sucking them into the cauldron before they had a chance to react.

In the blink of an eye, all of them had vanished without a trace, leaving only the cauldron hovering in the center of the room.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Weeping Soul appeared in the room amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, and the former's gaze was still fixed intently on the ancient text on the cauldron.

"Looks like this cauldron is indeed a remarkable spatial treasure. What do we do now? Do we wait for them to come back out?" Weeping Soul asked.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then opened his mouth to release a ball of azure flames to envelop the cauldron from all sides.

......

The five cultivators had been transported into a dark red space that was around ten kilometers in size.

The ground and the sky were all dark red in color, and there was a glacial aura in the air that made the environment feel very inhospitable.

At this moment, they were standing on a plaza that was surrounded by nine dark red stone plaques that were several hundred feet tall. All of them were etched with complex patterns, seemingly to form an array.

Unfortunately, three of the stone plaques were damaged, leaving the array in an incomplete state.

There were many tall buildings near the plaza that filled virtually the entire dark red space, but most of these buildings had collapsed, and there were also many rifts and craters in the ground, indicating that a fierce battle had taken place here at some point.

Right as everyone was looking around in bewilderment, Sun Chongshan's body suddenly began to swell up like a balloon, and in the blink of an eye, it had transformed into a crimson blob of flesh that was around ten feet in size.

The blob resembled a giant tumor that was soaked in blood and riddled with green spots, presenting a disgusting and horrific sight to behold.

The other four cultivators hurriedly sprang back in retreat upon seeing this, but all of a sudden, the tumor-like growth suddenly sprang to life and set off in pursuit of Lian Yan.

It was far faster than Lian Yan, and in the blink of an eye, the distance between them had been closed down to only less than two hundred feet.

An alarmed look appeared on Lian Yan's face as he hurriedly changed directions, darting away to the left while simultaneously sweeping a sleeve through the air to release the same green sword from before.

In the blink of an eye, the green sword transformed into a streak of green swordlight that was over a thousand feet in length before hurtling toward his assailant, but before the swordlight even had a chance to reach the tumor-like growth, it had already exploded, sending chunks of flesh flying through the air alongside fierce, crimson shockwaves.

An alarmed look appeared on Lian Yan's face as he hurriedly opened his mouth to release an antiquated, black shield in front of himself.

In the next instant, a resounding boom rang out as the explosive shockwaves struck the black shield, sending it and Lian Yan both flying back tens of thousands of feet.

Even though the black shield had managed to keep the shockwaves at bay, the power behind them was still enough to send Lian Yan reeling.

Before he had a chance to catch his breath, nine golden daggers suddenly appeared out of thin air, hurtling directly toward him from behind.

Engraved onto the hilt of each dagger was a strange two-headed beast, and the daggers were giving off an incredibly cold aura.

Lian Yan hurriedly dodged to the side once again while a burst of green light erupted out of his body to meet the nine golden daggers.

However, right at this moment, the two-headed beasts engraved onto the hilts of the nine daggers suddenly opened their mouths in unison, releasing nine bursts of golden soundwaves that descended upon him from all directions.

A pained look appeared on his face as he involuntarily stopped cold in his tracks, while the nine daggers quickly arranged themselves into an array.

The protective green light around Lian Yan was instantly torn to shreds, following which his body was sliced into pieces.

A ball of green light shot out his dismembered remains before fleeing into the distance, and it was none other than his nascent soul.

However, it wasn't able to get very far before it was intercepted by the black-robed young man, who caught it mid-flight as it was trying to flee.

"You're completely at my mercy now, Lian Yan! This is what you get for displaying such insolence to me! I'm going to burn this nascent soul of yours over a yin flame to torment you for centuries!" the black-robed young man chortled as he glowered at the green nascent soul with a look of twisted joy on his face.

A hint of disgust flashed through the white-robed nun's eyes at the sight of the black-robed young man's hideous expression, but she still flew to his side along with the red-robed woman.

"Lian Yan deserves to die for killing Fellow Daoist Sun, but we're not exactly safe ourselves in this place, so let's join forces to scout out the area, Fellow Daoist Tie," the white-robed nun said.

The black-robed young man hurriedly adopted a serious expression as he nodded in response and stowed away his nine golden daggers and the green nascent soul.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light toward Lian Yan's storage tool and that green sword, but right at this moment, a burst of dark red light suddenly flashed over the plaza, and Lian Yan's remains abruptly vanished, along with his storage tool and green sword.

The black-robed young man faltered slightly upon seeing this, as did the two women.

All of a sudden, Sun Chongshan appeared out of thin air with a smile on his face as he said, "Lian Yan's death was indeed well-deserved, but I'm afraid you'll be following in his footsteps before too long."

Chapter 1213: Bestowing A Gift

"Fellow Daoist Sun? Weren't you killed by Lian Yan?" the black-robed young man exclaimed with a dumbstruck expression.

At the same time, an alarmed look appeared on the white-robed nun's face, and she hurriedly dodged to the side, just in the time to evade a thin streak of red light that glanced past her body.

Another streak of red light also appeared behind the black-robed young man, and it pierced through his chest, leaving behind a large hole.

Blood began to gush out of his mouth in an uncontrollable manner as he fell to the ground with his aura in a state of complete disarray.

Behind them, the red-robed woman lowered her hands in an expressionless manner, and there was still some red light glowing over her fingertips.

"You two were working together all along!" the white-robed nun exclaimed in a furious manner as she drew to a halt several thousand feet away.

"You're very alert, Celestial Maiden Yu. Unfortunately, you're already in my territory, so no matter how much you struggle, it'll only end in futility," Sun Chongshan said with a faint smile as he swept a sleeve through the air, and countless rays of dark red light instantly shot out of the six stone plaques around the plaza, then intertwined with one another to form a massive net that descended upon the white-robed nun.

At the same time, a menacing, ghostly face appeared on one of the stone plazas, and it opened its mouth to release a burst of dark red light to encompass the black-robed young man on the ground.

The black-robed young man was just about to struggle to his feet, but he was instantly immobilized as soon as the red light shone down upon him.

The white-robed nun's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and she began fleeing from the plaza as a purple lightning spirit domain erupted out of her body.

Countless arcs of purple lightning were swirling within the spirit domain like a vortex, with the lightning at the center of the vortex glowing particularly bright.

All of the purple lightning within the spirit domain converged toward the center of the vortex, forming a purple lightning sword that struck the net of dark red light up ahead with boundless power.

An opening was instantly sliced into the net, and the white-robed nun flew out of her spirit domain, aiming to flee the plaza through the opening.

"So you've already attained a spirit domain, but so what?" Sun Chongshan chuckled coldly as he extended a hand forward before clenching it into a tight fist, and the sky above shuddered as rays of dark red light shone down from above, forming a projection of a dark red mountain that came crashing down from the sky.

A burst of terrifying force descended from the heavens, instantly destroying the lightning spirit domain, while the white-robed nun was also stopped in her tracks before plummeting from the sky like a meteorite.

As soon as she landed on the plaza, a giant, ghostly face appeared on the stone plaque nearest to her as well, then opened its mouth to release a burst of dark red light to envelop her entire body, immobilizing her just like the black-robed young man.

Sun Chongshan descended onto the plaza, and the red-robed woman landed behind him.

At the moment, there was a very stiff and wooden look on her face, making her resemble a puppet, presenting a stark contrast with the spritely and seductive demeanor that she had displayed in the past.

"You planned all of this from the very beginning, didn't you, Sun Chongshan? What are your intentions?" the white-robed nun asked in a cold voice.

Sun Chongshan paid no heed to her as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a black storage tool and a green sword, both of which previously belonged to Lian Yan.

At the same time, the white-robed nun and the black-robed young man's storage tools were also drawn into his grasp, and after taking a moment to inspect their contents with his spiritual sense, an ecstatic look appeared on Sun Chongshan's face as he exclaimed, "This is a massive haul!"

"So you lured us in here to kill and rob us? Don't forget about the stringent regulations of the Sun Moon Flying Boat! The identities and numbers of all of the cultivators in every room must be verified upon boarding and disembarking. If you kill us here, we'll be found missing, and you'll have to answer to the Sun Moon Alliance!" the white-robed nun threatened.

"You don't have to worry about that, Celestial Maiden Yu. I won't kill you, I'm only going to be refining you into puppet spirits of this Eighty-onefold Yama Array. From the outside, you'll be indistinguishable from your normal selves," Sun Chongshan chuckled coldly as he made a hand seal, and a giant, ghostly face appeared on another stone plaque, then opened its mouth to release a burst of light that vanished into a certain part of the plaza.

Lian Yan's remains appeared there amid a flash of crimson light, following which it was drawn into the ghostly face's cavernous mouth.

The ghostly face chewed on Lian Yan's remains for a moment, then opened its mouth once again, and Lian Yan flew out from within.

His appearance and aura were completely identical to before, and only his wooden expression indicated that there was anything wrong with him. However, all he required was a slight disguise like the one adopted by the red-robed woman, and there would be no way to tell him apart from his normal self.

"What do you think? Will the Sun Moon Alliance cultivators be able to tell?" Sun Chongshan asked with a triumphant smile, and looks of despair appeared on the faces of both the white-robed nun and the black-robed young man upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out across the plaza.

"That is indeed quite remarkable. My eyes have truly been opened."

"Who's there?" Sun Chongshan exclaimed as he hurriedly began inspecting his surroundings.

All of a sudden, the dark red light around the white-robed nun and the black-robed young man faded away, as did the dark red light emanating from the plaza and the stone plaques.

The white-robed nun and the black-robed young man hurriedly clambered to their feet before also looking around in bewilderment.

"This is impossible! This Yama Cauldron is mine! I've already completely refined it! How could it have been taken by someone else!" Sun Chongshan roared in an alarmed manner while frantically making a string of hand seals, but the surrounding space displayed no reaction.

"So Yama Cauldron is its name," Han Li remarked as he drifted down with Weeping Soul.

"It's you two! How dare you take my Yama Cauldron!" Sun Chongshan exclaimed at the sight of Han Li, then swept both sleeves through the air to release a flurry of items, most of which were powerful immortal treasures, interspersed with some offensive talismans, lightning beads, fire beads, and other one-time usage offensive treasures.

In response, Weeping Soul stepped forward and raised a hand, releasing a burst of black light to meet all of the oncoming immortal treasures and talismans.

The barrage of offensive treasures instantly slowed down to a crawl, as if they had plunged into a pit of quicksand, following which they flew obediently up her sleeve without posing any resistance.

"Who are you?!" Sun Chongshan exclaimed as his complexion turned deathly pale from fear, and the white-robed nun and the black-robed young man's expressions also changed drastically upon detecting Han Li and Weeping Soul's unfathomable auras.

"It's not everyday that I meet a Golden Immortal with such a vast collection of powerful treasures. Looks like you must've been robbing people for a very long time," Han Li remarked.

Sun Chongshan's complexion paled even further, and he began trembling uncontrollably.

"Thank you for saving us, seniors!"

The white-robed nun and the black-robed young man hurriedly stepped forward to offer their gratitude.

Han Li took a glance at the latter, then swept a sleeve through the air, and the black-robed young man instantly vanished, having been moved elsewhere.

The white-robed nun hurriedly lowered her head in a respectful manner upon seeing this.

Generally speaking, most vastly powerful cultivators had rather strange personalities, so she had to be extra careful not to cause any offense.

"What's your name?" Han Li asked as he strode over to the white-robed nun.

"My name is Yu Menghan," Yu Menghan hurriedly replied.

With that, Han Li's suspicions were confirmed.

"I can sense that you've ascended from a lower realm, is that right?"

Yu Menghan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied in a truthful manner, "You have a discerning eye like no other, Senior, I am indeed from a lower realm by the name of the Spirit Domain Realm."

"I knew it, I can sense the aura of the Spirit Domain Realm in you. I'm technically also from the Spirit Domain Realm, so I suppose we must've been fated to meet here. I can see that you have a great deal of lightning-attribute energy in your body, so you must've eaten some type of lightning-attribute spirit medicine, right?

“The cultivation art you're currently using is only going to squander the lightning-attribute energy in your body, so take this instead. It'll be my gift to you as a fellow cultivator of the Spirit Domain Realm."

Han Li pulled out a jade slip that contained a cultivation art from the Five Lightning True Mantra as he spoke.

Yu Menghan accepted the jade slip in a slightly dazed manner. She felt like there was something familiar about Han Li, but she couldn't recall where they could've possibly met before.

With another sweep of his sleeve, Yu Menghan was also evicted from the room.

"Wasn't that a friend of yours, Master? Why didn't you reveal your true appearance to her?" Weeping Soul asked through voice transmission.

"So many things have changed since we last met, so it won't do us or her any good for me to reveal my identity to her," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, then made his way over to Sun Chongshan.

"Please forgive me, Senior. I've done many heinous things in the past, but I can turn over a new leaf! I'm willing to offer this Yama Cauldron to you in exchange for my life!" Sun Chongshan pleaded as he fell to his knees and began kowtowing repeatedly to Han Li.

"Don't worry, I'm not here to kill you, and what you've done in the past has nothing to do with me. I have a few questions for you, and if you answer them truthfully, I can spare your life," Han Li said.

He wasn't some warrior of justice, and he had also killed and looted more than his fair share of people in the past.

The only difference was that all of the people that he had killed had harbored ill will toward him, whereas Sun Chongshan was killing purely for greed.

Chapter 1214: Arriving in Nine Origins City

Sun Chongshan was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly promised, "I'll tell you everything you want to know, Senior!"

"Where did you get this Yama Cauldron from?" Han Li asked.

"I found it in a set of ruins in the Heavenfall Immortal Region," Sun Chongshan replied.

"The Heavenfall Immortal Region?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

He had never heard of this immortal region before.

"It's a very small immortal region that's very sparse in spiritual power and resources, so the Heavenly Court hasn't bothered to set up a teleportation array there. As a result, very few people are aware of its existence. I only stumbled into it by chance as I was swallowed up by a spatial rift while fleeing from an enemy of mine," Sun Chongshan explained.

"You're certainly being very candid," Han Li remarked.

"I wouldn't dare to lie or keep anything from you, Senior," Sun Chongshan replied in a submissive manner.

"I see the words 'Yama Manor' engraved on the cauldron. Do you know of this place?" Han Li asked.

That inscription of Yama Manor was precisely why he had developed such a keen interest in the cauldron.

Following his return from his previous transmigration, he had searched extensively for information about this Yama Manor but to no avail, and never had he imagined that he would stumble upon a lead here.

"I'm afraid I've never heard of this place. Perhaps it's a certain place in the Heavenfall Immortal Region," Sun Chongshan replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Weeping Soul, who gave him a slight nod.

"You've answered my questions truthfully, so I'll hold up my end of the bargain and spare your life. Stay here for now, and I'll get you to take me to the Heavenfall Immortal Region sometime in the near future. After that, you're free to go," Han Li said.

"Thank you, Senior!" Sun Chongshan hurriedly replied in a grateful manner.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and Sun Chongshan instantly fell to the ground in an unconscious state.

After that, Han Li began examining the rest of the dark red space, and his gaze fell upon the six stone plaques around the plaza.

"These plaques are quite remarkable. I wonder what type of law powers they contain that allow them to resurrect the dead," Weeping Soul said with an intrigued look on her face.

"There are supposedly three thousand laws under the Great Dao, but in reality, there are far too many to count, so there's no way anyone can recognize all of them. By the way, you were saying that there's an interesting person here, were you referring to Sun Chongshan?"

"No, I was talking about her," Weeping Soul said as she pointed at the red-robed woman, and Han Li was rather taken aback to see this.

"Her soul is different from that of a normal person in that it harbors a strange, deathly aura, which we now know is because of these six stone plaques," Weeping Soul explained.

"This cauldron isn't really something I can fully make use of. Seeing as you're interested in it, you can have it. Also, make sure to keep an eye on Sun Chongshan," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air, sending a ball of dark red light flying into Weeping Soul's body.

"Thank you, Master," Weeping Soul replied in an ecstatic manner.

With Sun Chongshan restrained, Han Li didn't linger here any longer, returning directly to his room on the ship with Weeping Soul, who sat down with her legs crossed in the room to examine the Yama Cauldron, as opposed to returning to the Flower Branch domain.

The Golden Astral Winds were still raging outside, but the flying boat had already flown through the worst of the storm and was gradually speeding up.

After close to another month, the flying boat finally emerged from the storm of Golden Astral Wind and resumed travel at its normal speed.

Ten years flew by in a flash, and the destination of Nine Origins City was finally in sight.

Even though Han Li had already seen many enormous and majestic cities in the past, he still couldn't help but be stunned by the sight of Nine Origins City.

The first impression that the city gave him was that it was incredibly tall. Its walls were hundreds of thousands of feet tall, resembling an insurmountable barricade that stood between heaven and earth, while the city itself resembled a gargantuan beast in a state of slumber.

The city also stretched on for even farther than Han Li's eyes could see, with its borders encompassing several nearby mountain ranges.

The city was filled with countless streets that were packed people, presenting an incredibly lively and bustling sight to behold.

After taking a deep breath, Han Li sat back down in his room with his legs crossed, while the flying boat descended into the city.

An hour later, he emerged from a tall pagoda in the city and quickly vanished into the crowd on the street.

Yu Menghan emerged from the same pagoda shortly thereafter before looking around with an expectant expression, as if she were searching for someone, but in the end, a disappointed look appeared on her face as she departed.

Han Li was making his way quickly through the crowd, and even though this was his first time in Nine Origins City, he was racing along without any hesitation.

Wyrm 3 had already told him where in Nine Origins City he needed to go, so he had no hesitation in where he needed to be.

The street was lined with large shops that sold all types of wares, including immortal treasures, pills, and materials, and the city was thriving even more than Gilded City.

On top of that, the city was particularly lively, even more so than usual, as if preparations were underway for some type of festive event.

Han Li was rather intrigued to see this, but he continued onward without pause.

This was the territory of the Nine Origins Temple, and even though he couldn't sense anyone conducting surveillance on him, there was no telling how many people were currently scrutinizing him from the shadows.

According to Wyrm 3, the place that had been arranged for him to stay was the safest place in the city, while extra vigilance was required everywhere else he went.

Close to half a day later, Han Li arrived in an alley on the edge of the city, inside which was a small inn with its doors tightly shut.

He carefully inspected the main entrance of the inn, particularly a stone lion at the entrance, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he strode over to the doors before knocking on them in a certain rhythm.

"Who is it?"

A lazy voice rang out from inside, but the doors remained shut.

"Are there still any vacant rooms left? I want to stay here," Han Li replied while continuing to knock in the same rhythm.

Only after Han Li stopped knocking did the doors slowly swing open, and a boy who appeared to be in his mid-teens poked his head out from inside, sizing up Han Li as he asked, "You want to stay here?"

"That's right, I'm here to conduct some business in Nine Origins City, and I'm going to be staying here for half a year," Han Li replied, following a predesignated script.

"In that case, please come in."

The boy's eyes lit up slightly as he opened the door wider to allow Han Li to enter, then immediately closed the doors behind him.

Han Li stepped into a small courtyard, and as soon as he did so, he felt as if he had entered a special space, clearly indicating the presence of special restrictions around the inn.

He followed the boy to a room in the inn, where a portly, middle-aged man was going through some account books while clacking away on an abacus.

"We have a guest, shopkeeper," the boy declared.

The shopkeeper dismissed the boy, then closed the door and asked, "May I ask your name and how long you're planning to stay?"

"My name is Han Li, and I'm planning to stay here for half a year," Han Li replied as he pulled out his crimson mask to show the shopkeeper for a split second, then immediately stowed it away again.

This was also all part of the script.

"Welcome, Senior Han, Senior Wyrm 3 has already notified me of your arrival," the shopkeeper said as a fawning smile appeared on his face.

"Is Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 here?" Han Li asked.

"No, but she's asked me to inform you that she'll be here to meet with you and discuss the contents of the mission soon," the shopkeeper replied.

"Alright, I'll wait here for her then," Han Li replied with a nod, and the shopkeeper led him deeper into the inn.

After rounding a few corners, they arrived at a small courtyard that was very tidy and quiet.

Han Li gave a pleased nod, and the shopkeeper said, "You must be weary from your long journey, so I'll leave you to rest, Senior Han. If you need anything, then ring the little bell in the courtyard. I'll be taking my leave now."

"Hold on, don't go just yet, there's something that I want to ask you," Han Li said.

The shopkeeper faltered slightly upon hearing this, then said, "Go ahead, Senior, I'll be sure to answer your questions to the best of my abilities."

"I noticed that there seems to be a celebration taking place in the city. Is something happening?" Han Li asked.

"Have you not heard, Senior Han? The immortal envoys of the Heavenly Court are going to personally visit the Nine Origins Temple to present thirty-six spots to attend the Bodhi Banquet, and the entire city is preparing for the occasion," the shopkeeper replied in a surprised manner.

"Is that right? I've been busy with cultivation of late, so I haven't heard about this. I'm aware of the Bodhi Banquet, but what's the deal with the thirty-six spots that you mentioned?" Han Li asked.

"The Bodhi Banquet is the most highly anticipated event of the Heavenly Court, and countless people wish to be in attendance, but only those who are granted spots by the Heavenly Court are entitled to attend. Prior to the commencement of each edition of the Bodhi Banquet, the Heavenly Court releases spots to all of the major immortal regions for the powers within those immortal regions to compete for.

“Our greater Golden Origin Immortal Region has been presented with thirty-six spots, and all of the noteworthy powers of the immortal region will be gathering in Nine Origins City to compete for those spots," the shopkeeper explained.

"I see. When will the immortal envoys be arriving in Nine Origins City?" Han Li asked.

"There's no exact date stipulated, but it should be soon," the shopkeeper replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then asked a few more related questions before dismissing the shopkeeper.

After that, he made his way into the inner room of the courtyard and habitually set up several layers of restrictions before sitting down with a contemplative look on his face.

Wyrm 3 had asked him to arrive in Nine Origins City within thirty years, which coincided with the timing of the arrival of the Heavenly Court immortal envoys, so the Reincarnation Palace mission most likely had something to do with competing for the thirty-six spots.

After contemplating the matter for some time, Han Li shook his head to rid himself of the train of thought, then cast his gaze deep into the Nine Origins City.

Wait for me for just a little longer, Jin Tong.

Chapter 1215: Another Disciple

One morning, several months later.

The sun still hadn't yet risen over the city walls, yet the streets of Nine Origins City were already teeming with pedestrians.

In contrast with the high-pace lifestyle normally on display in the city, all of the pedestrians on this day were looking very lax and casual, either strolling around at a leisurely place or loitering and chatting with one another.

Many of them had expectant looks on their faces as they occasionally glanced up at the sky, seemingly waiting for something.

In the crowd was a handsome, white-robed young man who was slowly making his way deeper into the city while eavesdropping on the conversations taking place around him.

The young man was none other than Han Li, having adopted a disguise with his newly acquired black mask.

"I heard that the immortal envoys from the Middle Earth Immortal Region are a huge deal. Not only do they have countless servants with them, even the palace master of our Golden Origin Immortal Palace is personally accompanying them," a brown-robed elderly man said.

"They're immortal envoys from the Heavenly Court, so of course they're treated with the utmost respect. Otherwise, there's no way they would've been personally welcomed by Daoist Master Chun Jun of our Nine Origins Temple. Besides, they've come here to present Bodhi Tokens, which are highly sought after even among Great Encompassment cultivators, so of course everyone's sucking up to them!" a middle-aged man in a brocade robe said.

"What I wouldn't give for a Bodhi Token," someone else sighed in an envious manner.

Han Li continued onward without pause, listening to all of the nearby conversations, but refraining from taking part in them himself.

Right at this moment, an excited voice rang out in the crowd.

"Here they come!"

A disturbance instantly swept over the entire street as everyone stopped talking and looked up into the sky.

Han Li also stopped in his tracks to look up into the heavens above the city gates, where a vast expanse of radiant, golden light had appeared, as if the sun were rising from that direction.

The golden light was bordered by a ring of rainbow light, and there were large, five-colored clouds converging in the sky even further away.

Everyone looked up until their necks were feeling a little stiff and their eyes were beginning to water from the golden radiance, but no one appeared.

Right as someone was about to complain, a layer of rainbow light suddenly appeared over the horizon, then approached the city before spreading over the city wall and spilling into the city.

An opening that was around a thousand feet wide appeared in the city's protective array to grant the rainbow light free passage, and it formed a wide path.

A series of five-colored lotus flower projections appeared over the path, giving off a fragrant aroma that spread over virtually the entire city.

The sound of thunderous rumbling then rang out as eight qilins clad in suits of golden armor came galloping over the path, dragging along an excessively massive chariot behind them.

The chariot resembled an extremely lavish and intricately constructed pavilion, and behind the chariot was an army of horseback warriors clad in suits of golden armor and immortal cultivators.

There were far fewer of them than the exaggerated rumors had suggested, but it was still certainly a very formidable army.

Standing behind the white jade railing at the front of the chariot was a tall man in heavenly official attire. His face was rather square in shape, and he had a pair of long and thin eyes, coupled with a tall nose and a pair of thin lips.

Han Li was not very fond of the arrogant look on the man's face, and he was just about to turn and depart when he noticed the two figures standing behind the man.

One of them was a man with an unremarkable physical appearance and a placid expression, someone that could easily be lost in a crowd. If it weren't for his Immortal Palace attire, it would've been very difficult to draw a connection between him and Lu Chuanfeng, the master of the greater Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

The woman standing beside him was far more eye-catching. Not only was she exceptionally beautiful, her breathtaking figure was highlighted by her vibrant, red dress, and she instantly became the center of attention.

Chi Meng?

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this.

Right at this moment, around a dozen figures descended onto the path of light.

Compared with the immortal envoys and their impressive entourage, these people were made to appear far less remarkable, but as soon as they appeared, the entire city instantly erupted into thunderous cheers.

The group of new arrivals was led by a male figure dressed in a dark green daoist robe with a lotus flower hat on his head. His facial features weren't spectacular, but his face was glowing with vitality and exuberance, and it was immediately apparent to Han Li that this was most likely the abbot of the Nine Origins Temple, Daoist Master Chun Jun.

Trailing along behind him were two more daoist priests, one of whom was quite thin, with high cheekbones and a goatee. His eyes were incredibly clear and bright, and even though he was wearing a very old and worn gray daoist robe, there was a special, profound aura about him.

The other man was quite burly in stature and appeared to be around forty years of age. He was wearing an extremely opulent purple daoist robe, and his head was unadorned with any daoist hats. His face was very chiseled and angular, and it was completely expressionless, giving him the appearance of a daoist deity statue.

Given how close they were standing to Daoist Master Chun Jun, it stood to reason that they were most likely the two assistant abbots of the Nine Origins Temple.

Han Li didn't know much about the two of them. All he knew was that the gray-robed elderly man's name was Yang Junzi, while the purple-robed man was referred to as Daoist Master Lei Jun.

The dozen or so people standing behind them all had respectful looks on their faces, and among them was a familiar face for Han Li, namely Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

At this point, Miao Fa had already caught sight of Chi Meng standing behind the immortal envoy, and the two of them were staring daggers at each other.

It was clear that they had developed a great deal of resentment toward each other during their failed attempt to capture Han Li.

"Welcome, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian," Daoist Master Chun Jun said in a warm voice, and the two men began to engage in some small talk.

......

Han Li immediately lost interest upon seeing this, and he made his back to the inn.

He had only just returned to his own courtyard when he noticed a tall young man and a young woman wearing a veiled bamboo hat standing at the entrance, seemingly waiting for him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the two figures, and he didn't say anything.

"You're not going to invite us in for some tea, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5?" the woman asked with a bright smile.

"You're Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?" Han Li asked.

"The immortal envoy of the Heavenly Court has already arrived, so it's time for me to divulge to you the contents of the mission," the woman said.

"Alright, please come in," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air to open up the restriction at the entrance of the courtyard, and the three of them made their way inside before sitting down around a table.

Han Li noticed that the tall man had been staring directly at him ever since he entered the courtyard, and that he was making no attempt to hide his direct scrutiny.

"Who is this, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?" Han Li asked.

"He's one of the assistant palace masters of our Reincarnation Palace, Fellow Daoist Wu Yang," Wyrm 3 replied.

Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly upon hearing this name.

"It seems that you know of me," the young man said.

"I saw a portrait of you in the True Mantra Sect ruins, and I also heard about you from Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li explained.

"Hot Flame? Are you referring to that scoundrel's disciple?" Wu Yang asked as a hint of a fury appeared in his eyes.

"There's no need to harbor any animosity toward Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. He didn't betray the sect with Qi Mozi, and he's already met his demise in the Gray Realm," Han Li said.

Wu Yang's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "I heard from Jiuzhen that Qi Mozi almost died by your hands, is that right?"

Han Li had never heard the name Gan Jiuzhen, so he didn't know that it was Wyrm 3 that was being referred to here, and only after a brief hesitation did he make the connection, upon which he nodded as he replied, "I managed to defeat him thanks to some strokes of fortune, but unfortunately, I wasn't able to kill him."

"So you really are in possession of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, is that right?" Wu Yang suddenly asked, and the atmosphere in the room instantly became rather tense.

Han Li was silent for a moment, following which he replied, "Do you want it? If so, I can give it to you."

Wu Yang was rather taken aback to hear this, clearly not expecting Han Li to be so willing to part with the cultivation art.

"The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra belongs to the True Mantra Sect to begin with, and I can only be considered to be half a disciple to Patriarch Miro. You are the true heir to the True Mantra Sect, so returning the cultivation art to you would serve as repayment to Patriarch Miro for the instruction that he has provided me," Han Li said in a forthcoming manner.

A hint of guilt flashed through Wu Yang's eyes upon hearing this, and only after a long silence did he reply, "It's fine, I'll entrust the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to you. Make sure to keep it safe."

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and Wu Yang explained with a wry smile, "Aside from Qi Mozi, all of my other martial brothers have already perished to defend the sect, so the fact that I'm still alive means that I've already betrayed the sect. On top of that, I haven't even been able to kill Qi Mozi for betraying our master, so what right do I have to inherit the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra?"

Han Li wanted to try and convince Wu Yang to reconsider, but the latter raised a hand as he said in a firm manner, "I've already made up my mind, so there's no need to try and dissuade me."

"In that case, I'll hold onto the cultivation art for now, and I'll return it to you if you ever want to resurrect the True Mantra Sect," Han Li acquiesced.

Chapter 1216: New Mission

Wu Yang nodded in response with a hint of approval in his eyes, clearly very pleased with Han Li's handling of the situation.

"Alright, now that you two have had a chance to catch up, let's get down to business," Wyrm 3 said.

"Before that, tell me what information you have on Jin Tong," Han Li said.

"All I can tell you at the moment is that she's in no danger for now. We know exactly where she's being kept, and we'll tell you her whereabouts and provide the necessary assistance for you to rescue her once you've completed your mission," Wyrm 3 replied.

"So you're only going to reveal Jin Tong's location to me once I've completed my mission?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Han, we're not trying to coerce you. It's just that there's a very important step in your mission that has to be completed by you before we can initiate our followup plan, and only then will you have a chance to save Jin Tong," Wyrm 3 explained.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "What's my mission?"

"The token-bearing immortal envoy of the Heavenly Court has already arrived in Nine Origins City, so I'm sure the selection event is about to commence soon. We want you to take part in the event and strive to obtain a Bodhi Token," Wyrn 3 replied.

"What is the selection process going to be like?" Han Li asked.

"There have been a total of hundred Bodhi Tokens assigned to the entire greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, most of which will be taken by the Nine Origins Temple, the Hundred Creations Mountain, the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, and the Sun Moon Alliance.

“The remaining dozen or two will be fought over by all of the other sects in the immortal region, and you have to come out on top in a series of battles among the competitors to claim a token," Wu Yang explained.

"The main obstacle that you'll have to overcome is claiming a Bodhi Token while keeping your identity secret," Wyrm 3 added.

"How is that possible? There are many people here who already know of me. Just now, I saw Chi Meng and Immortal Lord Miao Fa. If I participate in this selection event, they'll be sure to recognize me, and I'll have most likely met my demise before I even get a chance to worry about Jin Tong," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, that's precisely why I gave you that black mask," Wyrm 3 said.

"How is that going to help? The mask can conceal my aura and appearance, but there's no way my abilities won't be recognized in battle," Han Li said in a puzzled manner.

"If you think that's all that the mask can do, then you're severely underestimating it. The mask can be used to absorb the immortal spiritual power and aura of others to mask your own, so as long as you don't use your time law powers, even a late-Great Encompassment cultivator may not be able to see through your disguise," Wyrm 3 said.

"Even so, I'm not from the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, so surely I won't be entitled to participate in the event," Han Li countered.

"You don't have to worry about that. We've already assigned a cover for you, and you'll be taking part in the event on behalf of an elder from the Prominent Mountain Sect," Wu Yang said.

Han Li had heard of the Prominent Mountain Sect before. It was one of the few medium-sized sects in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region to have not joined the Sun Moon Alliance, but there had never been any signs suggesting that it was affiliated with the Reincarnation Palace.

"Does that mean that the Prominent Mountain Sect is a secret subsidiary sect of the Reincarnation Palace?" Han Li asked.

"You can say that. However, very few people are aware of this, even in the Prominent Mountain Sect itself. Their sect master, Zhou Xianyang, will be personally leading the team that is to take part in the selection event, and they've already arrived in the city. All you need to do is go and find him while wearing this token, and he'll know what to do," Wyrm 3 said as she pulled out a white jade pendant before offering it to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the pendant as he asked, "What exactly is the objective for this mission?"

"That's not something for you to worry about, Fellow Daoist Han, just complete your part of the mission, and we'll tell you everything when the time comes," Wyrm 3 replied.

Han Li was silent for a long while upon hearing this, and in the end, he could only agree with this arrangement.

After that, Wyrm 3 notified him of some things that he had to take note of in Nine Origins City, then departed with Wu Yang.

As he turned to depart, Wu Yang suddenly said, "You are the only one to have inherited the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra from our patriarch, and you were also able to strike down Qi Mozi where I couldn't, so you can already be considered a member of our True Mantra Sect. As your senior martial brother, it's only right that I present you with a gift."

He swept a sleeve through the air to send a golden inkstone flying toward Han Li, then vanished from the spot with Wyrm 3 before Han Li had a chance to say anything.

Han Li caught the golden inkstone, then inspected it closely to discover that there was an ox engraved onto it. The ox was resting in a prone position with its eyes closed, and it was extremely lifelike.

He injected some immortal spiritual power into the inkstone, and it immediately began giving off bursts of formidable earth law power fluctuations, indicating that it was at least a fifth tier immortal treasure.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up at this discovery, and after examining the inkstone for a while longer to ensure that there was nothing amiss about it, he stowed it away into his storage bracelet.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, then stepped into the Flower Branch domain through it.

He made his way into a room on the second floor of the bamboo pavilion, where Weeping Soul was seated on the bed with her legs crossed and her eyes, looking rather pale.

Lan Yan was standing by the window, and she immediately approached Han Li as she extended a curtsey and greeted, "Fellow Daoist Han."

"How is everything going?" Han Li asked.

"The soul planting ritual went very smoothly, and my brother's soul has already been planted into a dream flower, so all that's left is for it to rest and recuperate. It's just that Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul has been exhausted by the ordeal," Lan Yan replied with a guilty look on her face.

Han Li took a glance at Weeping Soul, following which his gaze fell upon a black pot on a table in the room.

The pot was filled with loamy, dark red soil, protruding out of which was the stem of a strange flower with seven black leaves growing upon it. At the tip of the stem was a fist-sized white bud that was flashing incessantly with silver light, and Han Li was able to detect Lan Yuanzi's aura within it.

"If you need any help, feel free to tell me," Han Li said.

"I couldn't possibly ask for more from you and Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul. All I hope is that I can somehow repay you in the future," Lan Yan hurriedly replied.

Han Li offered her some comforting words to help put her mind at ease, then departed from the Flower Branch domain.

......

The western region of Nine Origins City was where several rivers that passed through the city met. The terrain here was flat and open, and due to the presence of multiple bodies of water, the greenery here was very lush, presenting some stunning natural scenery.

Many medium-sized sects of the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region had paid exorbitant prices to purchase plots of land here as branches for their sects, and the Prominent Mountain Sect was no exception.

As one of the most powerful medium-sized sects of the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, it had purchased a highly sought after plot of land near the point where multiple rivers converged, and a large branch for the sect had been constructed on that plot of land.

On this day, a handsome, white-robed young man arrived at the entrance of the branch.

The gatekeeper was unable to glean the young man's cultivation base, so he immediately reported the man's arrival to the higher-ups of the sect.

Before long, an beige-robed elderly man with a long beard emerged from within.

The gatekeeper had made it sound like some important figure had come to visit, but upon arriving at the entrance of the branch, the elderly man discovered that the visitor was only at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, and he was not very pleased.

However, he maintained a placid facade as he said, "I heard that you've come to see our sect master. Unfortunately, he's not in the branch right now, but I'm happy to pass on a message to him from you once he returns."

The young man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he brought out a white jade pendant as he said, "I have nothing to say to you. Get your sect master to come and see me."

The young man was naturally none other than Han Li.

A hint of fury flashed through the elderly man's eyes upon hearing this.

"Are you of the opinion that my cultivation base is too low for me to be worthy of an audience with your sect master?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Before the elderly man had a chance to reply, his aura instantly swelled to the mid-High Zenith Stage, and a stunned look appeared on the elderly man's face upon seeing this.

Almost everyone could suppress their aura, but to be able to do it as seamlessly as Han Li was far from an easy feat.

With that in mind, the elderly man hurriedly cupped his fist in a salute and apologized, "Please forgive me, Senior, I'll report your arrival to our sect master right away."

At the same time, he was notifying everyone in the branch to make preparations in case Han Li had come here with less than friendly intentions.

"Rest assured, I have no ill intentions. I have some matters to discuss with your sect master, and I know he's here right now. Take this token with you, and he'll come out to meet me when he sees it," Han Li said as he handed the jade pendant to the elderly man.

"Please wait here for a moment, Senior," the elderly man said in a respectful manner as he accepted the token, then rushed back into the courtyard.

Shortly thereafter, a streak of white light flew out of the courtyard, and an extremely physically imposing man with a warm smile on his face emerged before greeting Han Li in a booming voice that caused the entire courtyard to tremble slightly.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Han!"

Chapter 1217: Perfect Match

The man had a square face with a set of rather rough features, and his aura indicated that he was a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator.

He was greeting Han Li like an old friend, but Han Li had never met him before.

However, he then quickly caught onto what the man was doing, and he put on a warm smile of his own as he greeted, "Indeed, Fellow Daoist Zhou, it's been far too long."

The two of them began to engage in some small talk, while the elderly man standing beside them heaved an internal sigh of relief, thanking the heavens that he hadn't displayed any disrespect to Han Li for the lowly cultivation base that he had initially displayed.

Zhou Xianyang and Han Li made their way into the inner hall of the branch together, and the former instructed, "Elder Zhu, go and prepare a feast. Bring out that jar of Azure Haze Jade Elixir that I've been saving for a special occasion."

The elderly man immediately departed to carry out his bidding, following which Zhou Xianyang invited Han Li into the room before sweeping a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light.

Both of them remained silent as they stepped through the door of light into a secret chamber, where Zhou Xianyang explained, "My apologies, Senior Han. Elder Zhu is a mole planted by my side by the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, so I had to put on an act for him."

"It sounds like things aren't easy for you, Sect Master Zhou," Han Li said with an amused smile.

"It's not as bad as it sounds. Elder Zhu has some street smarts, but he's not the most difficult to deal with, so I haven't been in any peril. The higher-ups are going to make a big move on this occasion, and I've already prepared everything on my end," Zhou Xianyang replied.

"Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 hasn't told me much at all. All she said was for me to come here and follow your lead," Han Li said.

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Han," Zhou Xianyang chuckled. "That's not what she told me. She explicitly told me to follow your lead and provide you with any assistance that you require."

"I'm not being modest, I truly don't know much about this mission, so I'll have to trouble you to give me some details," Han Li said.

"The Bodhi Banquet is held by the Heavenly Court roughly once every five million years, but in the past, only those who receive invitations have the right to attend the banquet. This is the first time that spots have been given with no restrictions placed on who gets to attend," Zhou Xianyang said.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know, but it's definitely not a bad thing for our Reincarnation Palace. The greater Golden Origin Immortal Region has received a hundred spots in total, most of which were taken by the Nine Origins Temple and the Hundred Creations Mountain, while some were also taken by the Golden Origin Immortal Palace and the Sun Moon Alliance, leaving only twelve spots, out of which we must claim one," Zhou Xianyang replied.

"Which sects are participating in the selection event? Are there any that I should look out for?" Han Li asked.

"The Sun Moon Alliance presides over almost all of the small and medium-sized sects of the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, and their spots have already been distributed. These twelve spots will be contested by the medium-sized sects that haven't joined the Sun Moon Alliance, so that eliminates most of the competition, but there will still be ninety-six sects in participation," Zhou Xianyang replied.

"It'll take at least three rounds of battles to select twelve out of ninety-six entrants, and given the prestige of the Bodhi Banquet, I presume all of the participating sects will be sending their most powerful cultivators, right?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"That's right. The good thing is that the patriarchs and leaders of the sects most likely won't take part in such events as it's unbefitting figures of their status. Having said that, there's a chance that some sect leaders could be willing to lay down their pride and participate in the event in person," Zhou Xianyang replied.

"The fact that you're saying that means that you think some people will actually stoop to that, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The leader of the sworn enemy of our Prominent Mountain Sect, the Lone Sun Peak, is a man by the name of Sikong Jian. He's a very sly and shady individual, and he's willing to stoop to anything to get what he wants. One time, he killed an extremely promising young talent from our sect, and ever since then, he's been hiding on the Lone Sun Peak like a cowardly turtle.

“We've hunted down hundreds of disciples of his sect to try and goad him into coming out, but he remains as cowardly as ever," Zhou Xianyang said in a resentful manner.

"What's his cultivation base?" Han Li asked.

"In the past, Sikong Jian was at the early-Great Encompassment Stage, but he's been in seclusion for a very long time, and I don't know if he's been able to sever a corpse soul during that time. However, even at the early-Great Encompassment Stage, he displayed more power than those of the same cultivation rank, so he's not to be taken lightly. Of course, the ideal situation would be for you to not encounter him at all," Zhou Xianyang replied.

"There's no guarantee that I'll have an easy draw, so I'll have to trouble you to provide me with some detailed profiles of the most powerful cultivators that I could go up against, just so I can be prepared for anything," Han Li said.

"There's Luo Yuanshan of the Azure Remorse Forest, Zhao Bolao of Boundless Mountain, Celestial Maiden Ziluo of Serene Celestial Lake..."

Zhou Xianyang rattled off a list of around a dozen names before concluding, "There's a very good chance that all of them will be representing their sects in the selection event, and I'll compile detailed profiles on all of them for you."

"That would be best," Han Li replied with a smile.

"For this event, you'll be participating under the guise of my junior martial brother, Chang Qi. He's constantly traveling, so barely anyone in our sect has seen him before. The only problem is that this junior martial brother of mine is a Profound Cultivator, so he hasn't really even used the cultivation arts of our sect.

“He was able to reach the late-High Zenith Stage purely thanks to his bodily refinement cultivation, so if you take part in the event in his stead, then I'm afraid you won't be able to use any of your abilities," Zhou Xianyang said in a concerned manner.

"That suits me just fine," Han Li replied with a smile, and he finally understood why Wyrm 3 had told him to come here.

Zhou Xianyang raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and he asked, "Could it be that you're also a Profound Immortal, Fellow Daoist Han?"

In response, Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and over nine hundred profound acupoints lit up over his body, illuminating the entire secret chamber.

"That's incredible! Even Junior Martial Brother Chang Qi doesn't hold a candle to your physical prowess!" Zhou Xianyang exclaimed in an astonished manner.

Unbeknownst to him, Han Li had held back significantly in order to not startle him.

"In that case, this should be a perfect arrangement," Zhou Xianyang continued with a pleased expression. "You can come out now, Junior Martial Brother Chang Qi."

A thin and frail-looking young man stepped into the secret chamber from a hidden entrance, and his physical appearance didn't fit the bill for a Profound Immortal at all.

The young man strode over to Han Li and Zhou Xianyang before cupping his fist in a greeting.

"Very impressive, Fellow Daoist Chang. I can see that you've progressed so far in your physical cultivation that your power has become contained within your bones," Han Li remarked as he returned the greeting.

Chang Qi's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and he replied, "The fact that you were able to see through me right away indicates that there's still more work for me to do."

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Chang," Han Li said with a smile.

"There's still over a month left until the selection event. During this month, you have to do your best to familiarize yourself with the characteristics of my junior martial brother's cultivation arts. Even if you can't perfectly replicate all of the fine details, your disguise has to at least be convincing enough to fool everyone. You know how to use the Reincarnation Palace mask, right?" Zhou Xianyang asked.

"Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 has already taught me," Han Li replied with a nod.

"In that case, let's begin right away," Zhou Xianyang said, and Han Li turned his gaze to Chang Qi before giving him a nod.

Immediately thereafter, the black mask on his face was revealed at his behest, and a layer of dense and viscous black mist surged out of it, then flowed down his body to completely envelop him.

After spilling down onto the ground, the black mist began to make its way toward Chang Qi as if it were a living creature.

Chang Qi's hands were clasped behind his back, and he was looking a little tense and apprehensive, but he remained completely still.

More and more black mist accumulated at his feet before spreading upward to envelop his entire body as well.

Han Li and Chang Qi were connected by a bridge of black mist, which was absorbing the latter's aura before transferring into the body of the former.

A hint of anticipation appeared in Zhou Xianyang's eyes as he observed the process.

A few minutes later, the black mist around Chang Qi faded away, receding until it was only enveloping Han Li, whose body rapidly shrank down until he was the same stature as Chang Qi.

Immediately thereafter, all of the black mist flowed back into his black mask, which took on an appearance that was identical to Chang Qi's.

Zhou Xianyang's eyes lit up as he began inspecting the two Chang Qis, upon which he discovered that even to him, both of them were completely indistinguishable in appearance and aura.

Due to the fact that much of the true Chang Qi's immortal spiritual power had been absorbed by Han Li's black mask, his aura was wavering in a rather unsteady fashion, so he appeared more like the counterfeit than Han Li did.

Chapter 1218: Imminent

"As expected of a Reincarnation Palace mask of the highest caliber, even I can't tell you apart from myself," Chang Qi praised.

"Brilliant! I'm sure this disguise will be convincing enough to fool even the elders of our sect!" Zhou Xianyang exclaimed in an exultant manner.

"Fellow Daoist Chang, I'm going to need you to tell me about the characteristics of your cultivation arts," Han Li said.

Han Li was already very well-versed in posing as others from past experience, so he was already beginning to mimic Chang Qi's expressions and mannerisms. This made his disguise even more convincing, much to the delight of Zhou Xianyang and Chang Qi.

"I'll leave you two to chat here, I'll go gather some information on the other cultivators taking part in the selection event," Zhou Xianyang said before departing, leaving Han Li and Chang Qi on their own in the secret chamber.

......

A month flew by in a flash.

This morning, almost the entire population of Nine Origins City had gathered at the foot of Nine Origins Mountain, leaving the rest of the city virtually completely deserted.

The selection event for the Bodhi Banquet was set to commence on Nine Origins Mountain on this day, and Han Li had already adopted his disguise as Chang Qi and arrived with Zhou Xianyang and several Prominent Mountain Sect elders.

Even though Chang Qi was always traveling outside the sect, there were still a few acquaintances of his among the elders of the sect who approached him to strike up conversations, but Han Li was able to navigate these conversations in a confident and appropriate manner, with no one suspecting anything amiss.

The group arrived at the foot of Nine Origins Mountain, where they were greeted by the sight of a giant mountain range in the distance.

The mountain range was incredibly lush, and large sections of it were concealed by the clouds above.

There were rays of light that were flashing faintly within the clouds, indicating the presence of a protective array.

The mountain that the entrance of the Nine Origins Temple was standing upon was extremely abundant with the world's origin qi, and in front of the temple's entrance was a massive plaza that was several hundred kilometers in size.

The plaza was split up into many sections, within which stood elevated platforms that were raised roughly ten feet above the ground.

There was an array around the plaza that separated it from the area outside, and at this moment, there were already countless eager spectators gathered outside the array.

Han Li's group had already been led to the entrance of the temple through a designated passageway by a disciple of the Nine Origins Temple, and they were standing on a huge, semi-circular stone platform.

A massive, three-story, dodecahedral archway was standing at the entrance of the temple, and it looked as if it had been carved out of a single, enormous piece of spirit jade.

Hanging above the archway was a white jade plaque, upon which were inscribed the words "Nine Origins Paradise" in antiquated golden seal text.

Han Li cast his gaze through the archway to find a winding stone staircase that led up the mountain into a vast expanse of hazy mist, beyond which nothing could be seen.

There were already some rows of chairs laid out on the semi-circular stone platform, which were directly facing the dozen or so platforms up ahead.

The Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators were led by the Nine Origins Temple disciple to a chair slightly to the left of the center, and Zhou Xianyang exchanged some greetings with a few sect leaders that he was familiar with, then sat down onto the chair, while everyone else remained standing behind him.

An elderly man who was seated right next to Zhou Xianyang turned to him and asked, "I heard that Elder Chang Qi has returned to your sect and will be taking part in the selection event. May I ask which one he is?"

Thanks to the profiles compiled by Zhou Xianyang, Han Li was able to identify the elderly man as the master of Boundless Mountain, Zhao Yuanlai.

The representative for Boundless Mountain was a junior clansman of his by the name of Zhao Bolao, who was a late-High Zenith cultivator with mastery over the laws of ice, and he was quite formidable in battle.

"Junior Martial Brother Chang, come and pay your respects to Mountain Master Zhao," Zhou Xianyang said with a smile.

Han Li stepped forward as instructed, then cupped his fist in a salute toward Zhao Yuanlai as he greeted, "Chang Qi pays his respects to Mountain Master Zhao."

Zhao Yuanlai took a glance at Han Li, then turned to a white-robed young man behind him, and the two of them seemed to have been engaging in a conversation through voice transmission.

Han Li knew that the young man was none other than Zhao Bolao, and the two of them exchanged a glance and a nod.

"Fellow Daoist Chang looks to have a very good head on his shoulders. As expected of your secret trump card, Sect Leader Zhou. It looks like you're determined to secure a Bodhi Token for your Prominent Mountain Sect," Zhao Yuanlai praised.

Even though he was putting on a very convincing act, Han Li could tell that Zhao Yuanlai had already written him off as someone who posed no threat to Zhao Bolao.

Zhou Xianyang had made the same observation, and he couldn't help but feel rather amused. If Zhao Bolao were to be matched up against "Chang Qi", then the former was going to be in for a nasty surprise.

While Zhou Xianyang and Zhao Yuanlai were conversing with one another, a handsome and refined azure-robed man arrived on the stone platform with several beautiful women before making his way to another chair.

A look of resentment instantly appeared on Zhou Xianyang's face at the sight of the new arrival, and Zhao Yuanlai was clearly also less than happy to see him.

"Well, well, well, if it isn't the most shameless scoundrel in all of the Golden Origin Immortal Region," Zhao Yuanlai scoffed without making any effort to keep his voice down.

Han Li also cast his gaze toward Sikong Jian, who just so happened to also be glowering at Zhao Yuanlai through narrowed eyes, seemingly having heard his offensive remark.

He raised an eyebrow as he gave Zhao Yuanlai and Zhou Xianyang a provocative smile, then took a sip of tea out of the cup offered to him by one of the women by his side.

"Where are the disciples and elders of his Lone Sun Peak? Why has he only brought some maidservants with him?" Zhao Yuanlai asked in a perplexed manner.

"Is it not obvious enough? He's most likely planning to throw away what little dignity that he has to personally take part in the selection event," Zhou Xianyang replied in a completely unsurprised manner.

Zhao Yuanlai was rendered speechless upon hearing this.

It wasn't against the rules for a sect leader to personally participate in the event, but generally speaking, most sect leaders wouldn't do this. After all, if they were to suffer defeat at the hands of a junior, then they would be putting their entire sect to shame.

Right at this moment, a resounding bell chime suddenly rang out from within the Nine Origins Temple.

As the sound echoed throughout the mountain range, five figures appeared on the stone platform amid a flash of light.

All of the sect leaders seated on the stone platform instantly rose to their feet before extending respectful bows toward the five figures.

Han Li bowed along with everyone else, but at the same time, he was sizing up the five figures through his peripheral vision.

The five figures were led by none other than the token-bearing immortal envoy from the Middle Earth Immortal Region, and standing on either side of him were Daoist Master Chun Jun and the master of the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, Lu Chuanfeng.

The remaining two figures were unfamiliar to Han Li, but he had heard mention of them from Zhou Xianyang, so he was able to guess their identities.

The one on the left was a purple-robed elderly man with a large belly and a lethargic expression, and he was the leader of the Sun Moon Alliance, Immortal Lord Heavenly Star, while the one on the right was a tall and handsome young man by the name of Huo Yuan, also known as the current master of the Hundred Creations Mountain.

According to what Han Li had been told by Daoist Master Jingyang back in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, Huo Yuan was already the fifth mountain master of the Hundred Creations Mountain.

The arrival of these five figures was met with thunderous cheers across the entire plaza, and the waves of raucous cheers were only silenced when Daoist Chun Jun made a quieting gesture.

After everyone had taken a seat, Daoist Chun Jun turned to all of the spectators gathered on the plaza as he declared, "In light of the upcoming Bodhi Banquet, the Heavenly Court, in its infinite generosity, has bestowed upon the sects of our Golden Origin Immortal Region twelve Bodhi Tokens, granting twelve fellow daoists the opportunity to attend the banquet and sample the Bodhi Dao Fruit."

Everyone instantly erupted into thunderous cheers once again, as if each of them had also been granted a Bodhi Token.

The Heavenly Court envoy seemed to have been quite pleased with this reaction, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

Everyone else on the stone platform also had smiles on their faces, with the exception of Immortal Lord Heavenly Star, who had dozed off for a nap.

A Nine Origins Temple elder responsible for overseeing the competition stepped forward as he declared, "Our Golden Origin Immortal Region is home to a vast number of sects, but there are only twelve Bodhi Tokens to go around, so not everyone will be able to leave with one. All of the sects have already elected their representatives, so I'll now ask the representatives to step forward to draw lots for the first round."

Han Li exchanged a glance with Zhou Xianyang, then stepped forward alongside Zhao Bolao.

All of the elected cultivators of the other sects stepped forward as well.

Chapter 1219: First Battle

Han Li swept his gaze over the platform to discover that all of the noteworthy names that Zhou Xianyang had mentioned were present, including the likes of Luo Yuanshan of the Azure Remorse Forest, Celestial Maiden Ziluo, and of course, Sikong Jian of the Lone Sun Peak.

The spectators on the plaza were clearly also not fans of this course of action, and a chorus of boos rang out across the plaza.

Sikong Jian remained completely unfazed, and despite all the boos that were ringing out, everyone also couldn't help but be a little envious of his shamelessness. After all, if he could successfully obtain a Bodhi Token, then his shamelessness would be completely vindicated.

Overall, this was not a bad gamble to make for Sikong Jian.

"Sect Leader Zhou, if Fellow Daoist Chang manages to draw Sikong Jian, then he'd better make sure to come out on top. That way, not only will the Lone Sun Peak's reputation be razed to the ground, you'll also be able to give him some well-deserved payback," Zhao Yuanlai said with a smile.

"We can't count on such coincidences," Zhou Xianyang replied with a smile, and while defeating Sikong Jian would certainly be a very sweet victory, he was still hoping that Han Li wouldn't have to face him in battle.

After all, as a sect leader, Sikong Jian was going to be more powerful than most, if not all of the other competitors, and he was renowned for his insidious and devious character, so everyone else was naturally hoping not to have to face.

"I have here ninety-six numbered balls. Each of you will pick one, and the number you pick will be assigned to you. Number one will face number ninety-six, number two will face number ninety-five, and so on. Understood?" the officiating elder asked.

"Understood," all of the competitors answered in unison.

"Begin," the elder declared as he tossed the ninety-six numbered balls up into the air, and they began to glow like radiant stars as they hung above everyone's heads.

All of the competitors swept a sleeve through the air to each draw a ball into their grasp, and after claiming a ball for himself, Han Li injected a wisp of immortal spiritual power into it, upon which the number "ninety-one" was revealed.

Everyone else soon unveiled their numbers as well, and given that Sikong Jian was a hot favorite in the event, many people immediately turned to him to examine his number.

In the face of everyone's scrutiny, Sikong Jian made no effort to hide his own number, raising the ball in his hand up high to reveal the number "ninety" emblazoned upon it.

A loud groan rang out in the crowd, and everyone turned to discover a green-skinned man with a horn on his head, looking at Sikong Jian with utter despair.

Everyone else heaved a collective sigh of relief while also feeling rather sympathetic of Sikong Jian's unfortunate opponent.

"What's your number, Fellow Daoist Chang?" Zhao Bolao asked with a smile.

Han Li showed him the ball in his hand, and Zhao Bolao's expression instantly stiffened as he raised his own ball, which was marked with the number "six".

"Fate truly is a cruel mistress," Zhao Bolao said with a wry smile, but he was struggling to hide the elation in his eyes.

He and Zhao Yuanlai had already completely written off "Chang Qi" as a doormat that Zhao Bolao could walk over as he pleased, so he was naturally ecstatic with this pairing.

"Please take it easy on me, Brother Bolao," Han Li implored, putting his acting skills on full display as he injected just the right amount of disappointment and unease into his voice.

Zhao Bolao's confidence was bolstered even further upon hearing this, but he still put on a modest facade as he replied, "Likewise, Fellow Daoist Chang."

"Fellow daoists with the first and last twelve numbers, please step onto the twelve platforms for your matches."

Han Li and Zhao Bolao just so happened to be among the first batch of combatants, and in accordance with the assigned numbers, their battle was set to take place on the sixth platform.

Sikong Jian had taken his position on the seventh platform, which was no more than a thousand feet away.

The spectators erupted into thunderous cheers as the first batch of twenty-four combatants stepped onto their respective platforms.

Before Zhou Xianyang and Zhao Yuanlai even had a chance to celebrate the fact that neither Han Li nor Zhao Bolao had drawn Sikong Jian as their opponent, they saw the two of them appearing on the same platform.

"What a coincidence," Zhao Yuanlai and Zhou Xianyang exclaimed in unison, and there was a hint of schadenfreude in both of their voices.

"Sect Leader Zhou, our two sects have always been on very good terms with one another, so regardless of the outcome of this battle, let's make sure that we don't take it personally," Zhao Yuanlai said with a smile, clearly of the opinion that the outcome of the battle was already a foregone conclusion.

"Of course," Zhou Xianyang replied with a smile of his own.

Even if the true Chang Qi were facing Zhao Bolao in Han Li's place, he would still have a great deal of confidence in his junior martial brother.

The group of figures seated at the center of the semi-circular stone platform weren't very interested in the battles taking place, and they were casually conversing with one another. There was a restriction around them that ensured that even the other people on the platform couldn't overhear their conversations, and of course, no one dared to try and eavesdrop on them.

"Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, I've heard that there's been a great deal of unrest all over the True Immortal Realm of late. Not only has the Reincarnation Palace been making frequent moves, even the Gray Realm has been very active recently. Do you know what's happening?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"Gray Realm beings have appeared in many parts of our True Immortal Realm, including the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and the Black Mountain Immortal Region, but it hasn't been a cause for alarm," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian replied in a nonchalant manner.

Daoist Master Chun Jun's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. The fact that the Heavenly Court was displaying this type of attitude was already a big problem in itself.

"Hasn't the Heavenly Court been constantly monitoring the Gray Realm? Has something happened in the Gray Realm to trigger this change?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian hesitated momentarily, then replied through voice transmission, "Something has indeed happened in the Gray Realm. The previously neutral Black Rope Region has allied itself with the Reincarnation Region, and under the collective pressure from the two regions, the Infernal Region has been forced to cut contact with our Heavenly Court. It seems like they must have reached a consensus, given that they're beginning to invade our True Immortal Realm."

Even though Daoist Master Chun Jun had already received some word of this, he still couldn't help but be taken aback by this personal admittance from Immortal Envoy Feng Tian.

Many years ago, the patriarch of the Nine Origins Temple had analyzed the future state of the True Immortal Realm, and his predictions were gradually beginning to materialize.

Right at this moment, another wave of thunderous cheers rang out as the officiating elder announced the commencement of the battles.

"Please pardon me, Brother Bolao," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Zhao Bolao.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Chang," Zhao Bolao replied as he returned the salute, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a white light barrier that encompassed the entire platform.

The light barrier was flashing incessantly while countless six-tipped snowflake designs roamed over its surface, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

"Your command over the laws of ice is truly remarkable, Brother Bolao," Han Li praised with a smile.

"I've never faced a Profound Immortal of your caliber, so this is an eye-opening experience for both of us," Zhao Bolao said he swept both sleeves through the air, and wisps of glacial qi rose up from the platform, while a layer of blue frost quickly spread over the ground underfoot.

Han Li stomped a foot heavily down onto the ground, sending a burst of white energy erupting in all directions, and the converging blue frost was instantly pulverized into dust.

Zhao Bolao remained unfazed as another wave of glacial qi rose up from the ground at his behest, and a series of ice spikes emerged from the platform, pointing up at the sky like a collection of sharp spears.

Several hundred profound acupoints lit up over Han Li's body as he sprang up into the air, and Zhao Bolao immediately set off after him in pursuit with a blue spear in his grasp, appearing behind Han Li in the blink of an eye before thrusting the spear toward the center of his back.

Han Li could easily evade the attack with his speed, but given that he was currently supposed to be Chang Qi, displaying excessive speed would arouse suspicions, so he lowered his own center of gravity, standing on a pair of ice spikes as he allowed the blue spear to strike his shoulder from behind.

Even though Zhao Bolao's attack had missed Han Li's vital regions, the former was very quick to adapt to the situation, releasing a rapid torrent of immortal spiritual power into his blue spear.

A burst of radiant, blue light instantly erupted out of the tip of the spear, culminating in a glacial, blue flame that froze Han Li's entire arm and half of his shoulder solid.

"My apologies, Fellow Daoist Chang," Zhao Bolao said, but he was unable to suppress a smile.

With a forceful flick of his spear, the ice that had encased Han Li's arm was instantly shattered, and Han Li felt a numb sensation run through his arm, but aside from that, he was completely unscathed.

Zhao Bolao had expected Han Li's arm to have been shattered along with the ice that it had been encased in, and he was stunned to discover that this was not the case.

"You may be unfamiliar with Profound Immortals like myself, Brother Bolao. Our bodies are our best weapons, so we're a lot hardier than the average cultivator," Han Li said with a warm smile as a series of profound acupoints lit up over his arm, following which he threw a punch at Zhao Bolao.

He was imitating Chang Qi by releasing his power from his bones, and his entire arm looked as if it had been basked in a layer of white starlight.

Chapter 1220: Pouncing on An Opportunity

Zhao Bolao hurriedly sprang back in retreat upon seeing this, and at the same time, he thrust his spear forward in a rapidfire fashion to unleash a barrage of spear projections.

The surrounding air temperature instantly plummeted as a flurry of snowflakes converged to form a frosty vortex that swept directly toward Han Li.

However, Han Li displayed no intention of stopping as he charged directly forward while plunging his glowing arm straight into the glacial vortex.

A loud thump rang out as the frosty vortex exploded, and Han Li passed straight through it.

Before Zhao Bolao had a chance to adopt any further defensive measures, Han Li's fist had already struck him on the chest, but it was as if his fist had struck a ball of cotton, and it passed straight through Zhao Bolao's chest.

In the next instant, a huge hole was blown into Zhao Bolao's chest, and large volumes of water came gushing out of it.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he attempted to withdraw his arm, but the water flowing out of Zhao Bolao's chest instantly enveloped his arm, clinging onto it to prevent him from extricating it.

Immediately thereafter, Zhao Bolao's entire body transformed into a transparent body of water, which wrapped itself around Han Li like a layer of glue to lock him firmly into place.

At the same time, another Zhao Bolao appeared elsewhere on the platform.

"So I've been fighting your domain spirit this entire time," Han Li remarked.

"Looks like this is the end for you, Fellow Daoist Chang," Zhao Bolao said as he swept both sleeves forcefully through the air, and countless blades formed by peerlessly sharp snowflakes came converging toward Han Li from the surrounding spirit domain.

The entire platform was instantly inundated by a dense snowstorm, making it impossible to see anything from the outside.

On the semi-circular stone platform, Zhou Xianyang was looking on with his brows tightly furrowed with concern, while Zhao Yuanlai had a triumphant look on his face, having already turned his attention to Sikong Jian's battle.

"Looks like this is it, Sect Leader Zhou. Like I said, I hope this doesn't sour the relationship between our two sects," Zhao Yuanlai said as he turned to Zhou Xianyang with an apologetic expression, but the elation in his eyes was clear to see.

As for Zhou Xianyang, he continued to look on with a perplexed expression.

Is that all he's got? Did Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 overstate his powers?

Right at this moment, a burst of blinding, white light erupted over the entirety of the sixth platform, forming a massive vortex of white light that exploded violently.

The glacial spirit domain on the platform also exploded, sending gusts of frosty air erupting in all directions.

The surrounding air temperature plummeted drastically, and some of the weaker spectators couldn't help but tremble as they hurriedly channeled their cultivation arts to protect themselves from the freezing cold.

After the dust settled, it was revealed that Zhao Bolao had already fallen to the ground in an unconscious state, while Han Li remained standing beside him.

However, his clothes were in tatters, his complexion was quite pale, and his lips had turned purple, indicating that the victory had not come easily for him.

Zhou Xianyang heaved an internal sigh of relief, then turned to Zhao Yuanlai to discover that the triumphant look on his face had been completely erased.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Zhao, let's not allow something like this to sour the relationship between our two sects," Zhou Xianyang said as he cupped his fist in a salute, and Zhao Yuanlai nodded in response with a steely expression.

Right as everyone was wondering how the battle on the sixth platform had been decided, the battle on the seventh platform also drew to a conclusion, with Sikong Jian's opponent kicked off the platform, having already sustained severe injuries.

Sikong Jian cast a provocative gaze toward Han Li from afar.

Even though Han Li appeared to have been in a rather sorry state, that was nothing more than an act, and to Sikong Jian's surprise, Han Li didn't back down in the slightest, directly meeting his provocative gaze with a cold one of his own.

Before long, all of the other battles had also concluded, and a new batch of twelve battles commenced.

Instead of returning to the semi-circular stone platform following the conclusion of his battle, Han Li returned straight to the Prominent Mountain Sect branch.

From there, he returned to the courtyard that he was staying in, then entered the Flower Branch domain.

Weeping Soul was still nurturing Lan Yuanzi's soul, while Qu Lin remained in the unconscious state imposed upon him by Weeping Soul.

The next day.

For the second round, Han Li's opponent was Elder Chu Zhong of the Dauntless Sect.

Chu Zhong was someone who very rarely left his sect, so there were very few occasions where he had displayed his powers in public, and as a result, the Prominent Mountain Sect was only able to gather very limited information on him.

All Han Li knew was that he was a cultivator of earth law powers, and that he was an early-Great Encompassment cultivator.

For this battle, Han Li was on the second platform, and he arrived a little earlier than his opponent.

Chu Zhong was an elderly man with a dark complexion with a head of white hair. He had a very unremarkable stature, one that was even slightly shorter than the average person, and his sleeves were rolled up to reveal a pair of dark and wiry forearms.

He was slightly hunched over with his arms hanging down in front of him, giving him the appearance of an old gibbon.

Despite his unremarkable appearance, there was a faint, golden gleam in his eyes, and Han Li knew not to take this opponent lightly.

Zhou Xianyang had taken his assigned seat on the semi-circular stone platform, and even though Boundless Mountain had already been eliminated, Zhao Yuanlai was also present. Just like on the previous day, the two of them were sitting together, and it seemed like the battle from the day before hadn't driven a wedge between them at all.

"Do you know Chu Zhong, Sect Leader Zhou?" Zhao Yuanlai asked.

"I do not. Our Prominent Mountain Sect hasn't had any prior interactions with the Dauntless Sect, and Chu Zhong very rarely makes any public appearances, so I've only ever heard of him, but never met him," Zhou Xianyang replied.

"I've met him on one past occasion, but it wasn't exactly a pleasant encounter. I can tell you that he's very troublesome to deal with. In fact, I'd even go as far as to say that he's going to be the fiercest competitor to Sikong Jian in this entire event," Zhao Yuanlai said.

Zhou Xianyang was rather amused to hear this. Only now did he realize that Zhao Yuanlai had come on this day purely to see Han Li lose.

"Looks like Junior Martial Brother Chang hasn't had the luck of the draw on his side. He's going to have to get a little serious against such a formidable opponent," Zhou Xianyang replied, implying that he had managed to defeat Zhao Bolao the day before without even taking their battle seriously.

Zhao Yuanlai was furious to hear this, and only after a long and steely silence did he manage to spit out the words: "I look forward to seeing Fellow Daoist Chang's performance."

He had asked Zhao Bolao the day before how the latter had been defeated by Chang Qi, and he had thought that Chang Qi had to have employed some type of hidden trump card or used some underhanded tactics.

However, even Zhao Bolao himself was unable to explain how he had been defeated. All he had said was that a burst of power far beyond what he was able to tolerate had suddenly erupted out of Chang Qi's body, following which he was knocked unconscious by a single punch.

Right at this moment, the battles commenced.

Han Li cupped his in a salute toward Chu Zhong, then seized the initiative, springing forward to arrive behind his opponent in the blink of an eye before throwing an almighty punch.

A hint of astonishment flashed through Zhao Yuanlai's eyes upon seeing this.

This level of speed and power was far beyond what Chang Qi had displayed the day before.

Chu Zhong also seemed to have been caught off guard by Han Li's sudden attack, and he remained completely rooted to the spot.

However, right as Han Li's fist was about to strike him on the back, a burst of black light suddenly rose from the ground, forming a black stone wall that separated him from Han Li while simultaneously rising up toward Han Li's arm.

The timing was exceptional, and Han Li was struck in the armpit by the rising stone wall before his fist had a chance to reach Chu Zhong, flinging him up into the air.

Before he had a chance to steady himself, Chu Zhong had already sprung up into the air in pursuit while throwing a punch at his back.

His fist was enveloped in a layer of black light that exploded violently upon making contact with Han Li's back, and a burst of tremendous power came crashing down upon Han Li from behind, sending him plummeting heavily down onto the platform below.

Even though the platform had been fortified using special arrays, Han Li's feet still plunged deep into the ground like a pair of steel blades, sending massive cracks running over the platform's surface.

Immediately thereafter, Chu Zhong came crashing down upon Han Li with mountainous force, and his legs were slightly bent, while his entire body was enveloped in a layer of that same peculiar black light.

Han Li felt as if the entire sky were falling upon him, and all of the space around him seemed to have solidified from the immense pressure crashing down from above, making it impossible for him to move and take evasive measures.

He let loose a thunderous roar as over nine hundred profound acupoints lit up over his body in unison, and he channeled his Titan Vajra Arts as he thrust both palms up toward the heavens.

A burst of white light erupted out of the palms of his hands, forming a barrier of starlight to oppose the descending Chu Zhong.

The black and white light clashed to result in a violent explosion, sending powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions.

All of the spectators were stunned by the tremendous impact of the collision, and they hurriedly focused their gaze on the second platform, only to discover that the pair of combatants had been completely concealed within the explosion of black and white light.

Chapter 1221: Fierce Battle

On the semi-circular stone platform, Zhao Yuanlai's mouth was slightly agape in astonishment, while Zhou Xianyang took an uneasy glance at the five figures at the center of the platform, fearing that Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others would be able to see through Han Li's disguise.

The attention of Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others had indeed been drawn to the second platform by the commotion from Han Li's battle, and Immortal Envoy Feng Tian praised, "Those two are both quite impressive."

Lu Chuanfeng nodded in agreement with a smile on his face, while Daoist Master Chun Jun chimed in in agreement, "One is a Profound Immortal, while the other has mastered the laws of gravity. This is going to be a fiery matchup."

Even the snoozing Immortal Lord Heavenly Star had opened his eyes up wide to stare at Han Li and Chu Zhong, pondering if he should recruit their sects into the Sun Moon Alliance.

On the second platform, the black and white light gradually subsided to reveal the two combatants, but all of a sudden, both of them transformed into a pair of blurs.

The surrounding spectators looked on in awe as their eyes rapidly darted back and forth, desperately trying to track Han Li and Chu Zhong.

All of a sudden, a loud thump rang out as Han Li sprang up into the air, then swooped down from above before throwing a punch downward.

A pillar of white light erupted out of his fist before crashing down upon Chu Zhong down below, while the latter hunched himself over even further before launching himself up into the air.

A strange symbol appeared on his forehead, following which a layer of metallic, black light emerged over its surface, and he rushed headfirst toward the descending pillar of light, making no effort to take any evasive measures.

A string of resounding booms rang out incessantly as hundreds of profound acupoints lit up over Chu Zhong's body, and only then did Han Li come to realize that his opponent was also a Profound Immortal.

The pillar of white light between the two of them was rapidly shrinking, as was the distance between them, and it didn't take long before a fierce clash ensued.

The surrounding world's origin qi trembled violently as the combatants collided before separating again, sending an enormous cloud of dust rising up into the air.

Before the dust had a chance to settle, a black light barrier emerged to encompass the entire platform, and a black mountain that looked as if it had come straight out of an ink wash painting appeared high up in the sky.

Rays of black light began to cascade down upon the entire platform, and all of a sudden, the entire space had become incredibly heavy.

The dust that was still lingering in the air was instantly forced back down to the ground by the increased gravitational force, while Han Li also stumbled involuntarily under the immense pressure.

The section of the stone platform beneath his feet was instantly shattered and reduced to a pile of rubble, and a hint of schadenfreude appeared in Zhao Yuanlai's eyes upon seeing this as he remarked, "Not only is Chu Zhong a powerful Profound Immortal in his own right, he's also attained a formidable Creation Tier spirit domain. Looks like this is truly the end of the road for Fellow Daoist Chang."

"Let's not jump to premature conclusions, Mountain Master Zhao," Zhou Xianyang said.

He wasn't aware of the extent of Han Li's powers, but he knew that the latter was certainly no slouch. However, he was severely handicapped by the fact that he had to keep his own identity a secret, so there was definitely a chance that Chu Zhong could be too formidable an opponent for him to overcome.

At this point, the other battles were also beginning to reach their climaxes, eliciting a chorus of thunderous cheers from the spectators on the plaza, but the majority of the spectators still had their attention fixed on the second platform.

Han Li attempted to raise a leg, but the surrounding gravitational force had been increased by at least a hundredfold, making even such a small gesture incredibly difficult.

"Fellow Daoist Chang, you'll stand no chance against me if you don't also release your spirit domain," Chu Zhong declared as he hovered in mid-air with his arms hanging down in front of him.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Chu. I'm not trying to show off or anything, it's just that I've been solely dedicated to the cultivation of my body and have never dabbled with spirit domains," Han Li said.

"In that case, I suggest you surrender before you get hurt," Chu Zhong said as he made a hand seal before thrusting his palms downward, and the ink wash mountain in the sky instantly descended by over a hundred feet.

The surrounding gravitational force was instantly enhanced by at least another tenfold, and even with his tremendous physical constitution, Han Li was beginning to feel immense physical strain.

His joints were creaking and groaning audibly, and in a display of defiance, he let loose a loud roar as he clenched his fists tightly.

Over nine hundred profound acupoints lit up over his body in rapid succession, and his True Extreme Film also began to glow radiantly, releasing a burst of starpower to force back the surrounding rays of black light, forming what was akin to a miniature spirit domain around him.

Immediately thereafter, bursts of formidable starpower erupted out of the profound acupoints on his legs, propelling him up into the heavens toward Chu Zhong.

The propulsion force erupting out of the profound acupoints on his legs was nothing to scoff at, but his speed was severely limited by Chu Zhong's gravitational law powers, slowing him down to a crawl.

"You're still not going to give up?" Chu Zhong scoffed as he swooped down from above while making a rapid string of hand seals, and the ink wash mountain behind him instantly began to tremble violently as an avalanche of giant, black rocks came tumbling down from it.

The torrential barrage of black rocks came crashing down upon Han Li, but not only was he not forced back down by the ferocious barrage, he was pulverizing all of the oncoming rocks with his fists as he continued to force his way upward like a radiant, white arrow.

A resounding boom rang out as another giant, black rock was smashed to bits, only to reveal Chu Zhong behind it.

Chu Zhong raised a fist, and rays of black light surged out of the profound acupoints on his arm, following which he threw a punch at Han Li's chest with such incredible power that spatial rifts were opening up in the space beneath his fist.

Han Li was caught completely off guard and could only cross his arms to form a protective barrier in front of himself.

Right as Chu Zhong's fist struck his crossed arms, he channeled his Xuanwu bloodline, and a series of black, turtle-shell-like patterns appeared over his arms.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as Han Li was sent crashing down from above like a meteorite, crashing through countless black rocks before plummeting to the ground.

The platform below had already been reduced to ruins, and a massive crater that was over a thousand feet deep was instantly smashed into the ground beneath it, sending massive cracks spreading through the other nearby platforms.

Several Nine Origins Temple cultivators instantly flew onto the scene to prevent the eruption of power from spreading any further so that it didn't interfere with the other battles.

A chorus of loud cheers rang out as the riveting battle sent a wave of excitement sweeping through the crowd of spectators.

On the semi-circular stone platform, Zhou Xianyang was peering into the crater with an anxious expression.

"Do you still think I was jumping to a premature conclusion now, Sect Leader Zhou?" Zhao Yuanlai chuckled.

At the center of the platform, Lu Chuanfeng's brows were furrowed slightly in befuddlement as he asked, "Did any of you notice that the elder from the Prominent Mountain Sect seems to possess the bloodline of the true spirit Xuanwu in his body?"

"It doesn't seem to be very pure. Otherwise, he would've been able to withstand that attack," Immortal Lord Heavenly Star remarked in a wistful manner, while Daoist Master Chun Jun nodded in agreement.

As for Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, his attention had already drifted to other platforms.

In his eyes, the battle on the second platform had already been decided, so it required no further attention.

Right as he looked away to direct his gaze elsewhere, the ink wash mountain in the sky abruptly shrank down before plummeting rapidly from above, plunging straight into the giant crater down below.

The entire platform shuddered violently before falling still again, and Chu Zhong was standing atop the mountain summit in a victorious manner.

The spectators erupted into thunderous cheers once again, while the officiating elder from the Nine Origins Temple flew up into the air in preparation to announce Chu Zhong's victory.

However, right at this moment, the ink wash mountain that had sunken into the ground abruptly shuddered violently, and a burst of dazzling, white light spilled out from beneath it to illuminate the entire heavens.

Immediately thereafter, the entire plaza began to tremble, and the ink wash mountain slowly rose up bit by bit.

Everyone looked on with stunned expressions to discover Han Li rising up into the air with his palms pressed against the underside of the mountain, and the number of profound acupoints that had lit up over his body had exceeded one thousand.

Zhao Yuanlai's jaw instantly dropped to the ground in astonishment upon seeing this, while Zhou Xianyang put on a calm facade to mask his own bewilderment, doing his best to make it appear as if he had already anticipated this.

A wave of cheers louder than any of the previous ones rang out over the entire plaza, while Chu Zhong hurriedly crouched down to press his hands against the ink wash mountain, injecting his immortal spiritual power and law powers into it simultaneously.

The black light emanating from the mountain became even brighter than before, while its weight also drastically increased, allowing it to force its way back down again.

However, Han Li had already anticipated this, and he channeled his Titan Vajra Arts before throwing a punch to the left.

A burst of incredibly formidable starpower and bloodline power erupted out of his fist, piercing through space to create a vacuum passageway that was free from the interference of Chu Zhong's law powers.

Han Li darted straight through the passageway, then swiveled around before throwing a punch at Chu Zhong, and in the blink of an eye, he had arrived atop the mountain, then joined his middle and index fingers before thrusting them toward Chu Zhong.

Chapter 1222: Third Eye

An alarmed look appeared on Chu Zhong's face, and the aura that was currently surging out of Han Li's body was so incredibly formidable that Chu Zhong was barely able to work up the will and courage to oppose him.

In this moment, he felt as if he were facing an almighty primordial beast rather than a human cultivator.

He took a deep breath to compose himself, then curled his fingers before wrenching his hands apart.

A sharp, screeching sound instantly rang out across the platform, and black light converged from all directions, causing the entire space to cave in toward the center.

Under the effects of his gravitational law powers, the space on the platform had become completely warped, and as Han Li descended from above, he felt as if an insurmountable barrier had appeared before him, while a burst of immense power was compressing toward him from all directions.

He hurriedly channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and the light radiating from his profound acupoints brightened even further, while the starlight around him materialized itself into a sharp sword that pierced through the space down below.

A loud crack rang out as a rift was sliced into the surrounding black light, allowing Han Li to pass straight through.

All of a sudden, Chu Zhong's spirit domain faded away, as did the ink wash mountain.

His head was raised to the sky, and he was rooted to the spot in mid-air, while Han Li was suspended in the air directly above him in an upside-down fashion with his middle and index fingers pressed against Chu Zhong's glabella.

"I surrender," Chu Zhong sighed.

Han Li immediately removed his fingers from Chu Zhong's glabella, then turned himself upright as he cupped his fist in a salute.

After another wave of raucous cheers, the spectators on the plaza quickly turned their attention to the other ongoing battles, while Zhou Xianyang turned to the dejected Zhao Yuanlai with a gloating smile as he chuckled, "This junior martial brother of mine sure is full of surprises, isn't he?"

"With just one more victory, your sect will receive a Bodhi Token. Let's see if Fellow Daoist Chang can stand the final test," Zhao Yuanlai replied with a hint of bitterness in his voice.

As the two of them were conversing with one another, the officiating elder declared Chang Qi's victory, and Han Li and Chu Zhong exchanged a salute with one another before departing from the platform.

This time, instead of immediately returning to the Prominent Mountain Sect branch, Han Li stayed to watch the other battles.

In the wake of his battle against Chu Zhong, Han Li had come to realize just how severe a handicap it was to only be able to use his powers as a Profound Immortal, and only by learning more about his potential opponents for the next round could he maximize his own chances of securing victory.

There were going to be no slouches advancing to the final round, so he had to be as prepared as possible.

After some examination, Han Li discovered that the twelfth platform was already empty. That was the platform where Sikong Jian had taken part in his second round battle, and it had concluded prior to Han Li's battle.

At the same time, the other battles were also nearing their conclusions, and all of the combatants were making their final push for victory.

Among them, Lou Yuanshan of the Azure Remorse Forest, Wen Changtian of the Skyloom Sect, and Celestial Maiden Ziluo of Serene Celestial Lake had been of particular interest to him.

Wen Changtian possessed the most advanced cultivation base of the trio, having already reached the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage, so all that was left for him to reach the mid-Great Encompassment was to sever a corpse soul.

Celestial Maiden Ziluo's law powers were the most special of the three. She had mastered the extremely rare laws of amethyst, which were a derivation of earth law powers, but took advantage of the refractive quality of amethysts to create mystifying illusions.

As for Luo Yuanshan, he was a human cultivator with a green birthmark on his face, and what had been most noteworthy about him to Han Li was the brutality that he had displayed in battle.

His opponent was someone that he had no bad blood against, but he had beaten them to the point that their cultivation foundation had almost been completely destroyed. If it weren't for the officiating elder's intervention, there was a very good chance that he would've beaten his opponent to death.

By the time the final battle drew to a conclusion, it was already close to nighttime, and Han Li returned to the Prominent Mountain Sect branch.

An uneventful night passed by.

On the third day, Han Li arrived at the venue with the Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators.

This was the final day of competition, and there were far more spectators than on the previous two days. On top of that, a sixth figure had joined Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others at the center of the semi-circular stone platform, and to Han Li's dismay, it was none other than Chi Meng.

The two of them had only recently faced off in a battle against each other, and she was extremely sharp and observant, so he was going to have to be extra vigilant to ensure that she didn't see through his facade.

Before long, the officiating elder's voice rang out.

"All contestants, please step forward to draw lots for the third round."

"Junior Martial Brother Chang, I leave everything in your capable hands," Zhou Xianyang said to Han Li with a solemn expression.

With just one more victory, he would be able to secure a Bodhi Token.

"You can count on me, Senior Martial Brother," Han Li replied with a confident smile, one that was very reassuring to Zhou Xianyang.

As he stepped forward to draw lots, Han Li took a subtle glance at the surrounding area.

The selection event was going to conclude on this day, yet he still had no idea what Wu Yang, Wyrm 3, and the Reincarnation Palace were up to.

He cautioned Weeping Soul and Xiaobai to be on their guard through voice transmission, then stepped onto the platform with the other twenty-three contestants.

"Alright, begin," the officiating elder declared as he tossed twenty-four glowing balls up into the air, and everyone claimed one each.

This time, Han Li's ball carried the number eight, and a faint chuckle rang out from beside him.

He turned to discover that Sikong Jian was looking at him with an eager smile, holding the seventeenth ball in his hand.

Zhou Xianyang's heart immediately sank slightly upon seeing this.

Of all people, it just had to be Sikong Jian!

He knew that Han Li was a Great Encompassment cultivator, but given that he had to keep up his facade as Chang Qi, he wouldn't be able to unleash anywhere near his full power.

To compound his woes even further, Sikong Jian was already an extremely seasoned Great Encompassment cultivator, and judging from the ease with which he had come out on top in his prior two battles, it seemed that he had become even more formidable than before.

With the odds firmly stacked against him, could Han Li really emerge victorious?

The other Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators weren't aware of Han Li's true power, so they were even more concerned than Zhou Xianyang.

"Looks like Fellow Daoist Chang's luck has finally run out. Then again, given his powers, surely defeating Sikong Jian would be a piece of cake, right?" Zhao Yuanlai smirked.

Zhou Xianyang harrumphed coldly and offered no response.

At this point, there were only twenty-four contestants left, so all twelve battles for the round could take place at once.

Han Li and Sikong Jian's battle was set to take place on the eighth platform.

"I must say, this Sikong Jian has some really thick skin to be personally participating in the selection even as the master of the Lone Sun Peak," Immortal Lord Heavenly Star chuckled.

"There are no rules against that. Us cultivators should champion objectivity and practicality above all else. Only short-sighted fools would pass up such an opportunity for inconsequential things like humility and reputation," Huo Yuan harrumphed coldly.

On the surface, sects like the Prominent Mountain Sect and the Lone Sun Peak adopted a stance of neutrality, but under the surface, all of them had ties with the Sun Moon Alliance, the Hundred Creations Mountain, and the other superpowers.

Given the turmoil that was beginning to arise in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, it was very difficult for these sects to survive without powerful backers.

The Prominent Mountain Sect was on very good terms with the Sun Moon Alliance, while the Lone Sun Peak was very close with the Hundred Creations Mountain, so there was naturally some animosity on the subject between Immortal Lord Heavenly Star and Huo Yuan.

"There are indeed no rules prohibiting the participation of sect leaders in the selection event, but I don't think the outcome of this battle is going to be as clear-cut as everyone seems to think," Daoist Master Chun Jun remarked.

"Oh? Who do you think will come out on top, Abbot Chun Jun?" Lu Chuanfeng asked with an intrigued smile.

Daoist Master Chun Jun took a glance at Lu Chuanfeng while internally cursing the latter for his clear attempt to stir up conflict. On the surface, this was only a battle between Chang Qi and Sikong Jian, but in reality, it concerned the competition between the Sun Moon Alliance and the Hundred Creations Mountain, so no matter what he said, he ran the risk of offending one or both of those two superpowers.

"It's hard for me to say. I think you're much better equipped to answer the questions that you've posed me. Your Jade Void Divine Eyes are among the sharpest ocular abilities in existence. When it comes to observation, only Immortal Envoy Feng Tian and Fellow Daoist Chi Meng can compare with you," Daoist Master Chun Jun replied, choosing not to take any sides.

A pleased look appeared on Immortal Envoy's Feng Tian's face at Daoist Master Chun Jun's flattering words.

"My Jade Void Eyes are nothing compared with your Three Talents Qi Observation Technique. All of us are eager to hear your analysis, so don't be so modest, Abbot Chun Jun," Lu Chuanfeng countered.

"I'm not trying to be modest, I'm merely stating the facts. It would be downright comical of me to flaunt my observation abilities in the presence of the three of you. Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, Fellow Daoist Chi Meng, what do you two think?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"Both of these combatants are quite formidable. They could perhaps best even some of the cultivators nurtured by our Heavenly Court," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian replied in an ambiguous manner.

"You're far too kind, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian. The Heavenly Court presides over the entire True Immortal Realm, so there's no way that these cultivators of our Golden Origin Immortal Region can hope to compare with those of the Heavenly Court," Daoist Master Chun Jun said.

"The cultivators of the Heavenly Court are naturally nothing to be scoffed at, but the Golden Origin Immortal Region is extremely abundant with resources, so it's no surprise that it's home to so many elite cultivators. If only all of them were truly loyal to the Heavenly Court," Chi Meng remarked.

Everyone instantly fell silent as they turned to Daoist Master Chun Jun with peculiar looks in their eyes.

"There must be some misunderstanding, Fellow Daoist Chi Meng! We are not under the direct jurisdiction of the Heavenly Court, but our loyalty to the Heavenly Court has never wavered!" Daoist Master Chun Jun hurriedly said.

"There's no need to get so serious, I was just fooling around," Chi Meng giggled, and the tense atmosphere was instantly eased.

Chapter 1223: Seizing the Initiative

With a loud declaration from the officiating elder, the final round of battles commenced.

Han Li and Sikong Jian were standing across from one another on the eighth platform, and neither of them immediately made a move.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Chang. Your cultivation base has advanced significantly since we last met, so I must offer you my congratulations. I can tell that you haven't displayed your true power in the previous two rounds, isn't that right?" Sikong Jian asked with a smile.

"You're far too kind, Peak Master Sikong. I'm sure you haven't put your true power on display, either. Could it be that you intend to catch me off guard by going all-out from the beginning? In that case, I must regrettably inform you that such underhanded tactics aren't going to work," Han Li replied in an indifferent manner.

Sikong Jian's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Let's see if you can back up that big mouth of yours in battle!"

With a sweep of his sleeve, several dozen flying swords flew out of his sleeve before hurtling toward Han Li with astonishing power.

Han Li stomped a foot down onto the ground, blowing a large crater into the platform underfoot as he instantly vanished from the spot.

Sikong Jian's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly flipped a hand over to produce a small, green bell before tossing it up into the air.

The bell swelled drastically in size, and a vast expanse of green light cascaded down from it, forming a cylindrical, green light barrier that encompassed his entire body.

The surface of the giant bell was riddled with antiquated patterns and countless tiny, green runes, giving it the appearance of a very powerful defensive treasure.

The giant bell had only just appeared when a glowing, golden fist emerged behind Sikong Jian amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then struck the green light barrier released by the bell.

A resounding boom rang out as the green light barrier was brutally shattered, and the giant bell itself also exploded countless pieces that erupted in all directions.

A stunned look appeared on Sikong Jian's face as he hurriedly flew back in retreat.

Han Li let loose a low roar as over nine hundred profound acupoints lit up over his body, and he thrust his other hand forward like lightning.

A giant palm projection the size of a house appeared above Sikong Jian before crashing down from above with tremendous power, causing the nearby space to collapse.

Sikong Jian was sent plummeting out of the sky like a meteorite, smashing a huge crater into the platform below.

Han Li was drawing on as much power as he could from the over nine hundred profound acupoints that had lit up over his body, and he swung both hands through the air, conjuring up two more enormous palm projections that came crashing down upon Sikong Jian.

The first of the palm projections clenched itself into a fist that came plummeting down like a meteorite.

This sequence of attacks from Han Li had come incredibly fast, bombarding Sikong Jian without pause, and he was hoping to end the battle while the Sikong Jian was still in a state of complacency.

Otherwise, given the limited power that he was able to put on display, he was not very optimistic about his chances of securing victory in a long and drawn-out battle.

Not only had Sikong Jian been caught off guard by this rapidfire assault from Han Li, many of the spectators had also been stunned into silence.

On the elevated platform, a look of surprise had appeared on Daoist Master Chun Jun's face, while Chi Meng had also raised an eyebrow.

Immortal Lord Heavenly Star was naturally very pleased to see the Prominent Mountain Sect representative seizing the upper hand, while Huo Yuan was looking rather concerned.

Inside the crater on the platform, Sikong Jian was gritting his teeth tightly in fury and frustration. Having just been struck by Han Li's palm projection, there was immense starpower currently wreaking havoc within his body, rendering him unable to muster up any immortal spiritual power.

With a low roar, a layer of azure runes appeared over his skin, releasing an azure light barrier above him.

The descending fist and palm projections struck the azure light barrier with an earth-shattering boom, sending tremendous shockwaves erupting in all directions.

All of the nearby platforms had begun trembling violently, and the officiating cultivators of the Nine Origins Temple hurriedly intervened to stabilize the platforms and the restrictions around them.

The azure light barrier caved in significantly while flashing in an unsteady fashion, but it was able to keep Han Li's attacks at bay for a full second before finally shattering.

Sikong Jian had already managed to catch his breath during this brief window of respite, and he immediately released his spirit domain to encompass the entire platform.

Countless rays of green light were flashing within his spirit domain as a lush forest of tall trees emerged from the platform.

The branches at the tops of the trees were flashing with green light that was giving off a burst of peculiar wood law power fluctuations, and those branches were able to pierce through Han Li's fist and palm projections with ease.

The pair of projections then rapidly dimmed before fading away, as if the energy within them had been devoured.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this as he stopped cold in his tracks.

This was a very strange spirit domain, so he couldn't afford to be reckless.

"His wood law powers are quite remarkable," Daoist Master Chun Jun remarked with an intrigued expression.

"Chang Qi was able to catch Sikong Jian off guard with that unexpected barrage, but ultimately, Profound Immortals are simply inferior. Now that Sikong Jian has had a chance to recover, this battle is as good as over," Huo Yuan said with a pleased expression.

"The battles still not over yet," Immortal Lord Heavenly Star harrumphed in a disgruntled manner.

"Fine, then let's wait and see," Huo Yuan chuckled.

Meanwhile, Zhou Xianyang was looking on with his fists clenched tightly in nervous tension.

"I hope you had a good time using me as your punching bag because it's my turn now!"

Sikong Jian flew out of the crater with a look of cold fury on his face, and he swept a sleeve through the air, upon which the world's origin qi near the platform rippled violently before converging toward his green spirit domain in a frenzy.

All of the trees in the spirit domain began to sway from side to side like countless giant, green pythons, and they pounced at Han Li from all directions.

Han Li was in the process of examining the spirit domain for a way to counteract it, but Sikong Jian clearly wasn't going to give him the time to do as he pleased.

Han Li swiveled around the spot while lashing out with both fists, sending countless golden fist projections erupting in all directions, sweeping toward the surrounding giant trees.

The trees were able to absorb spiritual power, but they weren't very resilient, and they were easily destroyed by the fist projections.

Furthermore, having gleaned the properties of these trees, Han Li had refrained from injecting starpower into his fist projections. As a result, the trees weren't able to absorb any starpower from his attacks, thereby making them easier to break.

A cold sneer appeared on Sikong Jian's face as he more and more trees continued to sprout from his spirit domain at his behest, and at the same time, the dozens of azure flying swords that he had summoned earlier began circling around above his head before transforming into a series of azure threads.

The azure threads then shot forth through the as countless streaks of azure light, all of which rained down upon Han Li in a torrential barrage.

These streaks of azure light were incredibly sharp, and due to the absence of starpower, Han Li's fist projections were limited in power.

Hence, the streaks of azure light were able to pierce through them with ease before reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye.

Han Li remained unflustered as he took a deep breath, and his belly swelled to several times its original size, resembling that of a pregnant woman.

Dozens of profound acupoints lit up over his throat, and he let loose a thunderous roar, releasing a flurry of explosive soundwaves that formed countless blades of sound.

All of the oncoming streaks of azure light were destroyed by the formidable soundwaves, and many of the trees in the spirit domain had also exploded violently.

The restrictions near the platform flashed erratically, while the platform underfoot was on the verge of completely falling apart, despite the nearby officiating cultivators' best efforts to hold everything together.

Han Li had just unleashed the Purgatory Roar ability in the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and it was countless times more powerful than the Vajra Roar that he was capable of unleashing in his Giant Mountain Ape form.

It was an ability that he had only recently mastered, and he hadn't anticipated that he would need to use it so soon.

However, he had intentionally made many alterations while unleashing the ability in order to avoid blowing his own cover.

On the elevated platform, Daoist Master Chun Jun raised a hand, and a streak of golden light shot out of his sleeve before fusing into the restrictions near the platform.

The restrictions instantly turned golden in color, as did the platform, and both were instantly bolstered significantly.

On the platform, a stunned look appeared on Sikong Jian's face at the sight of the power of Han Li's soundwave attacks, but in the next instant, he immediately composed himself as a vast expanse of green mist burst of out of his back before fusing into the trees in the spirit domain.

A metallic gleam instantly surfaced over the trees, and they became far more resilient than before. As a result, they were able to turn the tables and overcome Han Li's fist projections before converging toward him.

Chapter 1224: Concealed Power

Initially, Han Li's fist projections had fanned out in an area with a radius of several hundred feet around him, but that was rapidly shrunk down to only several dozen feet, and it wasn't going to take long before he was inundated by the approaching trees.

His expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was feeling rather dismayed. As expected, the tide was quickly turning against his favor as the battle dragged on longer and longer.

With a flick of his wrists, a pair of giant, black swords appeared in his grasp.

The swords were twenty to thirty feet in length each and as wide as a door, and both of them were giving off a glacial aura.

Engraved onto each sword was a star array in the shape of a dragon, and there were over two hundred star designs in each array.

These two swords were Chang Qi's Black Dragon Swords, and they were forged from Heavenly Meteor Iron, packing immense destructive power.

Han Li begun swinging the pair of massive swords through the air with a loud roar, and even though he wasn't able to unleash their innate power as he hadn't had the time to refine them, just the swords alone were far more destructive than his fist projections, instantly shredding all of the trees that drew close to him.

After taking another gargantuan breath, Han Li let loose a second roar, but this time, the soundwaves were condensed into a single stream that was directed at Sikong Jian.

All of the trees in the path of the stream of white soundwaves were completely pulverized, clearing out a path that was around ten feet wide.

Han Li charged at Sikong Jian like a speeding arrow along the path, and the latter hurriedly joined his palms together to conjure up a ball of dazzling, green light, then thrust his palms forward to send the ball of light hurtling through the air before fusing into the surrounding trees.

A green giant that was several hundred feet tall instantly materialized, and bursts of tremendous wood law power fluctuations erupted out of its body, causing the nearby space to tremble and quiver.

The green giant was wielding an enormous, green saber that was roughly the same height as itself, and it swung the giant saber at the stream of white soundwaves.

A loud explosion rang out as the stream of white soundwaves was eradicated by the green saber, and the latter was only slowed down for a moment before continuing to sweep toward Han Li.

The green giant seemed to be able to draw upon the power of the entire spirit domain, piling immense pressure on Han Li.

At this point, Han Li was already not far away from Sikong Jian, and he had no intention of engaging the green giant in battle, but a clash was unavoidable, so he could only lash out with his Black Dragon Sword.

The sword clashed against the giant saber, and both weapons were instantly snapped into two upon impact.

Despite this, Han Li displayed no intention of backing down, and he abruptly vanished from the spot before immediately reappearing right in front of the green giant's head while sweeping his other Black Dragon Sword through the air.

The green giant was instantly decapitated, and Han Li used its shoulder as a platform to launch himself toward Sikong Jian.

However, the green giant's body suddenly exploded, and countless green branches shot out from within before wrapping themselves tightly around Han Li.

These branches were riddled with green runes and were far more resilient than the trees from before. On top of that, they were giving off a burst of tremendous devouring force that was rapidly leeching away his immortal spiritual power.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. The immortal spiritual power currently in his body had been borrowed from Chang Qi, and if it were to be stripped away by the branches, then his cover would be blown.

With that in mind, he knew that he couldn't conceal his own physical prowess any longer, and all of the close to one thousand eight hundred profound acupoints over his body lit up in unison.

A burst of devastating power erupted out of his profound acupoints, snapping all of the tree branches clinging to his body.

A stunned look appeared on Daoist Master Chun Jun's face upon seeing this, and he exclaimed, "This is remarkable!"

"Indeed. Our Heavenly Court has also developed some Profound Immortals, but it's very difficult for them to advance in their cultivation, so very few of them have even managed to open one thousand profound acupoints. I wonder how he was able to get to this point," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian remarked in an intrigued manner.

A mixture of shock and elation had appeared on Immortal Lord Heavenly Star's face as he took a gloating glance at Huo Yuan, while the latter remained silent with a steely expression.

As for Zhou Xianyang and the other Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators, they had already been stunned into silence.

They had already been astonished by the power displayed by Han Li during his previous battle, and never had they imagined that he was still holding back so much.

On the platform, an alarmed look appeared on Sikong Jian's face as he hurriedly channeled his spirit domain with all his might, attempting to bind Han Li with his tree branches, but in his current state, he was too powerful to be restrained, and he was tearing through the branches in his path with ease.

Right as Han Li was about to tear his way out of the branches altogether, a look of resolve appeared in Sikong Jian's eyes, and a burst of blinding, green light erupted out of his body.

The spiritual pressure emanating from his body instantly swelled to unprecedented heights, revealing his true cultivation base at the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

However, his aura was rather unstable, indicating that he had only recently made a breakthrough.

So he really has already reached the mid-Great Encompassment Stage!

Zhou Xianyang's expression instantly darkened upon seeing this, and his elation at Han Li's tremendous display of power quickly faded away.

In his eyes, an early-Great Encompassment Stage opponent would still be manageable for Han Li, but a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator was surely too much for him to overcome.

In contrast with the surprise and dismay displayed by Zhou Xianyang and Zhao Yuanlai, Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others remained composed and unflustered, as if they had already been aware of this.

Sikong Jian flicked his fingers through the air in rapid succession, and a series of translucent, green threads shot out of his fingertips, then transformed into numerous green rings that vanished into the branches around Han Li.

The branches instantly swelled to around twice their original thickness, and they were able to much better withstand Han Li's immense power.

Right as Han Li was about to unleash another Purgatory Roar to free himself, a series of green trees suddenly materialized out of thin air around him in rapid succession before wrapping themselves around him, instantly forming a huge cocoon that was several hundred feet tall and giving off tremendous wood law power fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, Sikong Jian flipped a hand over to produce a green, wooden ruler with fiery red patterns all over its surface, and it was giving off formidable wood and fire law power fluctuations in equal measure.

More and more green rings continued to fly out of his body before fusing into the green ruler, which began to radiate green and red light, while the wood and fire law power fluctuations surging out of it only grew in potency.

Sikong Jian pointed the ruler directly forward, and the tip of the ruler shuddered slightly as a ball of green light emerged, at the center of which was a crimson flame.

Two bursts of law powers were clashing violently within the ball of light, producing a sharp, screeching wound, but they didn't completely erupt.

All of a sudden, the ball of green light shot forth through the air at Sikong Jian's behest, and initially, it was only the size of a human head, but it quickly swelled to the size of a house and crashed into the green tree cocoon before vanishing into it.

A burst of violent fire law power fluctuations came surging out of the cocoon alongside rays of dazzling, crimson light, and the tree cocoon instantly erupted into flames.

At the same time, it shrank down to only a fraction of its original size while also taking on a perfectly spherical form, and incredibly ferocious wood and fire law powers were clashing violently within the cocoon, but were also somehow enhancing one another in a symbiotic relationship.

"That's the Divine Wood Flame Orb!" Chi Meng exclaimed upon seeing this.

"Isn't that the signature ability of Immortal Lord Wood King, the Dao Ancestor Envoy of the Heavenly Wood Dao Ancestor?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked.

"That's right. With his mastery over both the laws of wood and fire, Immortal Lord Wood King was able to perfectly combine the two to create this Divine Wood Flame Orb ability. With this ability, he was able to hold his own in battle against a late-Great Encompassment and two mid-Great Encompassment cultivators when he was only at the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

“Unfortunately, he became too arrogant for his own good and committed a transgression for which he was punished by the Profound Fire Dao Ancestor. The punishment left him with severe injuries, and he fled the scene, never to be seen again. It seems like he must've met his demise at some point.

“That wooden ruler is most likely the Wood King Ruler, Immortal Lord Wood King's bonded immortal treasure. The fact that Sikong Jian is in possession of it indicates that he must've received Immortal Lord Wood King's inheritance. With that in mind, it's no wonder that he was able to reach the mid-Great Encompassment Stage in spite of his limited aptitude.

“This Divine Wood Flame Orb of his is still far from perfect, and he was only able to unleash it by relying heavily on the Wood King Ruler, so he's still far from reaching the same heights as Immortal Lord Wood King," Chi Meng analyzed.

"Even so, this Divine Wood Flame Orb is still a very formidable ability. Looks like there's still some life in this battle," Daoist Master Chun Jun remarked.

As soon as his voice trailed off, an earth-shattering boom rang out from the platform.

As it turned out, the Divine Wood Flame Orb had suddenly exploded, sending red and green light erupting in all directions.

The entire surrounding space was completely destroyed, then collapsed to form an all-devouring black hole that was several thousand feet in size.

The platform creaked and swayed violently under the immense pressure emanating from the black hole, and it would've already been razed to the ground had it not been for the fortifications made earlier by Daoist Master Chun Jun.

At this point, Han Li had already been swallowed up by the black hole and was nowhere to be seen.

Chapter 1225: Chi Meng's Invitation

Even though Han Li had been swallowed up by the black hole, Sikong Jian didn't dare to let down his guard, and he chanted an incantation while sweeping his Wood King Ruler through the air.

The trees in his spirit domain converged, instantly forming another pair of tree cocoons that shot forth through the air.

The Wood King Ruler began flashing with spiritual light as two balls of red and green light shot out from within, then fused into the pair of tree cocoons.

The tree cocoons erupted into flames, transforming into two more Divine Wood Flame Orbs that plunged into the black hole.

A resounding boom rang out as the black hole warped and trembled violently before swelling to around twice its original size, almost encompassing half of the entire platform.

The restrictions around the platform began to waver once again, much to the alarm and apprehension of the nearby spectators.

At this moment, Sikong Jian's complexion was looking rather pale, and much of the green light around his body had faded away, clearly indicating that unleashing three Divine Wood Flame Orbs in such rapid succession had taken a severe toll on him.

Right as he was about to take a pill and catch his breath, an extremely high-pitched screeching sound suddenly began to ring out within the black hole, following which a Divine Wood Flame Orb shot out from within, flying back at Sikong Jian like a fiery shooting star.

A look of alarm and astonishment appeared on Sikong Jian's face upon seeing this. He had no idea how his attack had suddenly fallen under the control of his opponent, and he hurriedly shot back in retreat, while the trees in his spirit domain came to his aid at his behest.

However, right at this moment, a cold harrumph rang out in his ears, and he felt as if a red-hot dagger had just been plunged into his consciousness, causing him to stop involuntarily in his tracks as he let loose an agonized cry.

At the same time, the oncoming Divine Wood Flame Orb tore through the trees in front of him before crashing into his body with tremendous might.

The orb exploded upon contact, sending red and green light erupting in all directions to shatter the entire surrounding space.

Sikong Jian was naturally well aware of the power of his own Divine Wood Flame Orbs, and he gritted his teeth against the excruciating pain in his consciousness as his Wood King Ruler released a green light barrier around his body.

The green light barrier had only just taken shape when the wave of green and red light descended upon him, sending him flying back through the air.

Fortunately for him, the green light barrier was extremely resilient, and even though it was flashing erratically, it managed to hold itself intact.

However, some of the power from the Divine Wood Flame Orb's explosion was still able to penetrate through the green light barrier to strike Sikong Jian, shattering all of the bones in close to half of his body.

Blood came gushing out of his mouth, and to compound his woes even further, Han Li shot out of the black hole up ahead before crashing into him like a cannonball.

The two of them crashed heavily into the restrictions around the platform, even though Han Li had turned the tables to seize the upper hand, he was looking rather worse for wear himself.

Beneath his True Extreme Film, his clothes were in tatters, and his body was riddled with bleeding wounds and charred burns.

Sikong Jian threw up another mouthful of blood upon colliding against the light barrier on the edge of the platform, but Han Li refused to relent.

He pressed Sikong Jian against the light barrier with his left hand, and his right fist was glowing with blinding, golden light as he slammed it viciously into Sikong Jian's chest.

The light barrier around the platform was already struggling to hold itself intact, and it was instantly shattered upon impact, sending Sikong Jian slamming into the ground outside the platform like a broken rucksack.

The officiating elder had been taking shelter far away, and he hurriedly flew onto the platform to declare Han Li's victory.

It seemed like only an instant ago when Sikong Jian had been in a dominant position, and this sudden turnaround left all of the spectators in a stunned silence.

Only after hearing the outcome announced by the officiating elder did Zhou Xianyang snap out of his stunned stupor, and he sprang to his feet as he raised a fist to the heavens and let loose a thunderous roar of exaltation.

Zhao Yuanlai could only give a disgruntled harrumph, while Daoist Chun Jun and the others were all looking on with surprised expressions.

Given Han Li's physical prowess, it was no surprise that he had managed to smash through the restrictions around the platform, but none of them had been able to see how Han Li had managed to redirect Sikong Jian's own Divine Wood Flame Orb back at him.

"It looks like we all underestimated him! Aside from his physical prowess, he has some other tricks hidden up his sleeve as well. It's quite remarkable that a small sect like the Prominent Mountain Sect is home to such an impressive talent," Lu Chuanfeng remarked with a faint smile.

Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others were also all looking at Han Li with intrigued expressions.

Han Li took a pill to aid in his recovery while channeling his black mask with all his might to conceal his own aura.

Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others observed Han Li for a moment longer, then turned their attention to the other ongoing battles.

Chi Meng also did the same, but for some reason, her peripheral vision continued to linger on Han Li, and there was a perplexed look in her eyes.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief as he felt Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others cast their eyes elsewhere, and he made his way down from the platform.

Sikong Jian had already been helped to his feet by some cultivators of the Lone Sun Peak, and he had regained his mobility after some emergency treatment.

He stepped directly into Han Li's path, glowering intently at him as he asked through tightly gritted teeth, "How did you take my Divine Wood Flame Orb?"

"That's for me to know, and for you to find out," Han Li replied in an indifferent manner before walking away.

As a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator, Sikong Jian was too formidable an adversary for Han Li to defeat even with all of his profound acupoints revealed. Hence, after being cast into that black hole, he had taken a risk and summoned his Profound Heavenly Gourd, using it to seize control of Sikong Jian's Divine Wood Flame Orb and turn the tables.

Sikong Jian looked on with a venomous expression as Han Li departed.

With one final, resentful glare, he turned and stormed away toward the entrance of the Nine Origins Temple, while all of the other Lone Sun Peak cultivators hurriedly followed along.

Meanwhile, Han Li was greeted by all of the exultant Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators, led by Zhou Xianyang, who was brimming with excitement as he grabbed tightly onto Han Li's hand.

"Thank you, Junior Martial Brother Chang."

"There's no need to thank me, I've only done what's expected of me," Han Li replied with a faint smile, then sat down to continue his recovery.

Despite the complexities involved, the battle between Han Li and Sikong Jian was actually the first one to conclude, while all of the other battles were still ongoing.

However, within the span of the next two hours, all of the remaining battles were decided as well.

Before long, Han Li and the other eleven victorious contestants were standing on the same platform, looking down at the countless spectators below.

Luo Yuanshan of the Azure Remorse Forest, Wen Changtian of the Skyloom Sect, and Celestial Maiden Ziluo of the Serene Celestial Lake had all emerged victorious as well.

"After three days of fierce competition, the final twelve victors have arisen, and each one will be taking a Bodhi Token back to their sect," Daoist Master Chun Jun declared with a smile.

The leaders of the twelve victorious sects rose to their feet before cupping their fists in a salute toward the surrounding cultivators.

"Bodhi Tokens are prized treasures that are not to be given out lightly, so please come to the Nine Origins Pavilion in seven days for the token presentation ceremony," Daoist Master Chun Jun continued, and everyone on the platform gave a collective, affirmative response.

Daoist Master Chun Jun quickly announced the results of the third round of battles, following which everyone promptly departed.

Han Li made his way down the mountain with the Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators, but along the way, they were suddenly stopped in their tracks by Chi Meng.

"Zhou Xianyang of the Prominent Mountain Sect pays his respects to Celestial Maiden Chi Meng," Zhou Xianyang hurriedly said as he extended a respectful salute toward Chi Meng, and the other Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators quickly followed suit.

Chi Meng paid no heed to Zhou Xianyang as she cast her gaze directly toward Han Li.

A hint of foreboding welled up in Zhou Xianyang's heart as he noticed the subject of Chi Meng's attention, but he kept up a nonchalant facade as he asked, "To what do we owe this honor, Celestial Maiden Chi Meng?"

"I was very impressed with the incredible prowess displayed by Fellow Daoist Chang Qi during the battle just now, and I'd like to acquaint myself with him. Would that be possible?" Chi Meng asked as she cast her gaze toward Han Li with an alluring smile.

"Of course! It would be my honor to become acquainted with a breathtaking celestial maiden like yourself," Han Li replied in a composed manner.

"I'm flattered, Fellow Daoist Chang," Chi Meng said as her smile widened a little further.

"You can go back with everyone else for now, Senior Martial Brother Zhou, I'll be with you shortly," Han Li said.

Zhou Xianyang hesitated momentarily, then nodded in response, and he promptly departed with the other Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators, leaving Han Li alone with Chi Meng.

"The renowned Golden Maple Forest of the Nine Origins Temple is just up ahead, would you care to join me on a little stroll there, Fellow Daoist Chang?" Chi Meng offered with a bright smile.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this. Back when he was still in the mortal realm, there had been another woman who had extended a similar invitation to him, namely Chen Qiaoqian of the Yellow Maple Valley.

Unfortunately, the heavens had different fates in store for everyone. Han Li had ascended to the True Immortal Realm and even reached the staggering heights of the Great Encompassment Stage, whereas Chen Qiaoqian was already long dead.

Han Li couldn't help but wonder if she had already reincarnated, and if so, where she had reincarnated to.

Han Li quickly composed himself, then smiled as he said, "Who am I to turn down a scenic stroll with a stunning beauty such as yourself? Please lead the way, Celestial Maiden Chi Meng."

Given his cautious nature, there was no way that he would've accepted this invitation, but Chang Qi was a very outgoing womanizer, so Han Li had no choice but to mimic the same personality.

Chapter 1226: Crisis Averted

Han Li and Chi Meng walked along side by side for a short while, and after rounding a corner, they were greeted by the sight of a spacious valley, within which was a forest of golden maple trees that were shimmering with a splendid, golden hue under the light of the sun.

It was indeed a rare and marvelous spectacle to behold.

"These trees are called Rippling Golden Maples, a rare species of spirit tree that's only found in places abundant with metal-attribute spiritual qi. In addition to their beauty, they also give off a gentle, metal-attribute aura that's very beneficial to physical cultivation," Chi Meng introduced.

"Is that right? I'm surprised you're so knowledgeable about matters related to physical cultivation, Celestial Maiden Chi Meng," Han Li praised.

As soon as he arrived in the forest, he had already noticed the nourishing effect that these trees had on his physical body.

"When it comes to physical cultivation, I can't even hope to hold a candle to you, Fellow Daoist Chang. How were you able to reach such staggering heights in your physical cultivation? What's our secret?" Chi Meng asked with an alluring smile.

"Everyone has different physical constitutions, and there are countless bodily cultivation methods out there. I'm always out traveling to different regions, and I was able to open some profound acupoints through some strokes of fortune," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"I see. It looks like traveling the world really is immensely beneficial. I also need to get out more when the opportunity arises. Unfortunately, I haven't been able to explore many immortal regions. Not long ago, I made a trip to Gilded City, and I encountered quite a bit of trouble there," Chi Meng sighed in a wistful manner.

"Oh? What type of trouble are you referring to?" Han Li asked, doing his best to maintain a calm facade in spite of the rising unease in his heart.

"I traveled to Gilded City under orders from the Heavenly Court to capture a wanted fugitive. However, due to some intervention, not only did the fugitive get away, the people accompanying me were all killed," Chi Meng replied as a cold look appeared in her eyes.

"Oh? Who would be so brazen as to interfere with the Heavenly Court's official matters? Were they accomplices of that fugitive?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know, but one of them possessed tremendous physical prowess just like yourself, Fellow Daoist Chang," Chi Meng replied as a meaningful look appeared in her eyes.

"Why are you looking at me like that, Celestial Maiden Chi Meng? You're not suspecting me, are you? I was summoned back to the Prominent Mountain Sect in secret several thousand years ago in preparation to compete for a Bodhi Token, and I've been cultivating in seclusion this entire time. If you don't believe me, you can feel free to come to our Prominent Mountain Sect to cross-examine my story," Han Li said as he feigned a nonchalant expression.

It seemed that despite his best efforts, he was still unable to avoid rousing Chi Meng's suspicions.

Then again, this was no surprise. Great Encompassment cultivators were extremely sensitive, so even though his Reincarnation Palace mask was able to perfectly disguise his aura, there were still inevitably going to be some holes in his act.

"I believe you, Fellow Daoist Chang, but it can't hurt to be careful," Chi Meng said with a faint smile as she flipped a hand over to summon a white ball that was etched with countless golden patterns, and there was also a white vortex inside, giving it a very mysterious appearance.

"What's this?" Han Li asked.

"It's called an Omniscient Globe, and it excels in detecting for law powers. If you're really not the person that I'm looking for, then I'm sure you'd have nothing to fear under the scrutiny of my Omniscient Orb, isn't that right, Fellow Daoist Chang?"

Chi Meng was staring intently at Han Li as she spoke, and at the same time, Han Li could sense several powerful auras locking onto him from all directions in the forest.

"You're suspecting me of wrongdoing just because of my physical prowess, and you're even going as far as to examine my law powers? Don't you think you're being too unreasonable, Celestial Maiden Chi Meng?" Han Li asked in a disgruntled manner.

"I understand that I'm being a little unreasonable, but I have to make sure. If you really aren't the person that I'm looking for, then I'm willing to offer you a formal apology," Chi Meng said as she extended a slight curtsey, but her gaze remained fixed intently on Han Li.

"You're an extremely important figure in the Heavenly Court and the granddaughter of Dao Ancestor Chi Rong, while I'm just an elder of the tiny Prominent Mountain Sect, so of course I'm in no position to refuse. However, before you begin, I would like you to tell me what type of law powers the person you're looking for has mastered. Otherwise, I'm worried that you'll frame me for a crime that I didn't commit," Han Li harrumphed coldly.

They were currently still in the Nine Origins Temple, so if he refused to let Chi Meng carry out her investigation, that would only attract more attention to himself.

At this point, he could only pray that his black Reincarnation Palace could fool Chi Meng's Omniscient Globe.

With that in mind, he channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to conceal all of his time law powers deep within his own body, and his spiritual sense also retreated deep into his consciousness.

All of a sudden, the condensed time law powers in his body abruptly collapsed inward to form an egg-sized golden ball.

The ball was smooth and round, and all of his time law powers were perfectly contained within it without even the slightest amount of leakage.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this.

Chi Meng was unbothered by Han Li's frosty attitude, offering him a faint smile as she replied, "The person that I'm looking for is a cultivator of the laws of time. Thank you for your cooperation, Fellow Daoist Chang."

The golden patterns on the white ball instantly began to glow radiantly at her behest, while the vortex within it also began to revolve even more rapidly as it released a burst of invisible energy fluctuations that swept over Han Li's body.

His immortal spiritual power immediately began to tremble before being involuntarily brought to the fore.

Bursts of black light surfaced over his body, tinged with specks of golden lightning.

The black light represented Chang Qi's law powers, while the golden lightning came from the lightning law powers imbued within Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Having been refined recently, the law powers contained within Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had changed drastically, so there was no danger of the swords blowing his cover.

As for his time law powers, they were concealed deep in his body in an extremely stable fashion, completely unaffected by the Omniscient Globe.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, but on the surface, he continued to maintain a facade of indignant fury.

Chi Meng's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but she was still unconvinced and injected even more immortal spiritual power into the Omniscient Globe.

The immortal spiritual power in Han Li's body began to tremble more vigorously, revealing even more black light and golden lightning, but there were no additional changes aside from that.

"Have you seen enough?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

Chi Meng hesitated momentarily, then cast an incantation seal toward the white ball, and the light emanating from it instantly faded away.

The unrest in the immortal spiritual power in Han Li's body also subsided, and the black and golden light around him quickly faded away.

"Looks like I was wrong to have suspected you, Fellow Daoist Chang. Please accept my sincerest apologies," Chi Meng said in an apologetic manner.

"There's no need to apologize to me. Is there anything else I can help you with? If not, then I'll be taking my leave," Han Li harrumphed coldly, then turned to depart before Chi Meng had a chance to respond.

Chi Meng looked on as Han Li departed from the forest, and judging from her expression, it seemed that her suspicions still hadn't been completely erased.

......

After leaving the golden maple forest, Han Li immediately returned to the Prominent Mountain Sect branch.

As soon as he returned, he was immediately approached by an anxious Zhou Xianyang, who asked, "Did Chi Meng ask to see you because she was suspicious of your identity, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"No, she was just interested in how I was able to progress so far in my physical cultivation and wanted to ask me some questions," Han Li replied, deciding not to reveal the truth to Zhou Xianyang in case he reported the matter to Wyrm 3 and Wu Yang.

He had already completed his mission, and he didn't want anything to go wrong as that could potentially give the Reincarnation Palace second thoughts about giving him the information that they had on Jin Tong.

Zhou Xianyang was quite relieved to hear this, and he nodded in response.

"Now that you mention it, I'm also quite curious about how you were able to reach this level in your physical cultivation. Is there some secret that you can share? I'm willing to offer fifty million Immortal Origin Stones in exchange," Zhou Xianyang said with a look of fervent interest in his eyes.

"I'm afraid there's no secret for me to tell. I was able to progress to this point solely through a series of strokes of fortune," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, and a disappointed look appeared on Zhou Xianyang's face upon hearing this.

"I've already fulfilled my end of the agreement and secured a Bodhi Token for your Prominent Mountain Sect, when are you going to satisfy my request?" Han Li asked.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Han. Fellow Daoist Wu Yang has already been made aware of your mission completion, and he's already given me what you want, but I'm afraid I can only relay the information to you once I've gotten my hands on the Bodhi Token," Zhou Xianyang replied with an apologetic smile.

"That's a reasonable arrangement. In that case, I'll just have to wait seven more days," Han Li said with a slight nod.

After that, the two of them chatted for a while longer before parting ways.

......

Seven days flew by in a flash, and Han Li returned to the Nine Origins Temple with the Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators.

A cultivator from the Nine Origins Temple was already waiting at the entrance of the temple, and they led the Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators deeper into the temple.

Han Li was walking along with everyone else while surreptitiously scanning his surroundings.

He had already asked Lan Yan to tell him about as much of the temple's layout as she could, and she had also drawn him a map.

The Nine Origins Temple took up an enormous area, and it was split up into the inner temple and the outer temple.

Unfortunately, given Lan Yan's lackluster status in the sect, she was only permitted to move around in the outer temple, and she had only been to the inner temple once or twice. Hence, the map of the outer temple was quite detailed, while only several locations of the inner sect had been marked out.

However, the area that they were currently passing through was clearly illustrated on Lan Yan's map, and that was quite reassuring to Han Li.

Chapter 1227: Disturbance

Before long, Han Li's group had arrived in front of a giant palace halfway up the mountain, and the words "Nine Origins Pavilion" were inscribed onto a plaque above the palace's entrance.

"Please come with me, fellow daoists," the guide said as he led the Prominent Mountain Sect cultivators into the palace.

The Nine Origins Pavilion didn't appear very large from the outside, but its interior was surprisingly spacious, spanning over ten thousand feet in size, so it was clear that some type of spatial restrictions had been incorporated into the building during its construction.

At this point, cultivators from several other sects had already arrived, and some of Zhou Xianyang's acquaintances immediately approached him to exchange some greetings.

Due to the stunning display that he had put on during the selection event, some people also approached Han Li to try and befriend him. Thankfully, Han Li had already been made aware of who these people were and their relationships to Chang Qi, so he was able to hold conversations with them just fine.

Close to an hour later, the cultivators from all twelve victorious sects had arrived, but none of people from the other sects were present.

A short while later, the sound of a gong being struck rang out, and everyone in the palace immediately rose to their feet as Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, Daoist Master Chun Jun, Lu Chuanfeng, Huo Yuan, and Immortal Lord Heavenly Star made their way into the room.

Trailing along behind Daoist Master Chun Jun were several Nine Origins Temple elders, but to Han Li's relief, Chi Meng wasn't in accompaniment.

Everyone in the palace extended a collective salute.

"We pay our respects to Immortal Envoy Feng Tian and Abbot Chun Jun!"

"No need for formalities. All of you have been invited here to receive your Bodhi Tokens, so without further ado, I ask that the twelve victorious cultivators please step forward," Daoist Master Chun Jun declared with a warm smile.

Han Li and the others emerged from their respective sects, arranging themselves into a row in front of Daoist Master Chun Jun and Immortal Envoy Feng Tian.

Daoist Master Chun Jun took a step back, while Immortal Envoy Feng Tian stepped forward and declared, "Present the Bodhi Tokens!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, an ornate, rectangular, golden box appeared out of thin amid a flash of radiant, golden light.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian extended a bow toward the ornate box, then opened it to reveal twelve antiquated, golden tablets that gave off a peculiar aura, as if they contained some type of special energy.

Excited looks appeared on everyone's faces at the sight of the twelve tablets, and Han Li also feigned an excited expression to fit in with everyone else, but in reality, he wasn't all that excited by the sight of the Bodhi Tokens.

After all, securing a Bodhi Token was only a means to an end for him, and his ultimate objective had always been to rescue Jin Tong.

Once the Bodhi Token was secured, he would receive the information on Jin Tong promised to him by the Reincarnation Palace, and it would be time for him to plan a rescue.

Given his current cultivation base, there was no way that he could hope to oppose the entire Nine Origins Temple on his own, so the ideal situation for him would be for the Reincarnation Palace to muddy the waters.

However, even to this day, the objective for this mission still hadn't been revealed to him, and he didn't know if a good opportunity would arise, so he could only take things one step at a time.

Right at this moment, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian made a hand seal, and the twelve tablets flew out of the ornate box before landing in the hands of Han Li and the others.

Upon catching his Bodhi Token, Han Li was surprised to discover that it was extremely heavy for its size, and it was cold to the touch.

Furthermore, he could sense a burst of peculiar energy within it, and he couldn't help but wonder what type of material it had been forged from.

"These Bodhi Tokens were personally refined by the Time Dao Ancestor himself, and they're your tickets to the upcoming Bodhi Banquet, so make sure to keep them safe," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian said.

Han Li was just about to examine the contents of the tablet, and he immediately stopped what he was doing upon learning that the tokens had been refined by the Time Dao Ancestor.

"As usual, the Bodhi Banquet will be held in the Jade Pond Paradise. Each token will grant entry to three people. As for what you get out of the Bodhi Banquet, that will be up to you," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian continued.

Right at this moment, a beastly roar suddenly rang out from somewhere far away in the distance.

The expressions of all of the elders in the Nine Origins Pavilion instantly changed slightly upon hearing this, while Daoist Master Chun Jun turned to a short and stocky elder with his brows furrowed in an inquisitive manner.

The latter instantly closed his eyes and pressed the tips of his index and middle fingers against his own glabella, following which rings of golden light began to proliferate outward from his glabella.

The rings of golden light were giving off formidable soul power fluctuations, and it seemed as if he were using some type of special method of communication.

Moments later, he removed his fingers from his own glabella as he reported, "For some reason, the Green-Eyed Qilin over on the spirit beast mountain has gone on a rampage, and it's burst through its stable and currently wreaking havoc all over the mountain."

"The Green-Eyed Qilin is a Great Encompassment Stage spirit beast that's always possessed a high level of intelligence and a mellow nature, why has it suddenly gone on a rampage? Where's Elder Shan Yang? Isn't he the one who's always been responsible for looking after the Green-Eyed Qilin?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked, and his placid reaction made it seem as if this were only a minor incident.

"Elder Shan Yang traveled to a lower realm to tame an early-High Zenith Stage demon beast that's been causing a great deal of destruction, and he's still yet to return," the short and stocky elder replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the commotion outside became even more chaotic, and it sounded as if even more spirit beasts had broken free.

After some further communication with the people on the spirit beast mountain, an anxious look appeared on the elder's face as he reported, "Many of the stables on the mountain had been broken by the Green-Eyed Qilin, and over seventy spirit beasts have broken free. Many of them have already stormed off the mountain, and two of them have made it to the spirit medicine fields, but thankfully, Elder Murong was able to intercept them."

"I have to attend to our guests here, so get Senior Martial Brother Lei Jun to take care of this matter," Daoist Master Chun Jun instructed.

The short and stocky elder gave an affirmative response before closing his eyes to initiate another bout of communication.

"My apologies, fellow daoists. Let's get back to the matter at hand," Daoist Master Chun Jun said with a composed smile.

"No matter. Let's continue," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian replied, yet right as the proceedings were about to continue, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from outside the Nine Origins Pavilion, causing the entire palace to shudder violently.

This was immediately followed by a string of thunderous explosions that came from a different direction as the spirit beast mountain.

"What's going on?" Daoist Master Chun Jun asked as he turned to the short and stocky elder once again.

After some further correspondence, the elder delivered Daoist Master Chun Jun another report, but this time, it was through voice transmission.

After hearing what the elder had to say, a hint of fury finally appeared on Daoist Master Chun Jun's face.

"My sincerest apologies, fellow daoists, but some urgent matters have arisen that I must attend to in person, so please wait here for me in the meantime," Daoist Master Chun Jun said as he rose to his feet before cupping his fist in an apologetic salute.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Chun Jun, we'll have some tea here and await your return," Huo Yuan said.

With a flick of his wrist, Daoist Master Chun Jun summoned a silver horsetail whisk, which he casually swept through the air to conjure up a spatial door that collapsed inward.

Han Li was rather intrigued to see this. Daoist Master Chun Jun wasn't a cultivator of spatial laws, yet he was able to conjure up this spatial door, so the horsetail whisk in his hand had to have been a powerful spatial immortal treasure.

"Please attend to our guests in my stead, Elder Yu, I'll be right back," Daoist Master Chun Jun instructed, then stepped into the spatial door and vanished from the spot.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian and the others sat back down to chat over some tea, while the people from the twelve sects were looking a little uneasy.

"Rest assured, fellow daoists, Abbot Chun Jun won't be gone for too long," the short and stocky elder with the Yu surname reassured, and the people from the twelve sects could only continue to sit in silence.

Roughly fifteen minutes passed by, and Daoist Master Chun Jun still hadn't returned.

"Is the Reincarnation Palace making a move?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"Our mission is only to secure a Bodhi Token. I don't know anything else," Zhou Xianyang replied.

Han Li knew that he wouldn't be able to get any answers from Zhou Xianyang, so he didn't ask any further questions.

Right at this moment, another thunderous explosion rang out, and this one was far closer to the Nine Origins Pavilion, causing the entire palace to tremble violently.

Much of the furniture in the palace was knocked over by the violent tremors, and everyone hurriedly stood up to steady themselves.

"What's going on?" Celestial Maiden Ziluo asked.

Everyone had felt just how violent that explosion had been, and what was even more alarming was that it had taken place very close to the Nine Origins Pavilion.

Han Li swept his gaze around the palace to discover that a layer of golden light had surfaced over the ground, the ceiling, and the surrounding walls, and the complex patterns within the golden light formed an extremely advanced protective array.

"Rest assured, everyone, the Nine Origins Pavilion is an extremely important location in our sect, so it's protected by its own array. Even a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator would struggle to force their way into the palace through the array, so you'll be safe in here," Elder Yu hurriedly reassured.

As soon as his voice trailed off, an even more violent explosion rang out, rocking the entire palace once again.

The golden array around the palace also trembled violently, saving the palace from the verge of collapse.

This time, it had become abundantly clear to everyone that something was very wrong, and a sense of panic was beginning to spread.

Only Immortal Envoy Feng Tian and the others remained calm and composed, continuing to chat casually among themselves as if whatever was happening outside had nothing to do with them.

Chapter 1228: Incredulous

"What's going on, Elder Yu? This is clearly more than just a spirit beast outbreak," Luo Yuanshan asked with tightly furrowed brows, and everyone instantly turned their attention to Elder Yu upon hearing this.

"Don't go making wild guesses, everyone. Like I said earlier, some spirit beasts managed to break loose, and it's going to take some time to capture them, so please wait here for now," Elder Yu said in a serious manner.

"Elder Yu, if something's happened, then please be truthful to us, and perhaps we can help out," Zhou Xianyang said

"Nonsense! Since when has our Nine Origins Temple ever required external assistance!" Elder Yu snapped in an indignant manner.

"My apologies, that was presumptuous of me. Seeing as the Bodhi Tokens have already been presented, there's no point for us to stay here, so why don't we all return to our sects so that we don't get in your way?" Zhou Xianyang proposed.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the entire Nine Origins Pavilion was rocked violently once again. This tremor was even stronger than the previous one, and visible cracks had begun to appear on the wooden pillars in the palace. If it weren't for the fortifying restrictions that were in place, the entire building would've most likely already collapsed.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's brows furrowed slightly in displeasure upon seeing this, and he rose to his feet as he asked, "What's going on with your Nine Origins Temple? How is it taking this long to subdue a few spirit beasts?"

Elder Yu didn't dare to deceive a immortal envoy of the Heavenly Court, and after a brief hesitation, he cupped his fist in a salute as he answered truthfully, "After the spirit beasts broke loose, disturbances had begun arising in many other parts of our sect as well, so things have been a little hectic."

"Where is Daoist Master Chun Jun right now?" Immortal Envoy Feng Tian asked.

"He's concerned that the ancestral hall could be impacted by the disturbances, so he's currently stationed there, and he'll be back once everything has settled down," Elder Yu explained.

A sense of unease instantly arose once again, and everyone requested Elder Yu to open the restriction to let them leave.

"Just do as you're told and stay here!" Elder Yu snapped in an authoritative manner, and everyone instantly fell silent again, not daring to speak out any further.

"What is the meaning of this, Elder Yu? These people have received Bodhi Tokens and are entitled to attend the Bodhi Banquet held in our Middle Earth Immortal Region, yet you seem to have no respect for them at all," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian said in a cold voice.

"I meant no disrespect, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian," Elder Yu hurriedly said in an apologetic manner.

Right at this moment, Immortal Lord Heavenly Star suddenly stood up and came to Elder Yu's aid as he said, "With Fellow Daoist Chun Jun personally overseeing everything, there's nothing for us to worry about. Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, I hear that you're an avid go player. Would you care for a game to help take our mind off things?"

Lu Chuanfeng also stood up as he chimed in, "I'm sure Elder Yu meant no disrespect, he must simply be a little flustered from all of the commotion."

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian relented upon hearing this and sat back down, while Immortal Lord Heavenly Star sat down across from him and swept a sleeve through the air to summon a jade go board and a pair of jars that contained black and white go stones.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian initially had no interest in playing, but an intrigued look surfaced in his eyes at the sight of the items on the table, and he opened the jar in front of him, upon which a burst of faint purple light instantly shone out from within.

The go stones in the jar were all giving off a purple glow, making them resemble purple stars in the night sky, and they were also giving off bursts of starpower fluctuations.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's eyes instantly lit up as he hurriedly asked, "Could this be the legendary set of go apprati by the name of Starfall?"

"Indeed, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian. What a sharp pair of eyes you possess. If you can beat me in a game, then you can have this set of go apparati. What do you say?" Immortal Lord Heavenly Star proposed.

"Who am I to turn down such a kind offer?" Immortal Envoy Feng Tian chuckled, and the two of them began playing a game together, leaving everyone else to their own devices.

Huo Yuan took a glance at everyone else, then began discussing what appeared to have been some private matters with Lu Chuanfeng, as evidenced by the soundproofing light barrier that he had conjured up.

With that, the entire palace fell silent again, with the silence punctuated only by the occasional sound of the placed go stones.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian set a glowing stone down onto the board as he looked up at Immortal Lord Heavenly Star with a smile and asked, "Are you intentionally trying to present this set of go apparati to me as a gift? Otherwise, surely there's no way to explain all of these blunders that you've made."

"Not at all, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, I'm simply no match for you. Having said that, a go board is much like an array plate, and the stones that are placed upon it cannot be taken back," Immortal Lord Heavenly Star replied with a smile.

"What's that supposed to mean?" Immortal Envoy Feng Tian asked in a puzzled manner.

Immortal Lord Heavenly Star didn't answer the question. Instead, he merely declared, "It's my turn."

He picked up a white stone before setting it down upon the very center of the board, and as soon as the stone was placed, a burst of purple light appeared over the jade go board without any warning.

A burst of incredibly violent starpower then erupted out of the go board, forming violent shockwaves that swept through the air in all directions, destroying all of the surrounding furniture.

Huo Yuan and Lu Chuanfeng hurriedly retreated to the other side of the palace before looking back with alarmed expressions to discover that the table beneath the go board had already been completely pulverized.

The jade go board itself had also vanished, replaced by a glowing, azure go board projection on the ground that was over a hundred feet in size.

The lines on the go board projection had formed numerous threads of white light that were wound around Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's body, locking him firmly into place.

As for the white stones on the go board, they had formed a complex starlight array that was radiating purple starlight while also giving off formidable starpower fluctuations.

Meanwhile, Immortal Lord Heavenly Star was standing directly across from Immortal Lord Envoy with a smile on his face and his palms joined together as if he were praying.

"I need to borrow your head for an important matter, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian."

As soon as voice trailed off, he thrust his palms forward forcefully, and all of the white go stones on the ground immediately lit up before transforming into several dozen miniature starlight dragons before pouncing toward dozens of important acupoints all over Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's body.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and all Immortal Envoy Feng Tian had a chance to do was reflexively draw upon his own law powers to conjure up a suit of blue water armor around his own body.

An intrigued look appeared on Han Li's face at his gaze fell upon the suit of water armor, which was giving off faint water vapor while rippling incessantly, and despite the fact that it was no thicker than a normal robe, it contained tremendous water-attribute spiritual power that was as vast as an ocean.

"Have you gone insane, Immortal Lord Heavenly Star?" Huo Yuan roared in an incredulous voice as he sprang forward to try and intervene, but it was already too late.

The dozens of miniature starlight dragons plunged into the suit of water armor around Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, upon which they were slowed down significantly, as if they had dove headfirst into a sea of treacle.

With Huo Yuan and Lu Chuanfeng rapidly closing in, a look of disappointment appeared in Immortal Lord Heavenly Star's eyes as he sighed, "You're much more capable than I anticipated. What a pity..."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly switched to a different hand seal while flying back in retreat.

Immediately thereafter, the dozens of starlight dragons swimming through Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's suit of water armor began to radiate blinding, white light.

Specks of purple starlight could be seen within the white light, and it exploded violently to release a vast torrent of devastating starpower.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian was situated right in the epicenter of the explosion, and he was engulfed by a vortex of white starlight that rapidly proliferated outward in all directions.

The entire surrounding space in a radius of around a thousand feet was torn to shreds by the eruption of starpower, but strangely enough, the starpower vortex refused to spread any further beyond this point.

Instead, it remained enclosed around Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, continuing to ravage the surrounding space.

The top of the vortex had torn straight through the restrictions above to blow a huge hole into the ceiling, and Immortal Lord Heavenly Star flew out of the hole as a streak of light.

Huo Yuan was furious as he took a glance at the swirling, white vortex, then turned to Lu Chuanfeng as he yelled, "Palace Master Lu, you look after Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, I'll go pursue Heavenly Star."

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke to summon a purple flying boat that was around a hundred feet in length, and as soon as he leaped onto the boat, all of the spirit patterns on its surface instantly lit up, following which it also vanished in a flash through the hole in the ceiling.

Lu Chuanfeng was about to set off in pursuit of Immortal Lord Heavenly Star, but he could only descend back into the palace upon seeing this.

No one else in the palace had been harmed by the explosion, but they had still been startled, nonetheless, and all of them had retreated to the other side of the palace while staring at the swirling, white vortex in incredulity, unable to believe what they had just witnessed.

Chapter 1229: Exposed

A short while later, the vortex of white light finally began to wane in power, and it quickly faded away into specks of starlight, following which Immortal Envoy Feng Tian fell out from within.

Han Li cast his gaze toward Immortal Envoy Feng Tian to discover that his suit of water armor was already nowhere to be seen, and that his robes had been severely ravaged, revealing countless deep gashes all over his body.

What was even more concerning for him was the several important acupoints in his body that had been damaged by the explosion, including his dantian. Much of the residual starpower from the explosion had infiltrated those acupoints and were constantly slicing away at them from the inside like countless sharp knives, causing him immense agony.

A low snarl was rattling in his throat, and he was enraged beyond words.

He couldn't even recall how many millennia it had been since he had suffered such severe injuries, and the pain of the humiliation inflicted upon him by Immortal Lord Heavenly Star almost outweighed the physical agony that he was experiencing.

"I'm going to hunt down all of the Sun Moon Alliance cultivators in this entire immortal region!" he spat through gritted teeth.

"Please focus on treating your own injuries first, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian. Mountain Master Huo has already gone to pursue Immortal Lord Heavenly Star, and you can do with him as you please once he's been captured," Lu Chuanfeng said.

The Sun Moon Alliance was a superpower that could almost stand toe to toe with the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, and it had countless cultivators under its banner, certainly far too many for all of them to be realistically hunted down.

"I'm going to make the Sun Moon Alliance pay for this!" Immortal Envoy Feng Tian snarled, and his fury and resentment only seemed to be growing.

He swept his gaze over the cultivators from the twelve sects, and he felt even more enraged to have had so many people bear witness to his humiliation.

"How did things become like this?" Celestial Maiden Ziluo sighed in a forlorn manner.

"Something's clearly not right here. We can't continue to stay here. Otherwise, there's no telling what else could happen," someone else said with tightly furrowed brows.

"The restrictions here are meant to protect us, but if you ask me, all they're doing is keeping us imprisoned in this place! We can't stay here any longer!" a third person chimed in in agreement.

"Let's get out of here!"

Everyone quickly rose to their feet as they proceeded to depart from the palace.

"All of you are to stay here until further notice from our abbot!" Elder Yu said in a stern voice as he stood up to oppose everyone.

"We were only willing to stay here because you told us that this is the safest place in the Nine Origins Temple, yet that's clearly been proven not to be the case, so it would be far too unreasonable for you to expect us to continue to stay here!" Zhou Xianyang protested.

Elder Yu knew that Zhou Xianyang was right, and he didn't know how to respond.

"If you have the time to be opposing us, wouldn't your time be much better spent quelling the unrest in the temple? Right now, all we want is to leave the Nine Origins Temple!" Luo Shanyuan chimed in.

After a brief hesitation, Elder Yu heaved a faint sigh as he finally acquiesced, "In that case, I'll get some elders to guide all of you out of our temple, but if any of you stray away from the group to roam the temple without permission, then you'll be regarded as an enemy and struck down on sight, understood?"

Everyone was eager to agree to leave as soon as possible, so they all readily nodded in response.

With that, Elder Yu called over a few Nine Origins Temple elders and instructed them to guide the cultivators of the twelve sects out of the temple in batches.

Right as Han Li was hatching a plan to slip away, Zhou Xianyang's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"We've already completed our mission, so we can leave now, Fellow Daoist Han."

"I still have some unfinished business, so I can't leave the Nine Origins Temple for now," Han Li replied.

"In that case, give me the Bodhi Token, and I'll give you what you want in exchange," Zhou Xianyang said.

Han Li immediately pulled out the token that was hidden up his sleeve and handed it to Zhou Xianyang without any hesitation, who accepted the tablet while also slipping a jade slip into Han Li's grasp.

"I'll be going on ahead then, Fellow Daoist Han. Make sure to look after yourself," Zhou Xianyang communicated through voice transmission, then departed from the Nine Origins Pavilion with the first group of cultivators to leave.

Han Li had finally obtained the information that would help him rescue Jin Tong, but he still couldn't think of a good plan that would allow him to slip away unnoticed.

As one group of cultivators left after another, the number of people in the palace continued to dwindle, and finally, Han Li was among the final dozen or so cultivators who were still yet to leave.

Elder Yu took a glance at Han Li and the others, then turned to the final Nine Origins Temple elder as he instructed, "Take them away."

The elder gave an affirmative response, then led Han Li and the others out of the Nine Origins Pavilion.

Han Li was walking along at the very rear of the group, and he noticed out of his peripheral vision that Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's entire body was enshrouded in a layer of faint, blue light, and that there was a semi-transparent, longan-sized blue bead hovering above his head, giving off bursts of incredibly formidable water law power fluctuations.

Under the nourishment of these water law power fluctuations, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian had already fully recovered from his external injuries, but his aura was still wavering in an unsteady fashion, clearly indicating that the starpower wreaking havoc in his body still hadn't been eradicated.

Right at this moment, an intense sense of foreboding suddenly welled up in Han Li's heart, and he was so alarmed that he immediately abandoned his disguise, channeling his Reversal True Axis ability to instantly rush from the very rear of the group to the forefront.

However, right as he sprang into action, the surrounding air temperature abruptly plummeted drastically as a burst of glacial power swept over the entire Nine Origins Pavilion.

Han Li was in the process of passing by a group of Lake Mountain Sect elders when he saw them freeze solid right before his very eyes, and he was also frozen to the spot in the instant that he was about to make it out of the pavilion.

All of a sudden, he felt as if the entire world had been frozen solid, and what was even more alarming was that a burst of incredibly potent glacial power had infiltrated his body, freezing his immortal spiritual power and rendering him unable to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

It was a very strange feeling that was much like back when his soul had been sealed by the Origin Separation Law Chains, and it was as if his own immortal spiritual power no longer belonged to him.

Thankfully, he still had his physical prowess to resort to, and he hurriedly channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

All of the profound acupoints all over his body lit up at once, releasing bursts of formidable starpower to strike at the layer of blue ice crystals that he had been encased in.

However, the blue ice crystals displayed no signs of receding at all, and to compound Han Li's woes even further, they were releasing bursts of glacial power to infiltrate his body, spreading toward his internal organs.

He could even feel his own heart becoming colder and colder, while his heartbeat was also slowing, and he hurriedly called upon the Essence Fire Raven to protect his internal organs.

At the same time, the entire interior of the Nine Origins Pavilion had been sealed in ice, and everyone inside had been reduced to human ice sculptures, presenting a beautiful yet chilling sight to behold.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian naturally hadn't been encased in ice like everyone else, and he had already opened his eyes to regard Lu Chuanfeng with an inquisitive gaze.

"What are you doing, Palace Master Lu? Why have you released your spirit domain?"

"Don't be alarmed, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian. There's still a little Reincarnation Palace rat in this place, and I'll withdraw my spirit domain once I've captured him," Lu Chuanfeng explained as his gaze fell upon Han Li, and the sense of foreboding in Han Li's heart only deepened upon seeing this.

At the same time, he was feeling very perplexed. He had been wearing his black Reincarnation Palace mask this entire time, and he hadn't done anything to expose himself, so how had Lu Chuanfeng managed to see through his disguise.

At the moment, all he could do was channel his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might to try and break free from the glacial prison that he had been encased in, while the Essence Fire Raven did everything in its power to ward off the glacial power that was infiltrating his body.

Simultaneously, he was also frantically contacting the vial spirit of the Heaven Controlling Vial with his spiritual sense. If worse came to worst, then transmigration would be his only ticket to safety.

However, if he had to resort to that, then he would definitely have to leave the Nine Origins Temple, and that would make the objective of saving Jin Tong even more impossible to achieve.

"There's a Reincarnation Palace cultivator among these people?" Immortal Envoy Feng Tian asked in a surprised manner.

"Initially, I wasn't certain, but in the instant that I released my spirit domain, he used the True Mantra Sect's Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, so my suspicions have been confirmed," Lu Chuanfeng replied with a smile.

"Let me see who it is," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian said in a cold voice as he rose to his feet, dusting off the ice crystals that had taken shape over his robes as he made his way over to Lu Chuanfeng's side.

"If I'm not mistaken, this man is none other than Han Li, a very active fugitive that's only recently appeared on the Immortal Slaying List," Lu Chuanfeng said as he pointed a finger at Han Li.

A flash of recollection appeared in Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's eyes upon hearing this, and upon noticing his reaction, Lu Chuanfeng remarked, "It seems like you've heard of him, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian."

"I have, indeed. He has repeatedly meddled in our Heavenly Court's affairs and even stormed into the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Palace and killed Palace Master Dongfang Bai. Immortal Lord Miao Fa was sent to personally capture him, yet even she failed to detain him, but it seems like his luck has finally run out!" Immortal Envoy Feng Tian said in an ecstatic manner.

"It sounds like he has a rather extensive history of opposing the Heavenly Court," Lu Chuanfeng remarked.

Chapter 1230: Ulterior Motive

"On top of that, he's also harboring a massive..."

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian abruptly caught himself before he could utter the word "secret". In his excitement at the prospect of Han Li's capture, he had almost let slip some very sensitive information.

Lu Chuanfeng didn't pry into the matter, merely smiling as he asked, "What do you plan to do with him, Immortal Envoy Feng Tian?"

"Detain him for now, Palace Master Lu. I'll make a decision once I've reported this matter to the Heavenly Court. You and I will surely be rewarded handsomely for the capture of such an important fugitive," Immortal Envoy Feng Tian said with an excited smile.

Lu Chuanfeng's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was feeling rather disgruntled.

He was the sole contributor to Han Li's capture, yet Immortal Envoy Feng Tian had suddenly made it a two-man job.

On top of that, given his status in the Heavenly Court, most of the reward was most likely going to fall upon him.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian could sense Lu Chuanfeng's dissatisfaction, but his smile remained unchanged as he said, "Make sure to keep a close eye on him, Palace Master Lu. I'm going to report this matter directly to the Heavenly Court through my communication array plate, and I must not be interrupted in the process."

Lu Chuanfeng nodded in response, and Immortal Envoy Feng Tian immediately sat down with his legs crossed, then flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized, white jade plate.

He cast an incantation seal into the jade plate, and it rose up into the air on its own, following which all of the patterns on its surface lit up to form a series of runes that began to revolve rapidly over the array plate.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian closed his eyes upon seeing this, then began to chant an incantation, and a ring-shaped rune surfaced over his glabella before projecting a beam of white light onto the array plate.

The array plate shuddered slightly as a burst of rippling light came proliferating out of it.

Right at this moment, the white light emanating from Han Li's body suddenly faded, and it was replaced by a layer of dark red light, accompanied by an eruption of incredibly formidable bloodline power.

Having been backed into a corner, Han Li had no choice but to channel his true spirit bloodlines in conjunction with his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and he immediately began to take on his devilish deity form.

However, the glacial power that had infiltrated his body made the transformation extremely slow to complete.

A look of finality and resolve appeared in Han Li's eyes as he abandoned his protection of his own internal organs, releasing his Essence Fire Raven out of his body to melt away the layer of glacial ice to help him complete his transformation as soon as possible.

"Don't go causing trouble for me now," Lu Chuanfeng grumbled as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a blue talisman that fell upon Han Li's body.

In the instant that the talisman made contact with his body, his blood was instantly frozen solid in his veins. As a result, he was unable to channel his true spirit bloodlines any further, so all of his prior efforts were rendered null.

After being briefly distracted by Han Li, Lu Chuanfeng turned his attention back to Immortal Envoy Feng Tian to discover that a humanoid projection was already beginning to take shape on the jade array plate before him.

All of a sudden, a drop of blood essence flew out of the palm of Lu Chuanfeng's hand, forming a crimson rune as he slammed his hand down onto the top of Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's head.

A pillar of blue light erupted out of the palm of his hand, instantly filling Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's entire body.

Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's eyes sprang wide open as if he had just been struck by lightning, and his eyes were completely bloodshot, but strangely enough, the blood vessels in them were blue rather than red.

He opened his mouth slightly, but was unable to make any sound, and only a plume of blue mist escaped from between his lips.

In the next instant, his entire body was frozen solid, while the jade array plate in front of him had also been frozen solid, falling to the ground where it shattered into countless pieces.

Immediately thereafter, Lu Chuanfeng swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a gust of fierce wind, and Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's body and nascent soul disintegrated into an icy, blue powder that spilled down onto the ground.

Lu Chuanfeng took a glance at the storage tools strewn all over the ground, but he displayed no intention of retrieving them. Instead, he swept his sleeve through the air once again, and all of the storage tools were encased in a layer of blue frost before also being reduced to icy powder.

All the while, Han Li was looking on in complete astonishment.

Immortal Lord Heavenly Star's betrayal had already been a shocking turn of events, and right as it appeared as if Immortal Envoy Feng Tian's luck had turned for the better, he had lost his life under even more astonishing circumstances!

What on earth is happening here?!

Before Han Li had a chance to make sense of the situation, a string of loud thumps rang out in succession throughout the Nine Origins Pavilion, and the dozen or so frozen figures around Han Li all exploded into icy, blue powder, just like Immortal Envoy Feng Tian.

In the end, Han Li was the only one left.

Even so, he was still in a state of despair. He knew better than to believe that Lu Chuanfeng was here to save him. If that were the case, then there would've been no need for Lu Chuanfeng to freeze him here.

Han Li had been frantically calling upon the vial spirit this entire time, but for some reason, he received no response.

Without the vial spirit's help, there was no way that he could escape.

Right as he was preparing to use some extreme methods to make a last-ditch effort to free himself, Lu Chuanfeng suddenly swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of blue light that swept over Han Li's body like a whirlwind, melting away all of the ice around him.

A bewildered look appeared on Han Li's face, and he immediately withdrew his Essence Fire Raven into his body while simultaneously concealing his own aura.

"There's no need to be so cautious. Here in my spirit domain, no one will be able to detect your aura from the outside," Lu Chuanfeng reassured.

"You're from the Reincarnation Palace as well?" Han Li asked with a wary look in his eyes.

"You really are just as excessively cautious as the rumors say. That's right, I'm a member of a Reincarnation Palace, and I've been lurking in the Heavenly Court as a mole for countless years, but I've most definitely been exposed now," Lu Chuanfeng replied with a smile.

A hesitant look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he swept his gaze over the severely ravaged palace.

"If you have any questions, then feel free to ask me. There are some things that you're entitled to know," Lu Chuanfeng said in a nonchalant manner.

"Is this what the Reincarnation Palace has been plotting all this time? Surely this is way too much effort just to kill a Heavenly Court immortal envoy," Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows.

"Of course not. It would be a massive waste to expose both myself and Immortal Lord Heavenly Star just to kill that incompetent fool. This is just a part of the mission. The palace master has told me that you're to play no further part in the mission, so you don't need to know what happens next," Lu Chuanfeng replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly in befuddlement upon hearing this. Why had the master of the Reincarnation Palace specifically mentioned him?

He chose not to articulate this question, instead asking, "How do we clean up this mess? Surely it won't be long before the Nine Origins Temple finds out what's happened here."

"Like I said earlier, no one can sense anything within my spirit domain from the outside, and I'm going to completely erase all signs of what happened here, so it'll take some time for the Nine Origins Temple to piece together what happened. In any case, they're supposed to find out. Otherwise, things are still not quite chaotic enough," Lu Chuanfeng replied.

In stark contrast with his usual modest and benevolent demeanor, he was looking much more casual and free-spirited.

With a flick of his wrist, he tossed an object at Han Li, who caught it after a brief hesitation to discover that it was the identity token of a Nine Origins Temple inner sect disciple.

"The identity of Chang Qi is no longer going to work, so you'll need to adopt a new one," Lu Chuanfeng instructed.

"Thank you, Senior," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Alright, you can go now," Lu Chuanfeng said with a dismissive wave, and it was as if a weight had been lifted from his shoulders after shedding his disguise.

Han Li swiped a hand over his own face, and his facial features warped into those of an average-looking young man with a pair of long and narrow eyes.

His clothes also transformed into a daoist robe, and he strapped the identity token to his own waist, then cupped his fist toward Lu Chuanfeng in a parting salute before departing.

As he departed, he noticed that the powderized bodies of all of the cultivators in the palace were slowly fusing into Lu Chuanfeng's spirit domain, and that their auras were slowly fading away as well.

A hint of lingering fear flashed through his eyes upon seeing this. That could've easily been the same fate that he had been met with.

After leaving the Nine Origins Pavilion, Han Li began making his way toward a forest outside the plaza.

Shortly thereafter, a streak of white light erupted out of the Nine Origins Pavilion, and the entire building collapsed with a thunderous commotion, raising an enormous cloud of dust and debris.

Chapter 1231: Venturing Through the Lion's Den

Around fifteen minutes later.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on an enormous tree in a secluded forest in the Nine Origins Temple, making sure to conceal himself under the tree's dense canopy.

The jade slip that had been given to him by Lu Chuanfeng was pressed tightly against his glabella, and moments later, he removed the jade slip from his own forehead, then contemplated his situation for a while longer before reopening his eyes.

The jade slip contained a map of the Nine Origins Temple, and the location where Jin Tong was possibly being imprisoned had been clearly marked out. It was a restricted area of the Nine Origins Temple that wasn't easily accessible even to the core disciples and elders of the sect.

After some contemplation, Han Li pulled out another jade slip, then examined its contents briefly before nodding to himself.

The map provided by the Reincarnation Palace isn't much different from Lan Yan's, so it looks like it hasn't been tampered with. The problem is that Jin Tong is being imprisoned in a very troublesome location...

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out in the distance, accompanied by the sounds of a fierce battle.

The Reincarnation Palace must've made a massive move to have stirred up this much chaos in a superpower like the Nine Origins Temple, Han Li thought to himself as he observed the unfolding chaos in the distance from the top of the tree.

After taking a moment to gather his bearings, he sprang up into the air, but instead of ascending far into the heavens, he skipped from tree to tree, traveling toward a nearby mountain.

At the moment, the Nine Origins Temple had been infiltrated by large numbers of masked, black-robed figures, and what was once an immortal paradise was currently being ravaged by the flames of war.

As Han Li traveled deeper and deeper into the Nine Origins Temple, he passed by some important locations, all of which had been infiltrated by powerful Reincarnation Palace cultivators, and there were even some Great Encompassment cultivators among them.

The Nine Origins Temple had naturally also sent out hordes of elders and disciples to oppose the intruders, and all of the restrictions in the sect had also been activated.

However, it was clear that the Reincarnation Palace had prepared extensively for this invasion, and due to the mass unrest that had arisen across the entire greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, many powerful cultivators of the Nine Origins Temple had been sent out to fulfill various duties. As a result, the Nine Origins Temple had been caught completely off guard and was severely short-handed.

Then again, who could've possibly imagined that the almighty Nine Origins Temple would ever come under attack?

The Reincarnation Palace had to invest a tremendous amount of resources to stage this attack, and with that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but wonder what the Reincarnation Palace's true objective was.

Initially, the disciples of the Nine Origins Temple were caught off guard by the attack and were forced into retreat, but under the leadership of the sect's elders, they quickly rallied and took advantage of the arrays littered throughout the sect to retaliate against the intruders, resulting in a temporary impasse.

Han Li had no desire to take part in the conflict, and he was racing through the Nine Origins Temple under the guise of an unremarkable disciple.

Given the widespread pandemonium throughout the entire sect, no one paid any attention to him, and at his current cultivation base, no one below the Great Encompassment Stage could hope to delay him.

Before long, Han Li had ventured very deep into the Nine Origins Temple, and no Reincarnation Palace cultivators had been able to get this far yet.

He slowed down slightly as he activated his black mask's concealment ability, transforming him into a near-invisible shadow that wasn't giving off even the slightest bit of aura.

An elated look appeared on his face upon seeing this, and he continued to fly onward.

Even though no Reincarnation Palace cultivators had appeared here, the Nine Origins Temple was still taking no chances, having activated all of the defensive and detection restrictions in case of a potential Reincarnation Palace infiltration.

Fortunately, Han Li was able to sneak through undetected thanks to his tremendous spiritual sense and Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Close to half a day later, he descended near a mountain, then concealed himself in an obscure location before casting his gaze into the distance.

Up ahead were a pair of huge golden mountains that extended all the way up into the clouds like a pair of gargantuan pillars that were supporting the heavens, and the two mountains were connected by a passageway.

The pair of mountains were surrounded by a boundless expanse of golden mist that stretched as far as the eyes could see in either direction.

According to the map of the Nine Origins Temple given to him by Lan Yan, this was the Golden Jade Pass, the entrance to the inner temple.

There was a very clear divide between the inner and outer temples of the Nine Origins Temple, and the inner temple was the true center of the Nine Origins Temple, only accessible to the high-ranking members of the sect and a select few elite disciples.

According to the information given to him by the Reincarnation Palace, Jin Tong was currently being held captive in a restricted area in the inner temple.

This boundless expanse of golden mist was a super restriction in the Nine Origins Temple that was said to have been set up by the Nine Origins Dao Ancestor himself, and one had to pass through it in order to access the inner temple.

There were a total of three entrances like the Golden Jade Pass in the Nine Origins Temple, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he observed the Golden Jade Pass.

At this moment, the passageway of the Golden Jade Pass was tightly shut behind a thick, golden, light barrier, beyond which stood a horde of cultivators clad in suits of golden armor.

Why has the entrance been closed? Is it because of the Reincarnation Palace invasion?

After some contemplation, he released his spiritual sense into his Flower Branch domain to contact Lan Yan and inform her of the current state of the Golden Jade Pass.

"Given the current situation, it's no surprise that the Golden Jade Pass has been closed. All of the important locations in the Nine Origins Temple are in the inner sect, so it naturally has to be protected with extra vigilance," Lan Yan explained.

"Do you have a way to get me through this place?" Han Li asked.

A hesitant look appeared on Lan Yan's face.

She had revealed a great deal of information about the Nine Origins Temple to Han Li in order to save Lan Yuanzi, but none of those pieces of information had been of particular importance.

However, the Golden Jade Pass was different in that it concerned the core secrets of the Nine Origins Temple, and if it were to come to light that she had revealed such secrets to an outsider, then that would be regarded as an unforgivable transgression by the Nine Origins Temple.

Han Li could sense Lan Yan's reservations, and he smiled as he said, "Right now, the entire Nine Origins Temple is in a state of pandemonium, so no one is going to notice anything that happens here. On top of that, you won't even have to reveal yourself, so how could anyone possibly suspect you?"

Lan Yan still appeared rather hesitant, but she quickly made up her mind as she said, "That may be the case, but there are countless cultivators with unfathomable abilities in the Nine Origins Temple, even some who are adept in the art of divination, so no matter what precautions I take, there's no guarantee that my involvement won't be exposed. I can tell you everything that I know about the Nine Origins Temple, but on two conditions."

"What are your conditions?" Han Li asked.

"My first condition is that you have to ask Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul to save my brother," Lan Yan said.

At this moment, both Weeping Soul and Xiaobai were with Lan Yan in the Flower Branch domain, while Qu Lin was cultivating in the pavilion, around which Weeping Soul had set up numerous layers of restrictions.

Weeping Soul was still rather apprehensive when it came to Qu Lin.

Weeping Soul communicated with Han Li briefly through voice transmission, then nodded as she said, "I can do that."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul," Lan Yan said in an excited manner as she extended a grateful bow toward Weeping Soul.

"What's your second condition?" Han Li asked.

"After exposing so many of the Nine Origins Temple's secrets, I can't stay here any longer, so I want you to take my brother and I under your wing," Lan Yan requested, and Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this.

"You want me to take you in?" Han Li asked in a surprised manner, and Weeping Soul and Xiaobai were clearly quite surprised as well.

"That's right. Over time, I've developed a decent understanding of your powers and personality, and I'm confident that you can protect me and my brother. Only with this guarantee from you can I reveal more secrets of the Nine Origins Temple to you without any reservations," Lan Yan replied in a calm manner.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he offered no response.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he decided, "I'm willing to take you and your brother under my protection, but I'll have to plant certain restrictions into your souls as a safety precaution. Of course, if I deem the two of you to be trustworthy at some point, then I'll remove the restrictions. On top of that, I won't provide any assistance to your future cultivation, so you'll have to take care of that yourselves."

"That's fine," Lan Yan immediately agreed without any hesitation.

Han Li was rather surprised by her willingness to agree to these terms, but he didn't think anything of it as he instructed Weeping Soul to carry out the necessary procedure.

Weeping Soul began to chant an incantation, and a ball of black light flew out of her hand, then quickly transformed into a black ring with countless tiny, black runes dancing around inside.

In the blink of an eye, the ring transformed into a streak of black light that vanished into Lan Yan's glabella at her behest.

Lan Yan shuddered as her complexion noticeably paled, but she remained calm and accepted the restrictions placed upon her soul.

"You've definitely made the right decision by choosing to follow Master, Fellow Daoist Lan," Weeping Soul said with a warm smile, and Xiaobai also chimed in in agreement and encouragement.

"Alright, now that I've agreed to your conditions, please tell me everything you know about the Golden Jade Pass, Fellow Daoist Lan," Han Li said.

"The Golden Jade Pass is an important checkpoint that one must pass through en route to the inner temple. Only with the permission of the abbot, the two assistant abbots, and the four holy envoys can one enter through it, but given the special state of emergency that the temple is currently in, perhaps things will be different. With an appropriate reason, perhaps the guards inside will be willing to open the pass for us," Lan Yan replied.

Chapter 1232: Entering the Pass

"I don't know much about the Nine Origins Temple, so I can't think of any appropriate reason. Do you have one in mind, Fellow Daoist Lan?" Han Li asked.

"If there were any other guards stationed here, then I would be powerless to do anything as well, but given that it's the Golden Vein Guards that are here, I may have a trick up my sleeve," Lan Yan replied with a faint smile.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he began discussing the matter with Lan Yan through voice transmission.

After some contemplation, Han Li nodded as he decided, "It's a little risky, but it's worth a try."

"Master, even if you can fool the guards and enter the inner temple, the Reincarnation Palace cultivators are still yet to reach this point. If you enter the inner temple on your own and are discovered, then you'll be in a very perilous situation. Is this not too risky?" Weeping Soul interjected in a concerned manner.

"Given the current situation, I presume that there won't be too many powerful cultivators in the inner temple, so this is a prime opportunity. Having said that, your concerns are not unwarranted. As a safety precaution, I'll contact the Reincarnation Palace..."

All of a sudden, Han Li's voice trailed off here, and a faint smile appeared on his face, but he immediately concealed it.

"What's wrong, Master?" Weeping Soul asked in a puzzled manner.

"Nothing. Looks like I won't need to contact the Reincarnation Palace, after all," Han Li replied.

Weeping Soul was still rather confused to hear this, but she didn't ask any further questions.

"Come out, Lan Yan," Han Li instructed as he swept a sleeve through the air, and Lan Yan appeared out of thin air beside him.

At the moment, Lan Yan was wearing a blue cloak that concealed her face and body, and the two of them drifted down in to land in front of the Golden Jade Pass.

"Who's there?" an imposing man clad in a suit of golden armor yelled from the other side of the golden light barrier.

The man was around ten feet tall, and his entire body was riddled with bands of rippling muscle. There was also a large beard on his face, within which the individual strands of hair resembled black, steel needles, presenting a fearsome sight to behold.

His cultivation base was just as impressive as his physique, standing at the early-Great Encompassment Stage.

"It's me, Elder Qi," Lan Yan said as she lowered her hood to reveal her face.

"Lan Yan? What are you doing here?" the man asked in a perplexed manner.

"Please open the Golden Jade Pass, Elder Qi. I have important information to report to the sect," Lan Yan said in solemn manner.

"The three passes are closed due to the enemy invasion, and no one is allowed to enter or exit unless they have a special passage token. Do you have such a token?" Elder Qi asked.

"I was instructed by Holy Envoy Miao Fa to gather information on the enemy, and due to the rushed nature of the situation, she didn't grant me a token. However, the information that I've gathered is very important, so please let me through," Lan Yan said as she flipped a hand over to reveal a green badge.

The badge belonged to Immortal Lord Miao Fa, and a respectful look instantly appeared on Elder Qi's face at the sight of it.

The four holy envoys were only below the abbot and assistant abbots in status in the Nine Origins Temple, far superior to an ordinary elder like him.

As for what Lan Yan had just told him, Elder Qi didn't suspect her. Just like the Lan siblings, he had also been a vagrant cultivator, and the three of them had become acquaintances after joining the Nine Origins Temple. From there, Elder Qi had gone to the Golden Vein Guards, while the Lan siblings had been assigned to the shadow guard.

The three of them had remained in contact with one another, so Elder Qi was aware that Lan Yan had already been moved out of the shadow guard and was currently directly serving Immortal Lord Miao Fa, so it made sense that she had been sent out to gather information.

"You may be acting under Immortal Lord Miao Fa’s instructions, but even so, I'm afraid I cannot bend the rules for you," Elder Qi said after a brief hesitation.

"Elder Qi, the information that I've gathered is extremely important and concerns the objectives of the enemies outside. However, given my lowly status, I must report this information to Holy Envoy Miao Fa, and only she can relay it to the higher-ups of the sect.

“You've always wanted to enter the panel of elders, haven't you? If you do me this favor here, I can ask Holy Envoy Miao Fa to put in a good word for you with the abbot, and you'll be all but assured of a spot on the panel of elders," Lan Yan said through voice transmission.

While the Golden Jade Pass was an extremely formidable restriction, it didn't keep out sound.

A torn look appeared on Elder Qi's face, and he was clearly tempted by the proposition.

"You and I go way back, Elder Qi. I'm sure you're aware of my character. I can't say I'm someone who'll remain true to my word at all times, but I'm also not a deceitful charlatan, either. If you let me through to report this piece of information to Holy Envoy Miao Fa, I'll be rewarded handsomely as well, so this is mutually beneficial for both of us," Lan Yan urged.

Elder Qi was still a little hesitant, and he said, "In that case, please contact Holy Envoy Miao Fa and inform her of the situation so she can issue a direct order to open the pass."

"I've been trying to get into contact with her this entire time, but there's been no response, so she must be busy with something," Lan Yan said as she pulled out a blue communication array plate that was flashing with blue spiritual light, but just as she had said, there was no response being received.

Elder Qi's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Both of the assistant abbots and the other holy envoys have also sent out people to gather information on the enemy outside. If they gather the same piece of information, they'll be the ones to receive the reward, so this is a very fleeting window of opportunity that must be captured now!" Lan Yan said as a look of urgency appeared on her face.

Elder Qi shuddered slightly upon hearing this, but he was still unable to make a decision.

Right at this moment, a projection suddenly emerged from Lan Yan's blue array plate, and it was one of none other than Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

An ecstatic look appeared on Lan Yan's face upon seeing this, and Elder Qi's eyes lit up as well.

"Why have you contacted me, Lan Yan? I'm very busy right now, so keep it concise," Immortal Lord Miao Fa said in a cold voice.

"I was able to gather an important piece of information on the enemy that I must report to you in person, but the Golden Jade Pass is currently closed, so please ask Elder Qi to make an exception and grant me passage," Lan Yan requested.

"Open the Golden Jade Pass for her, Elder Qi. I'll explain the situation to the abbot," Immortal Lord Miao Fa instructed as she turned her gaze to Elder Qi.

"Yes, Holy Envoy Miao Fa," Elder Qi hurriedly answered, and the projection of Immortal Lord Miao Fa vanished from the array plate.

At this moment, Weeping Soul was inside the Flower Branch domain, having taken on the appearance of Immortal Lord Miao Fa, and there was a communication array plate in front of her that was identical in appearance to Lan Yan's.

After reverting back to her original appearance, she murmured to herself, "Hopefully everything goes well for Master outside."

"You can rest assured, Big Sister Weeping Soul. Master is very well prepared, and the timing is also just right. On top of that, Elder Qi is completely enamored by the carrot that's been dangled in front of him, so there's no way he would ever consider the possibility that someone could've posed as Immortal Lord Miao Fa to deceive him," Xiaobai reassured, and Weeping Soul nodded in response.

In front of the Golden Jade Pass.

"Now that Holy Envoy Miao Fa has spoken, please open the restriction for me, Elder Qi," Lan Yan requested loudly as she stowed her communication array plate away, as if he she were intentionally speaking for everyone else to hear.

Elder Qi was quite grateful for this as it showed all of his subordinates that he had followed correct official procedure in the matter, thereby giving his actions a seal of legitimacy.

Right as he was about to issue an order to open the pass, he suddenly noticed Han Li standing nearby. "Hold on, who's that?"

Han Li was currently displaying a very weak aura, and Elder Qi had been focused on his conversation with Lan Yan just now, so he had failed to notice Han Li's presence this entire time.

"His name is Zhou Yu, and he's an inner sect disciple of our temple. He served as an eyewitness to the piece of information that I'm about to present, so he has to accompany me to see Holy Envoy Miao Fa," Lan Yan explained.

"Disciple Zhou Yu pays his respects to Elder Qi," Han Li hurriedly said with a feigned look of fear and unease on his face as he extended a respectful bow toward Elder Qi before presenting his identity token.

The token contained the visage and name of its owner, but Han Li had already adopted Zhou Yu's physical appearance, so he wasn't afraid of being exposed.

Unfortunately, he hadn't personally met Zhou Yu, so he never had a chance to absorb Zhou Yu's aura, thereby leading to an imperfect disguise.

Elder Qi took a glance at Han Li, then flipped a hand over to produce a golden jade tablet, which released a beam of golden light that passed through the restriction to fall upon the identity token in Han Li's hand.

A burst of golden light instantly began to emanate from the token, and a projection emerged from it, one that was identical to Han Li's current appearance.

Elder Qi carefully compared the two while also meticulously examining Han Li with his spiritual sense, and only after verifying that there was nothing amiss did he give a nod before stowing the jade tablet away.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief as he stowed away his identity token as well.

"Open the restriction!" Elder Qi ordered, and eight golden-robed cultivators emerged from behind him.

Each of them was holding a large, golden flag, and the flags collectively unfurled at their behest, releasing bursts of radiant, rippling golden light that were formed by countless tiny, golden runes.

The waves of golden light quickly converged to form a ball of golden light roughly the size of a human head, following which Elder Qi swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of golden light, which contained a golden badge.

He cast an incantation seal into the badge, and it also began to glow with dazzling, golden light, following which it released a beam of translucent light that vanished into the golden ball.

The ball immediately split up into eight pieces, each of which transformed into a golden rune that was round a foot in size, and all eight of the runes fused into the golden light barrier in the Golden Jade Pass.

The light barrier instantly began to flash erratically, following which an opening that was only wide enough for one person to pass through appeared over its surface.

A hint of elation appeared in Lan Yan's eyes upon seeing this, and she immediately flew through the opening, followed closely by Han Li.

As soon as the two of them passed through the restriction, Elder Qi immediately issued an order to close the pass again, but before the order could be carried out, disaster suddenly struck.

Chapter 1233: Search

Right after Han Li and Lan Yan passed through the restriction, a burst of dark red light suddenly shot out of thin air outside the entrance of the Golden Jade Pass, and it flew through the opening in the golden light barrier before anyone had a chance to react.

"Close the entrance! Hurry!" Elder Qi called out in an alarmed voice upon seeing this, and a streak of golden light shot out of the badge in his hand before vanishing into the golden light barrier.

At the same time, the eight golden-robed cultivators frantically swept their flags through the air, and the opening in the light barrier was instantly closed.

Simultaneously, Elder Qi opened his mouth to release two streaks of white light, which transformed into a pair of giant, white swords that flew through the air at an astonishing speed, catching up to the streak of dark red light in the blink of an eye.

However, right as it was about to be struck by the pair of swords, waves of dark red light suddenly erupted out of the streak of red light.

The white light emanating from the two swords instantly melted away upon contact with the waves of dark red light, while the swords themselves were sent flying back through the air.

Immediately thereafter, Wyrm 3 emerged from the streak of dark red light.

A stunned look appeared on Lan Yan's face at this abrupt turn of events, but Han Li remained as composed and steadfast as ever, as if he had already anticipated this.

Wyrm 3 took a glance in Han Li's direction, and an imperceptible smile appeared on her face as she swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light.

A rapid stream of Reincarnation Palace cultivators came pouring out of the door of light, and in the blink of an eye, there were already hundreds of them, with more still to come.

"Seize control of the Golden Jade Pass!" Wyrm 3 instructed, and the Reincarnation Palace cultivators immediately began attacking Elder Qi and the other Golden Vein Guards.

Elder Qi was furious to see this, but he had no choice but to engage the enemy in battle.

Thankfully, there were over a thousand Golden Vein Guards stationed at the Golden Jade Pass, so they held a numbers advantage.

In the blink of an eye, a ferocious battle had broken out, and Han Li grabbed onto the stunned Lan Yan before flying away into the distance.

"Thanks for your help, Fellow Daoist Han. I'll be sure to compensate you once the mission is over."

Han Li paid no heed to the gleeful voice of Wyrm 3 that had rung out in his mind as he flew away with Lan Yan in tow, slipping away unnoticed by everyone else.

"Fellow Daoist Han, did you already know that those Reincarnation Palace cultivators were going to appear?" Lan Yan asked.

"Sometimes, knowing too much can be a curse rather than a blessing, Fellow Daoist Lan," Han Li replied in a cold voice, and he was also feeling a little dismayed.

It seemed like Wyrm 3 had been following them in secret all along. She knew that he had to travel into the inner temple in order to rescue Jin Tong, and she had used that to her advantage to seize the Golden Jade Pass. With that in mind, it was clear that his black mask had to have been tampered with, allowing Wyrm 3 to track him.

Lan Yan could sense Han Li's displeasure at the situation, and she hurriedly changed the subject as she said, "Let's go and save Jin Tong. Do you know where she's being held?"

"According to the information that was given to me, Jin Tong is currently being imprisoned in the Ghost Valley," Han Li replied as he offered Lan Yan the jade slip that contained the map of the inner temple.

"The Ghost Valley? That's the place where Holy Envoy Gui Lingzi cultivates!" Lan Yan exclaimed in an alarmed manner.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but it wasn't all that surprising a revelation to him.

Jin Tong had been captured by Gui Lingzi, so it made sense that she was being held captive on Gui Lingzi's territory.

"Gui Lingzi is a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator, and the ghostly law powers that he's mastered make him very difficult to deal with, so he's ranked at the very top among the four holy envoys. There's a decent chance that he's currently not in the Ghost Valley, given the Reincarnation Palace invasion, but we still have to plan for the worst," Lan Yan cautioned in a concerned manner.

"Of course. Rest assured, I am not taking Gui Lingzi lightly at all," Han Li reassured as he raised a hand to release a plume of black mist that encompassed both of them.

In the blink of an eye, the two of them transformed into a pair of invisible shadows before continuing onward.

Not only could Han Li use the powers of his black mask on himself, he could also use them on others as long as they were in sufficiently close proximity to him.

An intrigued look appeared in Lan Yan's eyes upon seeing this, but she then quickly refocused her attention on the task at hand.

In contrast with the dense clusters of grand and majestic buildings in the outer temple, there were far fewer buildings in the inner inner temple, the preservation of nature seemingly taking higher priority, but the world's origin qi here was far more abundant than in the outer temple.

Some restrictions had been activated in the inner temple, but not as many as there were in the outer temple, perhaps because the cultivators of the Nine Origins Temple felt like all of the restrictions in the outer temple would've been enough to keep the inner temple safe from infiltration.

This suited Han Li and Lan Yan just fine, and they were able to make rapid progress.

Close to a day later, they descended near a valley, all of the soil and rocks around which were completely black in color.

There was also a dense blanket of dark clouds hanging in the sky above the valley, and not only were they as viscous as water, their black coloration indicated that they most likely contained lethal poison as well.

Bone-chilling gusts of yin wind were sweeping out of the valley, producing a piercing, screeching sound that fluctuated in pitch and volume, striking fear and unease into the heart of the listener. At the same time, there were also bursts of violent intent churning within the gusts of yin wind, and it was as if this place had been taken straight from the depths of hell.

Even from very far away, Han Li and Lan Yan could still feel the malicious, ghostly qi emanating from the valley, threatening to pierce into their bodies like countless glacial needles, but thankfully, the hostile conditions were still not too much to bear for them.

"So this is the Ghost Valley?" Han Li asked as he swept his gaze over the surrounding area.

"That's right. I've never been here before, but I've heard stories about this place, and this is also the precise location marked out on the map," Lan Yan confirmed in a confident manner.

Han Li nodded in response, then closed his eyes to try and detect Jin Tong's presence.

A long while later, he reopened his eyes with his brows tightly furrowed.

"Are you unable to sense her?" Lan Yan asked.

Han Li nodded with a dark expression.

He had chalked up his inability to sense Jin Tong back in Gilded City to distance, but the fact that he was still unable to detect Jin Tong's presence even at such close proximity was very strange.

Could it be that Jin Tong was currently trapped within a seal that made her undetectable to others, or had the Reincarnation Palace fed him false information?

This valley was quite a foreboding place, even to him, and the possibility of an enemy mid-Great Encompassment cultivator lurking inside was even more cause for apprehension.

"Master, let's confirm if Jin Tong is actually in this Ghost Valley before we go in. There's no guarantee that the Reincarnation Palace's information is correct," Weeping Soul communicated to Han Li through voice transmission, and Han Li nodded in agreement.

"Let me out, Master. I was with Boss for a very long time, so I may be able to sense her," Xiaobai suddenly said, and Han Li duly obliged, releasing him from the Flower Branch domain.

As soon as he emerged from the domain, Xiaobai immediately sat down with his eyes closed, and a layer of faint, white light surfaced over his body.

A short while later, he reopened his eyes with a deflated expression as he shook his head and sighed, "I can't sense her, either."

Han Li wasn't surprised by this outcome. He had nurtured Jin Tong from a tiny Gold Devouring Beetle, so if even he couldn't sense her, then Xiaobai had no chance.

"What do we do now, Master?" Xiaobai asked in an agitated manner.

"It's alright, we may not be able to sense her, but there's someone who definitely can," Han Li replied with a faint smile, then made a hand seal, and the restrictions around the bamboo pavilion in the Flower Branch domain quickly dissipated.

A figure flew out from within, and it was none other than Qu Lin.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li summoned Qu Lin directly out of the domain.

Qu Lin was far from pleased at the way that he had been treated, and he said in a disgruntled manner, "I agreed to accompany you on your travels, not to be held captive as your prisoner!"

"It appears Weeping Soul was excessively cautious in her treatment of you. Please allow me to apologize on her behalf," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

Qu Lin gave a cold harrumph, but spoke no further on the matter as he inspected his surroundings before asking, "Where are we right now?"

"We are currently in the Nine Origins Temple, so if you don't wish to be detected, I suggest you don't release your spiritual sense," Han Li replied.

Qu Lin raised an eyebrow upon hearing this.

"If I recall correctly, aren't you currently a wanted fugitive of the Nine Origins Temple? How courageous of you to have ventured into the Nine Origins Temple given your wanted status!"

"I had some matters that I had to attend to here," Han Li said with a faint smile, making no mention of the Reincarnation Palace invasion.

"So why have you chosen to set me free at a time like this?" Qu Lin asked.

"I have a favor to ask of you, Fellow Daoist Qu. According to my sources, there may be a Gold Devouring Immortal in the valley up ahead. However, the valley is riddled with restrictions, and I'm unable to detect its aura. As a fellow Gold Devouring Immortal, I was hoping that you would have better luck in the endeavor," Han Li replied, keeping his ties with Jin Tong a secret.

Qu Lin's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, following which a hint of suspicion appeared on his face as he asked, "Are you planning to capture this Gold Devouring Immortal?"

"Not at all. It's just that I once had a run-in with this Gold Devouring Immortal, and it took something very important from me, so I'm here to recover it," Han Li replied.

"I see. It should be a simple task for me to see if there's a Gold Devouring Immortal in the valley up ahead," Qu Lin replied, then closed his eyes momentarily as a layer of golden light began flashing over his body.

A brief moment later, his eyes sprang open as a hint of elation flashed through them.

"There is indeed a Gold Devouring Immortal in the valley up ahead, but it's underground," Qu Lin said.

Chapter 1234: Delving Deep Underground

"Is that true?" Han Li asked in an elated manner.

"I wouldn't dare to proclaim full confidence in anything else, but when it comes to finding other Gold Devouring Immortals, there's no one I would count on more than myself," Qu Lin replied in a confident manner.

Unbeknownst to him, Han Li's question was posed at Weeping Soul in the Flower Branch domain.

"Judging from his soul fluctuations, he seems to be telling the truth," Weeping Soul verified.

"That's great! Take us to that Gold Devouring Immortal right away!" Xiaobai exclaimed in an excited manner.

Han Li glared at Xiaobai in a stern manner, and the latter stuck out his tongue in a sheepish manner, realizing that he had reacted with too much excitement.

"Can I trouble you to lead the way, Fellow Daoist Qu?" Han Li asked.

"We're in the Nine Origins Temple right now, and the valley up ahead looks like it's fraught with peril. Don't you think you're asking too much for me to serve as your guide?" Qu Lin scoffed with a cold sneer.

Han Li wasn't irked by his derisive demeanor. Instead, a faint smile appeared on his face as he said, "I understand that this is indeed a rather tall order. What would you like from me in exchange?"

"I've reached a critical juncture in my cultivation recently, and I require a great deal of resources. I won't ask for too much, just give me fifty million Immortal Origin Stones or the equivalent value in natural treasures, and I'll take the plunge for you," Qu Lin said with a smile.

"Fifty million Immortal Origin Stones?! This is blatant extortion!" Xiaobai yelled in an enraged manner.

Qu Lin paid no heed to Xiaobai as he said, "I've stated my price, the decision is up to you, Fellow Daoist Han."

"Alright, I agree to your condition, but I can only give you the Immortal Origin Stones once we've found that Gold Devouring Immortal," Han Li replied.

"Looks like we have ourselves a deal then!" Qu Lin chuckled.

"In that case, let's enter the valley right away. Xiaobai, you go stay in the Flower Branch domain with Weeping Soul. Fellow Daoist Qu, Fellow Daoist Lan, and I will enter the valley," Han Li said.

Xiaobai wanted to protest and ask to be allowed to remain outside, but he was deterred by the sight of Han Li's stern gaze.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li sent Xiaobai and Weeping Soul into the Flower Branch domain, following which he used his black mask to conceal himself, Qu Lin, and Lan Yan before drifting down to the entrance of the valley.

As soon as the trio entered the valley, a gust of yin wind that was tinged with incredibly potent baleful qi and resentment instantly swept over them.

A horrific scene filled with mountains of heads and never-ending rivers of blood instantly filled their minds, threatening to devour their souls.

Han Li was able to dispel the killing intent by channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique, while Qu Lin was also able to do the same with ease as a layer of golden light flashed over his body.

In contrast, Lan Yan's complexion paled slightly, but she was also able to somehow steady herself.

"Fellow Daoist Lan looks a little frail. Are you sure it's a good idea to have her accompany us, Fellow Daoist Han?" Qu Lin asked.

"Fellow Daoist Lan, if you're unable to bear the baleful qi in this place, then you can take shelter in the Flower Branch domain as well," Han Li said.

"It's alright, I can persevere. I know the most about the Nine Origins Temple, so I can be of use by your side," Lan Yan replied with a determined shake of her head.

"Alright, but don't force yourself," Han Li said, and the three of them continued deeper into the valley.

Inside the valley was a barren, stone landscape that was devoid of buildings, and there was also a complete lack of vegetation from the constant ravages of the yin wind.

Upon reaching this point, Qu Lin suddenly stopped in his tracks and declared, "This should be the place."

"I've heard that Gui Lingzi constructed his palatial manor underground, but where's the entrance?" Lan Yan asked as she scoured her gaze over the surrounding area.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to inspect the area upon hearing this, but he refrained from releasing his spiritual sense.

Before long, he discovered something amiss, and he made his way over to a large, black rock.

"That's the entrance?" Lan Yan asked.

She hadn't detected anything abnormal about the rock.

Han Li offered no response as he made a grabbing motion with one hand, and five streaks of azure light shot out of his fingertips, each of which transformed into an azure sword projection that was several dozen feet in size before crashing down upon the rock with tremendous power.

A burst of radiant, black light erupted out of the rock, forming a pillar of black light to oppose the azure sword projections.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he swept his other sleeve through the air, releasing a bolt of golden lightning that instantly struck the side of the pillar of black light, causing it to disintegrate.

The black rock down below also quickly fell apart, and the ground beneath it collapsed to reveal a black cave that was several dozen feet in size.

Inside the cave was a winding staircase that led deep underground.

"It's very impressive that you were able to identify that secret entrance so quickly, Fellow Daoist Han," Qu Lin praised.

"There's no way I would've found this secret entrance if you hadn't narrowed it down to this area. Please continue to lead the way, Fellow Daoist Qu," Han Li said.

Qu Lin didn't waste any more time with words as he leaped into the cave.

Gusts of black yin wind were sweeping through the air down below, forming a series of vortexes of different sizes within the cave, and these gusts of yin wind were around twice as formidable as the ones outside.

The three of them hurriedly conjured up layers of protective spiritual light over their bodies to ward off the gusts of yin wind, and Han Li noticed that the walls on either side of the cave were encased in a layer of black ice that was giving off an incredibly potent glacial aura.

"This is Profound Yin Ice, a type of ice that only takes shape in places with an extreme abundance of baleful qi and ghostly qi, and it's an exceptional material for refining ghostly immortal treasures," Han Li remarked.

There was a very large quantity of Profound Yin Ice here, and if all of it could be harvested, then it could be sold for a sizable amount of wealth. However, that wasn't the priority, and given the peril that could be afoot at every turn in this place, the three of them chose not to do any harvesting.

The cave was very deep, and the three of them only reached the end of the staircase after walking for a full fifteen minutes, upon which a square hall that was around two hundred to three hundred feet in size appeared up ahead.

There were several fist-sized white stones embedded into the ceiling of the hall, providing just barely enough light to illuminate the surrounding environment.

The ground and walls of this place were all paved with black tiles with some patterns engraved upon them, and the entire hall was completely empty, with the exception of a dark passageway at the very back that led somewhere unknown.

The howling ying wind gradually abated here, but the ghostly qi in the air was even more potent.

Han Li and Qu Lin were still able to fend for themselves just fine, but despite her best efforts, Lan Yan was beginning to struggle. Her body was trembling, while her teeth were chattering audibly, and her blood was beginning to freeze in her veins.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon noticing this.

Right at this moment, a purple bead suddenly appeared in his hand amid a flash of dreamy, purple light.

"Give this to Lan Yan to help her ward off the ghostly qi," Weeping Soul said to Han Li through voice transmission, and Han Li did as he was told, tossing the purple bead at Lan Yan.

"You can use that to protect yourself from the ghostly qi here."

Lan Yan faltered slightly as she caught the purple bead, then injected her immortal spiritual power into it, and a layer of faint, purple light instantly appeared over her entire body, keeping most of the surrounding ghostly qi at bay.

"Thank you," Lan Yan said with a grateful sigh of relief.

With that, the three of them continued onward, quickly passing through the hall before entering the passageway on the other side.

Up ahead was a crossroads that led in three different directions, all of which were so dark that Han Li couldn't see to the end even with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he extended his spiritual sense into the three paths, but as soon as his spiritual sense left his body, a burst of peculiar, glacial qi instantly began to infiltrate his body, spreading along his spiritual sense toward his soul.

"Make sure you don't release your spiritual sense here," Han Li hurriedly warned as he withdrew his spiritual sense while channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique to eradicate the glacial qi that had infiltrated his consciousness.

Lan Yan nodded in response, seemingly very thankful for the warning, while Qu Lin offered no response, seemingly having already made the same discovery as Han Li.

"This place appears to be enormous and riddled with restrictions, so we'll have to count on you to serve as our navigator, Fellow Daoist Qu," Han Li said.

Qu Lin nodded in response, then closed his eyes momentarily before reopening them as he pointed to the path on the left and said, "That's the way to go."

Han Li nodded in response and began making his way down the indicated path.

This path was also very long, taking roughly fifteen minutes to traverse through, and at the end was a spacious stone hall.

Once again, the stone hall was completely empty, but there were two passageways connected to it, leading in different directions.

Qu Lin's services were employed again, and the three of them continued down the path that was pointed out by him.

This underground space was astonishingly massive, and it was filled with confounding crossroads. Thankfully, there was only yin wind and ghostly qi here, and no ghostly creatures or other hazards were encountered.

With Qu Lin leading the way, the three of them were able to make relatively smooth progress.

By Han Li's estimates, they had already traveled for several hundreds of kilometers, and according to Qu Lin, they weren't far away from where Jin Tong was.

Despite this piece of good news, Han Li was only growing more apprehensive.

The journey thus far had been far too smooth. This was the cave abode of one of the four holy envoys, so surely it shouldn't have been so easy to traverse through, particularly when Gui Lingzi himself appeared to have been absent.

With that in mind, he was making sure to be extra vigilant, keeping a close eye on his surroundings at all times.

Chapter 1235: Unexpected

At this moment, Han Li's trio was advancing through a dark passageway with Qu Lin at the forefront, walking along while keeping constant tabs on Jin Tong's location.

It didn't take long before they reached the end of the passageway, arriving in another giant stone hall.

This stone hall was tens of thousands of feet in size, but it wasn't empty like the previous ones. Instead, it was lined with two rows of huge, black stone pillars.

The stone pillars were all completely translucent, seemingly having been crafted from some type of crystalline material, and they were etched with ghostly designs that could've been array patterns or some type of text.

The two rows of stone pillars lined the entire hall, leaving only a path that was around a hundred feet wide in the center, leading deep into the hall.

Given the dim environment, it was only just barely possible to make out an azure gate at the very back of the hall.

Han Li stood cautiously at the entrance of the hall as he asked, "Do you know what this place is, Fellow Daoist Lan?"

Lan Yan shook her head in response.

"The inscriptions on these stone pillars seem to be the legendary infernal text," Qu Lin remarked as he closely examined the black stone pillars.

"Infernal text?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Infernal text is said to be text used in the underworld. I just so happened to see it by chance in an ancient scripture a very long time ago," Qu Lin explained.

"Does the underworld really exist?" Han Li asked.

"It does. It's said to be the place where all living beings are reincarnated, but very few people can go there without first passing away, so it gradually became the stuff of legends," Qu Lin replied.

"Can you read infernal text, Fellow Daoist Qu?" Han Li asked.

This wasn't the first time that he had heard of the concept of reincarnation, and he had always been very curious about the underworld, but prior to this, he had never found any evidence that it truly existed.

"I only know such text exists, but I'm unable to comprehend it. Having said that, it looks like these pillars were erected to form a seal, so presumably, something must be sealed inside. It should be fine as long as we don't touch them," Qu Lin said, and Han Li nodded in response.

That was his assumption as well.

However, he was unsure of whether it was safe to walk through the path between the pillars.

He activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes and even took the risk of releasing his spiritual sense once again to examine the pillars, but was unable to find anything useful.

"Are you sure that Gold Devouring Immortal is up ahead, Fellow Daoist Qu?" Han Li asked.

"I'm certain that it's nearby. However, the presence of this infernal text here makes me feel a little apprehensive. I don't know if we'll encounter some unforeseen perils up ahead, so you'll have to make the decision on whether we continue onward from here," Qu Lin replied.

"We've already made it this far, it would be a huge pity to turn around now. Having said that, this is indeed a rather strange place, so from here onward, I'll lead the way. Fellow Daoist Qu, you can follow along behind me, while Fellow Daoist Lan brings up the rear," Han Li decided.

Lan Yan naturally raised no objections to this, while Qu Lin smiled as he said, "That would be ideal. I may be a Gold Devouring Immortal, but I have no weapons other than my physical body. Your powers far exceed my own, so with you leading the way, I'm sure we'll all be safe."

"In that case, let's keep going. Make sure to be on your guard," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Han," Lan Yan replied with a faint smile, then blinked twice at Han Li while Qu Lin wasn't looking.

With that, Han Li stepped into the hall, with Qu Lin and Lan Yan trailing along behind him.

After walking for a short distance, nothing happened.

However, Han Li remained alert and vigilant as he continued onward.

Right as they reached the center of the hall, the sound of faint rustling suddenly rang out from the stone pillars on either side of them.

The sound was very faint, but given Han Li's incredibly sharp senses, he was able to hear it right away.

"Something's happening!" he yelled as a layer of protective golden light appeared over his body.

Right at this moment, a series of writhing black shadows suddenly appeared over the stone pillars in the hall, and Han Li immediately stomped a foot down onto the ground upon seeing this, propelling himself forward like a speeding arrow.

Lan Yan hurriedly followed along upon seeing this, whereas Qu Lin shot back in retreat instead.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything, streaks of black light suddenly shot out of the black shadows on the stone pillars like countless arrows, converging toward Han Li's trio from all directions.

The streaks of black light were giving off a high-pitched shriek, striking the listener with a sense of disorientation and nausea.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to stabilize his own soul, and at the same time, arcs of golden lightning emerged over his body, forming a series of golden lightning whips that lashed out in all directions to clash against the arrows of black light.

The lightning in Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had all evolved to become Cardinal Heavenly Lightning, granting them a significant power boost, and the arcs of lightning were able to eradicate the arrows of black light with ease.

Meanwhile, Lan Yan had summoned a set of around a dozen flying daggers, which were revolving around her to form an intricate array that kept the oncoming arrows of black light at bay.

As for Qu Lin, his skin had turned a pure golden color, and he simply allowed the arrows of black light to strike him as he continued to fly back in retreat.

A string of resounding thumps rang out as the streaks of black light struck his body, but they were only able to leave some faint marks behind, and no substantial damage was inflicted.

In the blink of an eye, Qu Lin had already returned to the entrance of the stone hall, and his hands began to glow with radiant, golden light as he swept them through the air.

Two bursts of golden light flew out of the palms of his hands before striking a wall in the stone hall.

There were two very shallow indentations on the wall, and they were pulverized by the two streaks of golden light.

The streaks of black light shooting out of the stone pillars instantly became over ten times brighter, and they suddenly changed directions, piercing into the ground.

All of a sudden, a series of inky black infernal text runes emerged from the ground below, forming an enormous array that was giving a bone-chilling glacial aura.

Han Li instantly felt his entire body tighten up as he plummeted down onto the ground, and at the same time, countless strands of black light rose up from the array below to envelop his entire body.

In the blink of an eye, he was completely bound and immobilized, and the immortal spiritual power in his body had also become stagnant.

Lan Yan fared even worse, falling to the ground ahead of Han Li before she was also immobilized by the black array.

"What's the meaning of this, Qu Lin?" Han Li yelled.

He had never truly trusted Qu Lin, but he hadn't anticipated that Qu Lin would be so familiar with the restrictions in this place.

It was clear that his offer to take Han Li to Jin Tong for the price of fifty million Immortal Origin Stones had been nothing more than a ruse, and his objective all along was to lead them here.

"Thank you for bringing me into the Nine Origins Temple and taking me so close to the Gold Devouring Immortal, Fellow Daoist Han. You've saved me a great deal of trouble," Qu Lin said with a gleeful smile.

"You're also searching for that Gold Devouring Immortal? Have you been here before?" Han Li asked.

"Of course I'm searching for that Gold Devouring Immortal. Us Gold Devouring Immortals can only evolve by devouring our own kind. Additionally, that Gold Devouring Immortal devoured an avatar of mine, so I have to take back the power that it took from me," Qu Lin replied with a cold smile.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

The Gold Devouring Immortal that Jin Tong had devoured earlier had to have been the avatar in question.

"That's enough chit-chat. If I stay here any longer, Gui Lingzi is going to get here. Farewell," Qu Lin said as he turned to depart.

Right at this moment, the stone gate deep within the hall abruptly sprang open with a resounding boom, and gusts of howling yin wind swept through the hall as a huge, black shadow emerged before descending upon Han Li's trio.

Han Li and Lan Yan were already immobilized on the ground, and they were even more ensnared under the weight of the black shadow, with Lan Yan even falling onto her bottom.

"Shoot! He certainly wasted no time!" Qu Lin grumbled as he rubbed his hands together, and countless streaks of translucent light that resembled sword qi erupted out of his body, then combined to form a massive, golden sword projection to strike the black shadow up above.

A gash was instantly torn into the shadow, and Qu Lin's eyes lit up as he flew back the same way he had come from as a streak of golden light.

"To think you would dare to come back here after betraying and fleeing from the Nine Origins Temple all those years ago! I'm not letting you get away again!"

A piercing voice rang out up above as a giant, black claw the size of a house appeared out of thin air before making a grab for Qu Lin.

The claw was covered in scales, and the nails of its five fingers were riddled with special runes and patterns that were giving off unmatched power, easily scratching five huge rifts into the space in its path.

A loud thump rang out as Qu Lin's body was sliced into several pieces, but those pieces of his body then each transformed into a golden beetle that was around the size of a human head before racing away in a flash, instantly vanishing into the passageway leading into the stone hall.

The black shadow up above faded away, revealing a thin and gaunt black-robed young man with a bewildered look on his face.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly at the sight of the black-robed man.

Gui Lingzi!

Chapter 1236: Ghostly Array

Gui Lingzi contemplated pursuing Qu Lin momentarily, but ultimately decided against it.

Compared with a Gold Devouring Immortal, he was more drawn to Han Li.

After all, it had been confirmed that the Heaven Controlling Vial was in Han Li's possession.

In this situation, Lan Yan was in a very awkward position.

She was a Nine Origins Temple disciple, yet she was helping an outsider invade her own sect. However, Han Li was her only hope for saving Lan Yuanzi, so she had no choice but to help him.

"A traitor like you deserves to die even more than all those Reincarnation Palace scoundrels outside!" Gui Lingzi harrumphed coldly as his gaze fell upon Lan Yan.

Lan Yan had no way to defend herself, so she could only bite her lip in silence.

At this point, she had no choice but to follow Han Li, whether that be to salvation or a bitter end.

In the face of a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator, Han Li wanted to avoid a conflict if at all possible, so he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "I'm not here to cause trouble, Senior, I'm just here to recover a spirit pet of mine. Right now, the temple is under attack, so why not let me be and go after those who truly pose a threat? I saw many Reincarnation Palace cultivators as I was coming through the Golden Jade Pass earlier."

Gui Lingzi took a cold glance at him and offered no response. It seemed like he was pondering what he was going to do with these two trapped intruders.

Han Li was naturally aware that he most likely wasn't going to be able to talk his way out of this situation, so as he was speaking, he was also scouring his surroundings with his Infernal Devilish Eyes while also secretly channeling his immortal spiritual power, searching for an opportunity to escape.

As his gaze roamed over the surrounding stone hall, he could see that the walls were riddled with strange patterns that resembled troughs of blood embedded deep into them.

After walking a lap around the array, Gui Lingzi suddenly made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and his voice began to echo around the stone hall.

As his voice rang out, a sharp screech sounded within Han Li's mind, followed by a sense of sluggishness.

At the same time, he began to hear the sound of flowing water around the stone hall, accompanied by a bloody odor permeating through the air.

Are these the effects of his soul law powers?

Han Li felt like something wasn't quite right.

He hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, while an outer garment of golden lightning appeared over his body, instantly eradicating all of the strands of black light that were clinging to him and binding him into place.

At this point, Lan Yan's eyes had already become completely glazed over, and her face was twisted in agony.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and a streak of translucent light shot out of his glabella to strike Lan Yan's glabella, while several arcs of golden lightning also sprang out of his body to dispel the strands of black light around her.

She slumped to the ground with a pained moan, and a hint of lucidity had returned to her eyes.

"How incompetent do those Heavenly Court immortal envoys have to be to have allowed you to cultivate the Spirit Refinement Technique to this level? Then again, I suppose this is a blessing for me," Gui Lingzi said as a peculiar grin appeared on his face, and it was unclear whether he was speaking to Han Li or himself.

As his voice trailed off, he gave himself a nod, as if he had just made some type of decision.

Han Li didn't know what Gui Lingzi had in mind for him, but the smile on his face clearly indicated that it wasn't going to be anything good.

All of a sudden, he noticed that Gui Lingzi had already ceased his chanting, but his voice was still echoing throughout the stone hall, and it was compounding upon itself, growing louder and louder.

Furthermore, the bloody odor in the air had also become even more potent.

"It's over for us, Fellow Daoist Han... We've entered Holy Envoy Gui Lingzi's Myriad Spiritfall Immortal Array," Lan Yan said in a despairing voice.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he looked around to discover that countless sinister, ghostly faces had appeared on the surrounding black stone pillars, and they were packed together extremely tightly in a trypophobic nightmare.

Some of the faces belonged to humans, while others were more beastly in appearance, and all of them had their eyes and mouths wide open in rage and horror.

The voices that were compounding upon each other were coming directly from the mouths of these ghostly faces, and a sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

These voices were like snowflakes falling from the sky, and if he were to allow these accumulating snowflakes to compound into a full blown avalanche, then even his Spirit Refinement Technique most likely wasn't going to be able to save him.

"Seal off your hearing and destroy these pillars!" he yelled in an urgent manner, and Lan Yan immediately did as she was told.

However, even after she sealed her ear canals with her immortal spiritual power, she discovered that the voices hadn't been silenced in the slightest. Instead, it was as if they were ringing out directly in her mind.

This was naturally quite alarming, but she had no time to dwell on this as she summoned a blue longsword before lashing out at the black stone pillar that was closest to her.

Gui Lingzi made no attempt to stop her, merely looking on with a cold smile.

This was naturally not an encouraging sign for Lan Yan, but she still had to continue, nonetheless, and her longsword transformed into hundreds of streaks of blue swordlight that struck the black stone pillar in a torrential barrage.

However, the collisions were completely silent, and the streaks of blue swordlight vanished into the stone pillar as if they had struck a pillar of quicksand.

Before Lan Yan had a chance to process this, a loud commotion suddenly rang out not far away from her.

She hurriedly turned to discover that Han Li had summoned several dozen flying swords with arcs of golden lightning flashing over them, and they released countless streaks of golden swordlight that rained down upon the dozens of stone pillars up ahead.

The golden lightning was so formidable that it was as if a bout of divine tribulation had fallen upon this place directly from the heavens, threatening to annihilate the entire space.

Gui Lingzi's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, clearly having failed to anticipate this turn of events.

In the next instant, a deafening boom rang out, and the entire stone hall was inundated by a vast expanse of golden lightning.

Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords succeeded where Lan Yan had failed, destroying all of the black stone pillars in their paths, but instead of exploding into chunks of stone, they imploded into clouds of ghostly mist that instantly spread through the hall.

Shrill shrieks and ghastly howls were ringing out incessantly from within the ghostly mist, and countless malicious ghosts were flying out of the mist, with seemingly no end to their numbers.

Lan Yan was horrified to see this, but in direct contrast, a look of elation had appeared in Han Li's eyes.

He swept both sleeves through the air, releasing a web of golden lightning that extended in all directions to form a barrage of lightning spears, instantly eradicating countless ghostly creatures at once.

This seems like a waste, Han Li thought to himself with slightly furrowed brows.

Right at this moment, the wall directly up ahead suddenly began to glow with dazzling, crimson light, and a massive, ghostly face appeared over its surface before opening its cavernous mouth.

A huge, crimson vortex instantly appeared in its oral cavity, sucking in all of the golden lightning released by Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The Cardinal Heavenly Lightning in Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords should've been the bane of all ghostly entities, but the tables had suddenly been turned somehow.

Han Li was quite alarmed to see this, and he hurriedly reached out to try and withdraw his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but a long, crimson tongue suddenly shot out of the vortex in the mouth of the giant, ghostly face like lightning, sweeping up most of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in the blink of an eye before dragging them toward the vortex.

Han Li was only able to retrieve a small portion of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which combined as one before landing in his grasp, while the rest were sucked into the crimson vortex, and he was no longer able to sense them.

Without the golden lightning from the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords standing in their path, the ghostly creatures surging out of the black stone pillars instantly converged toward Han Li and Lan Yan once again.

The latter hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, conjuring a water-attribute spirit domain that was over ten thousand feet in diameter.

As soon as the ghostly creatures entered the spirit domain, it was as if they had plunged headfirst into a vast sea, and they were stopped in their tracks by waves of turbulent, blue ripples.

However, as more and more ghostly creatures surged into the spirit domain, it was quickly overwhelmed, placing Lan Yan in a dire situation.

Right at this moment, Han Li's time spirit domain unfurled to encompass all of the oncoming ghostly creatures.

The ghostly entities were able to overwhelm Lan Yan's spirit domain through sheer numbers, but in Han Li's spirit domain, they were completely rooted to the spot as if they had been reduced to inanimate objects.

Chapter 1237: Arduous Battle

Lan Yan was quite relieved to see this, but Han Li's brows remained tightly furrowed as he swung his sword through the air.

A pillar of golden lightning erupted out of his sword with a rumbling thunderclap, blasting a huge passageway with a diameter of several hundred feet through the immobilized ghostly creatures, and through this opening, Han Li had a direct view of the massive, ghostly face on the wall.

Upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that the face was very similar to that of a human, but the degree to which its mouth was opened was extremely exaggerated, causing the rest of its facial features to be squashed together.

There was a strange mianguan sitting atop its head, giving it the appearance of an authoritative ruler.

Within its cavernous mouth were two rows of sharp, canine teeth, and specks of golden light could be seen in the gaps between those teeth.

To Han Li's surprise, he discovered that those specks of golden light were a series of miniature golden swords, and they were none other than his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Upon making this discovery, he immediately shot through the passageway toward the ghostly face, only for a cold, mocking voice to ring out from outside the array.

"I was waiting for you to make a move!"

All of a sudden, Gui Lingzi made a hand seal before casting an incantation seal into the array, and all of the ghostly creatures that had been immobilized by Han Li's spirit domain instantly sprang into action again.

The hordes of ghostly beings converged toward Han Li from all directions, inundating him in a ghostly sea.

Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he swept his longsword through the air like a windmill, releasing countless arcs of golden lightning that eradicated any ghostly creature that dared to get close to him.

However, right as he was about to rush out of the encirclement, the ghostly creatures up ahead suddenly parted on their own.

A sense of foreboding instantly welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, but it was already too late.

Right as the horde of ghostly creatures parted, a long, crimson tongue came spearing directly toward Han Li, who reacted extremely quickly, stopping cold in his tracks before thrusting his sword forward to unleash a bolt of golden lightning to oppose the oncoming tongue.

However, to his astonishment, a series of golden lightning patterns suddenly appeared over the tongue, following which a huge pillar of golden lightning erupted out of it, forcing its way through the golden lightning released by his sword before striking his body.

A jolt of numbness instantly ran through his entire body, stopping him cold in his tracks, and even his immortal spiritual power circulation had become a little stagnant.

The lightning that the tongue had just released was none other than his Cardinal Heavenly Lightning. It wasn't as powerful as the original, but it was still very formidable, nonetheless.

Before he had a chance to make sense of what had just happened, the tongue came hurtling toward him once again, but this time, it attempted to wrap itself around his body instead of releasing more lightning.

Han Li immediately shot back in retreat, only to crash into a horde of ghostly creatures behind him.

These ghostly creatures weren't particularly powerful, but there was virtually no end to their numbers, making them very troublesome to deal with even with his entire body cloaked in golden lightning.

After a brief hesitation, he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light.

All of the converging ghostly creatures stopped in their tracks momentarily upon seeing this, then began to surge into the door of light in a frenzy.

"That's a domain treasure! How kind of you to offer up such a precious gift to me!" Gui Lingzi exclaimed in an ecstatic fashion.

However, in the next instant, all of the ghostly creatures that had just surged into the door of light suddenly turned tail and began to frantically flee as if they had just encountered the bane of their existence.

Unfortunately, the entrance to the door of light was currently blocked by countless more ghostly creatures, so the ones that were already inside were trapped, and a chorus of horrific howls and shrieks began ringing out from within.

Before long, the chorus of ghastly sounds subsided, and the ghostly creatures finally scattered, trembling in fear as they stared at the door of light.

A young woman in a green dress emerged from the door of light, and Gui Lingzi's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of her.

As soon as the young woman appeared, she gave a loud burp, then turned to Han Li with an embarrassed expression.

"This man is also a ghostly cultivator, but there's something strange about his powers. I originally intended to gather more information on the nature of his powers before I called upon you, but he's forced my hand a little here," Han Li said.

"It's alright, leave him to me," Weeping Soul replied with a smile, then scoured her gaze over the countless ghostly creatures up ahead as if she were a predator staring down her prey.

A thunderous roar erupted out of her mouth as her eyes turned crimson, and her body swelled rapidly in size as she transformed into a giant, black ape that was over a thousand feet tall in the blink of an eye.

Her black fur was as hard as steel needles, and a strange horn had appeared on her head, while a third crimson, demonic eye had surfaced over her glabella. Additionally, three black bone spikes had emerged from her back, and all of the ghostly creatures frantically flew back in retreat at the sight of her horrific new form.

"A Xing Beast!" Gui Lingzi exclaimed as his eyes widened in shock, but it was difficult to tell whether he was excited or horrified.

In contrast, the expression of horror that had appeared on Lan Yan's face was much more clear-cut. Weeping Soul had always appeared to her as an elegant young woman, and she had never imagined that the latter would possess such a terrifying true form.

With such a delectable smorgasbord laid out before her, Weeping Soul naturally wasn't going to hold back. A vast expanse of black light surged out of her nostrils, and all of the ghostly creatures that came into contact with it instantly disintegrated into black smoke that was sucked into her belly.

A deafening chorus of ghostly shrieks and howls instantly rang out, but Gui Lingzi was observing all of this with a sinister grin.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he hurriedly warned through voice transmission, "Be careful, Weeping Soul. Something doesn't seem right."

Before Weeping Soul had a chance to respond, Gui Lingzi's body suddenly disintegrated into a plume of ghostly mist, and the foreboding in Han Li's heart was only further compounded upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, the entire stone hall shuddered violently, and a series of ring-shaped crimson patterns lit up over the ground, illuminating the surrounding walls and the ceiling above.

All of a sudden, Han Li discovered that the stone pillars were nowhere to be seen, and it seemed that he had been transported into another space.

All of the ghostly creatures had also vanished, leaving Weeping Soul with nothing to feed on.

It was a murky, crimson space with no direction or landmarks, and Lan Yan had already flown to Han Li's side with an alarmed look on her face.

"It's rumored that Holy Envoy Gui Lingzi's spirit domain has already reached the Oneness Tier. We are most likely in his spirit domain right now, the space referred to as the Ghost Realm," Lan Yan warned.

"Shut your mouth, you shameless traitor! I'll claim your head first!"

A cold voice rang out from an indeterminate direction, and even with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, Han Li was unable to find any trace of Gui Lingzi in this crimson space.

Right at this moment, he suddenly detected something, and he grabbed onto Lan Yan's shoulder before dragging her closer to his side.

Immediately thereafter, a crimson vortex abruptly emerged without any warning from the very spot where she had just been standing, and countless bloodstained, ghostly arms reached out from within to flail and grab at the air above.

Han Li lashed out with his sword, sending a bolt of golden lightning crashing into the crimson vortex, and it instantly vanished amid a flash of crimson light.

Right at this moment, a dark shadow suddenly appeared over Han Li's trio.

Han Li looked up to discover a mountainous figure looming over them, and it was currently stomping down upon them with one of its enormous feet.

The figure was dressed in a black official robe embroidered with a dragon and a phoenix. It had a set of unsightly facial features, and there was a mianguan perched atop its head. It was identical in appearance to the ghostly face that had appeared on the wall of the stone hall.

The giant figure was holding a thick, black book in one hand and a crimson brush in the other, and it was a spitting image of an underworld magistrate.

Han Li could clearly see circles of runes lighting up over the underside of its giant official boot, forming some type of array.

Is this thing a domain spirit? Han Li wondered to himself as he sprang away to the side to take evasive measures.

Even though Weeping Soul had revealed her true form, she was still completely dwarfed by the gargantuan underworld magistrate.

However, seeing as this was a ghostly entity, Weeping Soul had nothing to fear, and a layer of white light appeared over the bone spikes on her back as she launched herself directly up toward the underside of the underworld magistrate's boot.

"Don't..." Han Li called out frantically as his expression changed drastically, but it was already too late, and the bone spikes on Weeping Soul's back had already made contact with the array on the underside of the underworld magistrate's boot.

Rings of crimson light instantly surfaced over the underside of the boot, forming a series of walls of crimson light that came crashing down with such tremendous force that even Weeping Soul was forced to her knees.

Han Li immediately sprang forward to assist her, but the underworld magistrate's head suddenly swiveled around to an impossible degree to face him, following which it opened its enormous mouth in an expressionless manner.

A long tongue shot out of its mouth like a red python, and it was hurtling directly toward his forehead at an incredible speed.

Even before the tongue was fully upon him, Han Li was already inundated by a suffocating stench.

Chapter 1238: Sword Array VS Underworld Magistrate

In the face of the oncoming tongue, Han Li channeled his time law powers and dodged to the side, only just barely managing to evade the attack.

At the same time, he noticed that the lightning patterns on the tongue had disappeared.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul let loose a thunderous roar, and the white light emanating from the bone spikes on her back began to glow radiantly as it resisted against the walls of crimson light, destroying them layer by layer.

However, a burst of golden light suddenly erupted out of the destroyed walls of crimson light, and this was accompanied by a resounding thunderclap.

Dozens of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords suddenly descended out of the crimson light, and they connected together with one another to form a circular, golden lightning array to suppress Weeping Soul once again.

Arcs of golden lightning were churning over Weeping Soul's back like boiling water, and given that the golden lightning within the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had a suppressive effect on all ghostly beings, they were naturally very effective on Weeping Soul as well, and it didn't take long before her back was reduced to a mass of torn and ravaged blood and flesh.

Han Li was frantically trying to summon his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back to himself through their spiritual connection, and the swords were trembling violently as they strove to return to his side, but with the crimson light clinging to them, they were unable to act of their own volition.

As the flying swords descended out of the sky with the underworld magistrate's boot, Han Li let loose a loud roar as he bit through the tip of his own tongue, then sprayed a mouthful of blood onto the combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in his grasp.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that had been seized by Gui Lingzi instantly began to tremble even more violently than before, and they were able to struggle free from their constraints before flying back to him.

With the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and their golden lightning removed, the pressure on Weeping Soul was greatly lessened, and she reverted back to her human form, then sprang back to Han Li's side, evading the falling boot in the process.

"His ghostly powers are indeed rather different. It's as if his powers have reached their peak and have returned to a more natural state, granting it a righteous quality, and that has robbed me of my usual advantage against ghostly cultivators," Weeping Soul explained while panting heavily.

"Are you alright? This is why I didn't want to release you earlier. I figured that he had to have been the most powerful of the four holy envoys for a reason, and it seems that my concerns were warranted," Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows.

"I'm alright, Master," Weeping Soul replied with a reassuring nod. "What is this creature that we're facing right now? It's rather infuriating that Gui Lingzi has managed to remain hidden to us this entire time."

"Who says he's remained hidden all this time?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Weeping Soul turned to Han Li with a perplexed expression, whereas Lan Yan realized what Han Li was implying, and she exclaimed, "You're saying that this underworld magistrate is Gui Lingzi?"

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, the underworld magistrate came stomping down upon them once again, and at the same time, its long tongue curled through the air to form a semi-circle, blocking their path for retreat.

"Lan Yan, hold off that tongue for me for a moment," Han Li yelled, and Lan Yan immediately sprang into action upon hearing this, flipping a hand over to summon a blue cloth pouch with wave designs embroidered upon it.

With a single glance, Han Li was able to identify it as the pouch that the Lan siblings had obtained in the Eon Pagoda.

She chanted an incantation as she pointed a finger at the cloth pouch, and the wave patterns on its surface instantly lit up, accompanied by the sound of turbulent, rushing water.

Immediately thereafter, the mouth of the pouch opened up wide to release eight blue water dragons that were hundreds of feet in length, all of which crashed their way toward the crimson tongue.

A string of resounding thunderclaps as countless arcs of blue water lightning erupted out of the eight water dragons to bombard the long tongue, and a bemused look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

During the formation of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, the five immortal treasures, including the white fire bead and the blue cloth pouch, had all been summoned back into the array.

Following the array's destruction, the Essence Fire Raven had managed to recover teh white fire bead, and it was clear that Lan Yan had somehow managed to recover the blue pouch as well.

Furthermore, compared with back in the Eon Pagoda, Lan Yan had clearly become far more proficient in her usage of the immortal treasure.

Even though she was still unable to completely unleash its full power, it was enough to keep the crimson tongue at bay.

The tongue was unable to withstand the barrage of water lightning, and it began to withdraw back into the underworld magistrate's mouth, but Lan Yan refused to let up, holding the blue pouch in one hand while raising her other hand.

The eight water dragons instantly began to soar their way up along the tongue en route toward the underworld magistrate, while the underworld magistrate's boot continued to descend with mountainous force.

Han Li let loose a resounding roar as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines with all his might, instantly transforming into a giant devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

He pushed off against the ground with both feet, launching himself up toward the giant boot while lashing out with his six fists in retaliation.

A deafening boom rang out high up in the sky, and Han Li was sent plummeting into the ground below.

The underworld magistrate's giant foot was flung up into the air by the force of the impact, tipping it off balance.

At the same time, the eight water dragons under Lan Yan's control were rapidly closing in on its head.

A string of violent thunderclaps rang out as the eight water dragons exploded in unison near the underworld magistrate's head, destroying half of its mianguan.

Before the underworld magistrate had a chance to steady itself, a golden light barrier erupted out of Han Li's body before rapidly proliferating outward in all directions.

A short mountain range descended from the heavens, crashing down upon the underworld magistrate's head, while a golden river that was flowing through the mountain range wrapped itself around the underworld magistrate's body like a golden belt.

Under the debilitating effects of Han Li's time law powers, the underworld magistrate was immobilized, and its movements had slowed down to a crawl.

"Get away from here," Han Li yelled, and Weeping Soul and Lan Yan immediately did as they were told without any hesitation.

A bright, full moon rose up into the air from behind Han Li, and with a sweep of his sleeve, thirty-six of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot forth through the air, fanning out around him like an army adopting a formation.

All of the swords had arcs of golden lightning flashing over them, and they were hovering upside-down with their tips pointing up at the heavens. On top of that, they were gently bobbing up and down in a rhythmic fashion.

Once all of the flying swords were in place, they began releasing a burst of peculiar spiritual power fluctuations. It was as if in that instant, all of the surrounding world's origin qi had become connected with the flying swords to form a small world.

With the formation of the sword array, the flow of air through the area suddenly changed. A layer of faint, white mist arose, and occasional flashes of golden lightning could be seen within it, as if it were a golden lightning cloud.

"That's the Almighty Sword Array!" Lan Yan exclaimed with a stunned expression.

Back in the Eon Pagoda, she had personally witnessed the Almighty Sword Array, and even though it had been quite different from the sword array that Han Li had set up, it was giving off the same type of suffocating aura.

In fact, the vast and oppressive aura of this sword array struck her with an even deeper sense of apprehension, to the point that she was having difficulty breathing, and only after flying back a long distance did she feel a little better.

At this point, the underworld magistrate had finally managed to steady itself, and its expressionless facade remained unchanged, but a hint of fury had surfaced in its eyes.

The red light around his body reared up to clash against the restrictive golden light around its body, and at the same time, the tip of the red brush in its hand began to glide through the air.

However, its movements were still very slow under the effects of Han Li's time law powers, and a series of ancient, crimson runes were beginning to take shape beneath the tip of its brush.

With each rune that appeared, the surrounding space would shudder violently, and the harrowing shrieks and cries of countless ghosts began to ring out within the crimson space.

As more and more runes took shape beneath its brush, an ancient text appeared high up in the sky, and the pressure in the air was constantly building.

The ghostly cries were already drowning out the rumbling thunderclaps, and Lan Yan's complexion had turned deathly pale in the face of this harrowing chorus.

Weeping Soul was faring much better than her, but she was also struggling somewhat. In fact, she could even sense a hint of subjugation from the Great Dao through the passage of crimson text.

Right as the crimson text was about to be completed, Han Li's sword array finally began to display a change.

Loud thunderclaps rang out as arcs of golden lightning exploded incessantly, and the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords transformed into thirty-six thick pillars of golden lightning that erupted straight into the heavens.

Countless streaks of incredibly formidable golden sword qi appeared in the surrounding space, all of which converged toward the underworld magistrate in a frenzy.

Chapter 1239: Decisive Blow

In the instant that the surrounding streaks of sword qi began converging toward it, the underworld magistrate felt as if it had been inundated in a sea of astonishingly violent lightning power.

In the face of the mounting pressure, it had no choice but to respond, pointing the tip of its brush down at the crimson text below.

The crimson runes that were suspended in mid-air instantly sprang to life, plummeting out of the sky one after another, and as they descended, they glowed brighter and brighter and became heavier and heavier.

By the time they were in close proximity with the sword array, every single one of the crimson runes had become as heavy as mountains, causing the space down below to crease and tear.

Countless streaks of formidable sword qi came surging toward the descending runes, but many of them plunged headfirst into the spatial rifts up above.

However, there was virtually no end to the streaks of golden sword qi, and they stacked themselves on top of one another in layers, forming an impenetrable golden net that captured all of the crimson runes, which immediately began to churn violently.

The countless streaks of sword qi within the sword net were constantly whittling away at the crimson runes, and plumes of thick, white smoke were rising up into the air as the runes faded away one after another.

Before long, all of the crimson runes had been eradicated, but immediately thereafter, an enormous hand came crashing down upon the sword net from the heavens above.

A massive, crimson vortex surfaced over the palm of the enormous hand, and at the center of the vortex was a huge, golden rune.

The palm strike was imbued with even more powerful than the passage of crimson text from earlier, and all of the sword qi was sucked into the crimson vortex before being torn to shreds.

The entire sword net was also torn apart, leaving the remaining streaks of sword qi in a state of disarray.

Han Li wasn't fazed at all to see this, and he switched to a different hand seal as he said, "As expected of a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator. How about this then?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, the thirty-six pillars of golden lightning rising up from the Almighty Sword Array converged to form a true golden cloud even higher in the air above the underworld magistrate.

Countless lightning runes were flashing within it, and a peculiar aura that was steadily growing more potent was emanating from deep within the cloud.

A hint of alarm finally appeared on the underworld magistrate's face upon seeing this.

Before it had a chance to do anything, Han Li channeled his sword array with all his might, and the golden cloud high up in the sky began to churn violently at his behest.

The surrounding world's origin qi was stirred up into a frenzy, and unfathomable volumes of lightning-attribute spiritual qi were converging toward the golden cloud in a frenzy.

The thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords down below were trembling incessantly as they continued to release more streaks of sword qi, and the golden lightning flashing over them was gradually being devoured by the golden cloud above, revealing the green bamboo swords underneath.

Deep within the golden cloud was a pair of gargantuan pillars, in between which was a golden gate.

Arcs of golden lightning were flashing over the pillars, and they were etched with countless sword-shaped patterns that were giving off incredibly formidable sword qi fluctuations, as well as a tremendous lightning law aura.

The golden gate seemed to have been connected to the boundless Great Dao of heaven and earth, and the underworld magistrate looked up with a horrified expression as it roared, "Who are you? How have you mastered both the Almighty Sword Array and Cardinal Heavenly Lightning?"

Han Li offered no response as he thrust his palms forward in a strenuous fashion, as if he were opening a door that was reluctant to budge.

The golden gate in the heavens slowly opened up, revealing a narrow gap.

A deafening boom rang out as countless bolts of golden lightning came flooding out of the gap between the gates before cascading downward like a golden waterfall.

Through the gap between the gates, one could see a boundless sea of golden lightning that was eagerly gushing out like floodwaters through a broken dam.

The patterns on the golden gates flashed incessantly, and in the instant that the golden lightning emerged, it immediately took on the form of countless golden longswords that were identical in form to Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before raining down upon the underworld magistrate.

Violent thunderclaps rang out incessantly, and it was as if this almighty storm of golden lightning were the only thing that remained between heaven and earth.

The underworld magistrate's face became twisted with rage as it let loose a thunderous roar, and the thick book in its hand sprang open to release a deafening chorus of ghostly wails.

In the next instant, the crimson light within the book erupted into the heavens, and countless malicious ghosts flew out from within, some of which were as tiny as infant children, while others were as enormous as mountains, and they rose up into the air to clash against the storm of sword qi.

The entire space was filled with ghostly howls and rumbling thunderclaps, and an impasse ensued as a battle of attrition commenced.

Han Li remained standing on the spot, looking up at the heavens with an alert and focused expression.

At this current cultivation, the Almighty Sword Array was very taxing to maintain. However, as time passed, the sword array was only going to become more and more powerful, so he was confident that he would ultimately emerge victorious.

The string of explosions continued to ring out for around fifteen minutes, but the storm of golden sword qi hadn't abated in the slightest, and Gui Lingzi was finally beginning to grow agitated.

He emerged from the glabella of the underworld magistrate, then made a rapid string of hand seals before pointing a finger at the red brush.

The massive brush instantly began to rapidly shrink, transforming into a small flying sword amid a flash of crimson light.

The crimson flying sword shot forth through the air, hurtling directly toward Han Li while leaving a trail of afterimages in its wake.

At the moment, Han Li was fully focused on operating the sword array, and his brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the oncoming flying sword.

If only this could've kept up for a little longer...

He heaved a disappointed sigh as the golden moon behind him began to radiate dazzling, golden light, forming a golden space around him that was filled with a vast abundance of time law powers.

As soon as the crimson flying sword flew into the golden space, it was instantly slowed down significantly.

The underworld magistrate hurriedly thrust a palm downward against the blinding, golden light down below, and the crimson light emanating from the flying sword instantly brightened significantly, accelerating drastically even through the obstructive time law powers to pass straight through the center of the golden space.

However, Han Li had already vanished from the spot, and as a result, the flying sword pierced through nothing but empty air.

Right at this moment, the underworld magistrate looked up into the sea of golden clouds to discover that a tall figure had appeared in front of the enormous heavenly gate, and it was none other than Han Li.

In the next instant, Han Li raised his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword up high before sweeping it through the air, and a vast volume of golden lightning came gushing out through the gates to connect with his sword.

A string of incredibly loud thunderclaps rang out incessantly as the edge of Han Li's sword parted the sea of clouds, as well as the storm of sword qi and the army of ghostly creatures down below, then descended upon the underworld magistrate's head with incredible speed.

A blood-curdling howl rang out as the underworld magistrate's mianguan was sliced into two, immediately followed by its head, its head, and its torso, all of which had been split apart by a golden line.

The underworld magistrate's body was split into two amid the sound of tearing fabric, and countless bursts of ghostly qi erupted out of its body to form a gargantuan cloud of black mist, within which were countless specks of ghostly green flames that were frantically spreading in all directions.

At the same time, the surrounding crimson space was also sliced apart, and Gui Lingzi's spirit domain receded to reveal the collapsed wreckage of the stone hall outside.

"Weeping Soul!" Han Li yelled, and Weeping Soul immediately flew up into the air before adopting her true Xing Beast form again, then opened her mouth up wide to begin devouring the cloud of black mist.

At the same time, Han Li had finally been reduced to a spent force, and he tumbled out of the sky, while the Almighty Sword Array faded away.

Without the leadership of Gui Lingzi, the army of ghostly creatures began dashing around in a blind panic, and most of them were devoured by Weeping Soul, while the rest fled back into the thick book.

Lan Yan hurriedly flew over to catch Han Li, then gently lowered him to the ground as she asked in a concerned manner, "Are you alright, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"I'm fine," Han Li replied as he took a pair of pills, then swept a sleeve through the air to recover the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that had been used to set up the Almighty Sword Array.

The Cardinal Heavenly Lightning in these thirty-six flying swords had virtually been completely depleted during this battle, and it would take some time for them to recover.

"What's become of Holy Envoy Gui Lingzi?" Lan Yan asked with tightly furrowed brows.

Chapter 1240: Corpse Severance Talisman

"There should no chance that he was able to survive my Cardinal Heavenly Lightning," Han Li said as he struggled to his feet, but as soon as he did so, he was overcome by a rush of feebleness, and his legs gave out from under him as he fell back into a seated position.

Lan Yan hurriedly rushed over to Han Li's side to lend him her support, but he waved her off and said, "Don't worry about me. I'm just a little overexerted, I'll be fine after some rest."

With that, he sat back down again with his legs crossed to rest and recuperate.

Lan Yan heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, and she remained by Han Li's side as she looked up at the already completely collapsed ceiling of the underground space. A ray of sunlight was spilling down from above, shining directly down upon her, casting a long shadow that stretched all the way to Han Li's side.

Meanwhile, Weeping Soul had just devoured the final bit of ghostly qi in the air before giving a pleased burp as she reverted back to her human form.

She then made her way over to the thick book for a closer examination, leaving Han Li to rest on his own.

Lan Yan was just about to approach her, but she had only just raised a foot when her body abruptly stiffened, and an incredulous look flashed through her eyes.

Somehow, she was moving, but her shadow remained rooted to the spot.

All of a sudden, a burst of black light erupted out of her stagnant shadow, and a figure sprang out from within, holding a sharp dagger that it was plunging directly toward Han Li's chest.

The figure was none other than Gui Lingzi, and this was such an abrupt turn of events that before either Lan Yan or Weeping Soul had a chance to react, the tip of the dagger was already no more than several inches away from Han Li's chest.

All the while, Han Li's eyes remained closed in a seemingly oblivious manner.

Gui Lingzi's eyes were wide open, and a faint flush had appeared on his pale face from excitement.

However, right at this moment, the seemingly defenseless Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open, and a cold sneer also appeared on his face as he scoffed, "I knew you wouldn't give up so easily..."

At the same time, his hand shot forth like lightning with arcs of golden lightning flashing over its palm, and he was able to close his hand around Gui Lingzi's throat in the blink of an eye.

The tip of Gui Lingzi's dagger had already made contact with Han Li's chest, but it was unable to pierce into his body at all, and Gui Lingzi murmured in an incredulous voice, "How?"

"I knew that attack wouldn't have been enough to kill you. If you had fled the scene, then I would've let you go. However, you simply couldn't help yourself and struck at the first sign of weakness that I displayed, so you have no one to blame but yourself," Han Li sneered.

"You wouldn't dare to kill me! This is the Nine Origins Temple!" Gui Lingzi exclaimed.

"I've already prepared myself for all types of potential scenarios prior to coming here. Right now, it would be easy for me to kill you in your current state, but I'll hold off until I've searched your soul," Han Li said, and a translucent thread shot out of his glabella before piercing into Gui Lingzi's glabella.

At the same time, he began to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique in preparation to force his way into Gui Lingzi's consciousness.

Even before Han Li's spiritual sense had entered Gui Lingzi's consciousness, the latter's voice suddenly rang out in his consciousness.

"You think you can search my soul? What a joke! Now that you're here, please accept this gift from me!"

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, and he immediately withdrew his spiritual sense before opening his eyes.

Right as he did so, a strange, purple talisman came drifting out of Gui Lingzi's glabella, and it imploded into a purple rune that flew directly into his glabella.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li was struck by a burst of unprecedentedly excruciating pain in his head.

Even with his tremendous pain tolerance, this agony was too much to bear, and he involuntarily released Gui Lingzi, then clasped his hands to his own head as he began rolling around in pain.

Gui Lingzi immediately sprang back in retreat to open up some distance between the two of them.

"What did you do?" Weeping Soul yelled in a furious manner.

"I gave him a precious gift. I was saving that Corpse Severance Talisman for myself. The talisman is more useful for a late-Great Encompassment cultivator than any dao pills or spirit medicines, but on an early-Great Encompassment cultivator..."

Gui Lingzi's voice trailed off here as he erupted into raucous laughter.

"Undo what you did!" Weeping Soul demanded as she launched herself at him, only for Gui Lingzi to dissipate into a cloud of ghostly mist.

The injuries that he had suffered in his battle against Han Li had been extremely severe. Even if he could somehow maintain his current cultivation base, there was most likely no chance that he would ever be able to reach the late-Great Encompassment Stage.

If it wasn't for that, he wouldn't have been willing to bestow his Corpse Severance Talisman upon Han Li.

All of a sudden, a blood-curdling howl rang out as Han Li abruptly sprang to his feet, then stood rooted to the spot like a spear that had plunged into the ground.

Weeping Soul immediately moved to rush to his side, but Lan Yan stopped her in her tracks as she cautioned, "Don't go near him!"

Upon being stopped by Lan Yan, Weeping Soul was able to catch a clear glimpse of Han LIi, and only then did she notice that something was clearly very wrong.

Two expressions had appeared on his face at once, presenting a very unsettling sight to behold.

The left half of his face wore a malicious smile, while the right half of his face was twisted in agony and suffering.

"What's wrong with you, Master?" Weeping Soul yelled in alarm.

Han Li turned slightly to face Weeping Soul as if he had heard her question, and it seemed that the right half of his face wanted to answer, but the left half of his face refused to budge, and as a result, he was unable to speak.

"This is really bad..." Lan Yan murmured to herself with a grim expression.

All of a sudden, Han Li let loose an agonized roar as he suddenly rushed forward, as if to tackle Weeping Soul and Lan Yan.

An alarmed and fearful look appeared in Lan Yan's eyes as she reflexively stumbled back a few steps , but in the next instant, Han Li abruptly stopped cold in his tracks and began rolling around again with his hands clawing at his own head.

"What did he do to Master? I can sense that even his soul has become unstable!" Weeping Soul exclaimed in an alarmed voice.

"He used a Corpse Severance Talisman on him," Lan Yan replied with a grim expression.

"What's that?" Weeping Soul asked in an agitated manner.

"The Corpse Severance Talisman is one of the most precious talismans in the entire True Immortal Realm, and it's one of the only known devices that can help a Great Encompassment cultivator sever a corpse soul," Lan Yan explained.

"How does that work? Isn't one supposed to only be able to sever corpse souls upon reaching the pinnacle of the three Great Encompassment Stage cultivation ranks?" Weeping Soul asked in a puzzled manner.

"That's right, and therein lies the problem. Right now, Fellow Daoist Han is still quite far away from the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage, so he's not prepared to sever a corpse soul at all, but he's been forced to do so by the Corpse Severance Talisman," Lan Yan explained.

A horrified look appeared on Weeping Soul's face as the implications of the situation finally dawned on her after hearing Lan Yan's explanation.

Indeed, just as Lan Yan had said, despite the rapid progress that Han Li had been making in his cultivation of late, he was still far from the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, making him severely underqualified to sever his first corpse soul.

On top of that, all Great Encompassment cultivators would go out of their way to make extensive preparations before each corpse soul severance, and even then, there were many reasons that could lead to a failed severance. Even if one could complete a successful severance, there was a very high chance of backlash, potentially resulting in cultivation base regression or even death.

Hence, this priceless Corpse Severance Talisman was most definitely a curse rather than a blessing for Han Li.

In his current state, there was naturally no way that he could successfully sever a corpse soul, so he was doomed to suffer an excruciating demise.

"Is there any way to stop the process?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Once a Corpse Severance Talisman has been activated, it cannot be stopped. It'll be up to Fellow Daoist Han to suppress the effects of the talisman on his own," Lan Yan replied in a grim manner, but she was already aware that there was no way an early-Great Encompassment cultivator would be capable of suppressing the power of a Corpse Severance Talisman.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly sprang up from the ground again, and in the blink of an eye, he had already rushed over to Weeping Soul, who only had time to reflexively cross her forearms in front of herself to form a protective barrier before Han Li made a grab for her.

Weeping Soul could see that Han Li's entire face had been twisted into a sinister facade, and that his lips were stretched wide into an exaggerated grin, while drool was trickling down from their corners.

"Your aura seems to be very closely interconnected to his," the malicious Han Li remarked, and in the next instant, Weeping Soul felt a burst of mountainous power crash into her.

Her arms were almost shattered upon impact, and she was sent tumbling through the ruins of the underground space like a cannonball, leaving a deep trench in the ground in her wake.

She finally drew to a halt after crashing into a massive stone wall, and she hurriedly clasped a hand over her own mouth, but was still unable to hold back the blood gushing out from within.

Chapter 1241: Battle Between Selves

Han Li was cackling with glee, and it was difficult for Lan Yan to fathom that this twisted and malicious abomination of a man was actually Han Li.

Weeping Soul cast aside the blood that she had thrown up into the palm of her hand with a look of mixed emotions in her eyes.

Lan Yan cast her gaze toward Weeping Soul, and she was just about to say something when the latter suddenly yelled, "Look out!"

Lan Yan immediately sprang into action at this warning, moving over a thousand feet horizontally in the blink of an eye.

She had only just moved from her original spot when an enormous crater was blasted into the ground there amid a resounding boom.

"He seems to have grown even more powerful in this state," Weeping Soul yelled.

"The Corpse Severance Talisman has already taken effect. His wicked corpse soul has taken over his body, and if he's unable to sever it, then it will sever him and completely claim his body," Lan Yan said in a horrified manner as she rushed to Weeping Soul's side.

"We have to do something. At the very least, we have to restrict his movements," Weeping Soul said in a grim voice.

"How do we do that?" Lan Yan hurriedly asked.

"Help me keep him occupied for a moment, I'll think of a plan," Weeping Soul replied with a solemn expression.

Before Lan Yan had a chance to ask any further questions, Han Li erupted out of the crater up ahead, launching himself high up into the air before swooping down upon them at an incredible speed.

Even with over a hundred feet still separating them, Weeping Soul and Lan Yan could feel tremendous wind pressure sweeping over them.

Weeping Soul had already closed her eyes with her hands clasped into a hand seal, seemingly preparing some type of secret technique.

Hence, Lan Yan had no choice but to oppose Han Li on her own, and she took a step forward as a blue pouch appeared in her grasp.

The sound of splashing waves rang out as ten blue water dragons erupted out of the blue pouch amid a flash of radiant, blue light, and they broke through the tremendous wind pressure up ahead to pounce at Han Li.

Han Li let loose a wild roar as he threw a punch forward, and the two water dragons at the forefront instantly exploded upon impact, while the other eight flew past his fist before wrapping themselves around him.

Immediately thereafter, countless arcs of water lightning erupted out of their bodies in unison, and Han Li let loose an agonized roar as the arcs of lightning exploded around him.

All of a sudden, a dark red aura erupted out of his body, and it was as if he had instantly activated all of his bloodline power, forming bursts of incredibly formidable shockwaves that scattered all of the surrounding water lightning.

"Are you ready on your end?" Lan Yan yelled as blood began to trickle out of her mouth and nostrils, but Weeping Soul displayed no reaction to her frantic question.

Right as the eight water dragons were about to be overwhelmed, Lan Yan opened her mouth to release a globule of blood essence, which splattered onto her blue pouch before seeping into it.

The blue pouch instantly began to glow brightly, while the eight water dragons opened their mouths to release a translucent ball of blue lightning each, all of which were sent hurtling toward Han Li.

The eight balls of lightning reached Han Li in unison before exploding into an enormous pillar of lightning, and with that, the eight water dragons faded away, seemingly having expended all of their power.

As a result, Han Li was revealed, and his entire body was charred black, but he remained standing.

He cast his gaze toward Lan Yan, then bared his teeth in a malicious grin as a burst of baleful qi and tremendous malicious intent locked onto her at once, sending a chill running down her spine.

A look of despair appeared in her eyes as she slumped to the ground, while Han Li launched himself at her.

However, in the next instant, a peculiar gleam suddenly flashed through his eyes, and his body instantly became completely rigid. His momentum was still carrying him forward, and as a result, he began tumbling end over end like a wooden plank.

Immediately thereafter, a figure arrived by his side before pressing a palm down onto the top of his head, and Lan Yan was very relieved to see that Weeping Soul had finally intervened.

She was standing directly in front of Han Li with a hand pressed down upon the top of his head, and waves of rippling, dark red light were surging out of the palm of her hand.

Somehow, she had managed to completely immobilize Han Li, forcing him into a seated position on the ground.

However, blood was trickling down from the corners of her eyes, and it was clear that unleashing this secret technique had taken a significant toll on her.

With her other hand, she was making a rapid string of hand seals, following which she pointed a finger at her own glabella, and the skin and flesh there instantly split apart to reveal a vertical, crimson eye.

Immediately thereafter, a series of translucent, crimson threads emerged from the vertical eye like a mass of vines before piercing directly into Han Li's glabella.

In the instant that the crimson threads entered Han Li's glabella, Weeping Soul let loose a pained cry as her eyes sprang shut, and in the next instant, her spiritual sense entered Han Li's consciousness.

This was the first time that she had witnessed Han Li's consciousness, and it was a vast expanse of heaven and earth.

However, at the moment, the entire landscape had been plunged into a state of complete chaos. Gusts of howling wind were sweeping through the air, while countless tornadoes were wreaking havoc everywhere. On top of that, a dense blanket of dark clouds had appeared at a very low altitude, with arcs of lightning flashing incessantly within them.

All of a sudden, a bolt of lightning came crashing down upon Weeping Soul's spiritual sense, and she hurriedly dodged to the side before rushing forward.

However, she had only managed to advance for no more than ten thousand feet when a violent tornado came sweeping toward her.

"Where are you, Master?" she yelled in an agitated manner.

As an intrusive body of spiritual sense, she was only going to be met with more and more backlash in Han Li's consciousness, and once her secret technique ran its course, Han Li would reawaken, at which point there would be nothing more that she could do to stop him.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul suddenly raised her head and spotted an indistinct figure in the lightning clouds up above. An elated look appeared on her face as she immediately rose up toward the dark clouds, evading bolts of falling lightning as she went.

As soon as she arrived above the lightning clouds, a resounding thunderclap rang out as a giant bolt of lightning exploded, instantly illuminating the entire surrounding area.

As a result, Weeping Soul was able to catch a glimpse of a lonesome figure that was trudging arduously toward an area of dense lightning.

The figure was none other than Han Li, and she immediately yelled out to him.

Han Li instantly stopped in his tracks upon hearing her voice, then turned around to face her, and Weeping Soul couldn't help but be startled by the sight of his face, which resembled two halves of different faces stitched into one, with one half filled with malice and insanity, while the other half wore a grim and serious expression.

Both halves of his face raised an eyebrow in unison at the sight of Weeping Soul, and two voices rang out at once from his mouth at once.

"What are you doing here?"

One of the voices was uttering a surprised enquiry, while the other was conducting a furious interrogation.

His soul is already beginning to split apart!

The dire nature of the situation became even more apparent to Weeping Soul upon seeing this.

She was just about to reply when a burst of lightning rose up from the dark clouds beneath her feet, and she hurriedly evaded the attack before rushing toward Han Li.

More lightning continued to rise up behind her in hot pursuit, and Han Li raised his right arm upon seeing this to scatter some of the lightning.

"Right now, my soul has been split, and I'm unable to completely control my consciousness. Get out of here right now, or you're going to get hurt," Han Li said in a strained manner.

As soon as his voice trailed off, another voice rang out.

"You came at just the right time to see me devour him! How about you serve me instead once I've taken over his body and consciousness?"

Weeping Soul paid no heed to the wicked corpse soul as she said, "Now that the Corpse Severance Talisman has already taken effect, the only temporary solution to the problem is to seal your soul away and place you in a state of slumber, then reawaken you once a permanent solution has been found."

Given that the wicked corpse soul was one with Han Li, it would be able to hear everything that Han Li did, even if she tried to communicate to him through voice transmission, so she didn't bother.

"Is that your solution? That's perfect! Go right ahead!" the wicked corpse soul encouraged.

"That's not going to work. The more time that passes, the more my consciousness will be corroded, and it's an inevitable process that won't stop even if we're both placed into a state of slumber. There's a very good chance that the next time I'm awakened, my consciousness will have already ceased to exist," Han Li said.

Weeping Soul fell into a grim silence upon hearing this.

"I've already made an agreement with him to split ourselves apart using the lightning here, at which point we'll battle each other to see which of us will be able to sever the other," Han Li declared with a look of finality on the right side of his face.

"That's a suicide mission! You're still way too far away from the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage to successfully sever a corpse soul!" Weeping Soul exclaimed in an urgent manner.

"I don't really have any other alternatives now, do I?" Han Li sighed in a resigned manner.

"Cut the chit-chat! You're beginning to get on my nerves! If you keep trying to meddle in our affairs, then I'll kill you first!" the wicked corpse soul snapped.

"In that case, I won't try to dissuade you any further. No matter what happens, I'll continue to follow you, even if your body is taken over by your wicked corpse soul," Weeping Soul sighed.

"You've made a smart decision, little girl. Let me show you the power of your new master!" the wicked corpse soul guffawed, clearly supremely confident in its ability to come out on top.

Weeping Soul could only stand by and watch as Han Li continued to trudge toward the lightning.

Chapter 1242: Stalling for Time

After entering the area of lightning, Han Li raised both hands in unison before making a beckoning motion, and countless arcs of lightning instantly came converging from all directions within the lightning clouds below.

Right as all of the arcs of lightning came together, a pillar of white lightning erupted out of the lightning clouds and into the heavens.

Han Li was situated right at the center of the pillar of lightning, and he let loose a horrific roar of agony that rang out for close to twenty seconds.

Weeping Soul was doing her best to peer into the pillar of lightning, but it was far too bright for her to see anything within it.

A long while later, the pillar of lightning gradually subsided, becoming thinner and thinner, and the blinding light finally began to dim.

Standing atop the lightning clouds were two Han Lis, one of which was looking himself up and down with a twisted look of elation on his face, while the other was looking on with tightly furrowed brows.

They're both the same person, how could they be so different? Weeping Soul thought to herself in a concerned manner.

The wicked corpse soul's aura was clearly far more powerful than Han Li's.

"Finally! I'm finally free! Do you know how painful it's been to have constantly been suppressed and stifled by you? Now that I'm free, I'll be sure to return the favor!" the wicked corpse soul roared with a look of intense resentment on its face.

Han Li's consciousness had only just settled down slightly, but it was instantly riled up once again by the wicked corpse soul's vengeful fury.

In the left half of the world, the inky-black lightning clouds gradually took on a crimson coloration, while the lightning clouds in the right half of the world turned an even darker shade of black, with lightning constantly flashing within it.

"It's time for you to relinquish control of this world to me!" the wicked corpse soul roared as it reached out with one hand to make a grabbing motion toward Han Li, and the entire world behind him instantly began sweeping toward the other side.

Han Li naturally wasn't just going to surrender and accept his fate, and he drew upon the power of his half of the world to oppose the power of the wicked corpse soul.

The two seas of clouds clashed against one another, instantly splitting the entire world into two halves, with neither side able to get the better of the other.

"Right now, you're essentially nothing more than a soul fragment. How could you possibly hope to stand up to me?" the wicked corpse soul harrumphed coldly as it rushed forward and pounced directly at Han Li.

"You're just a manifestation of my wicked thoughts, so perhaps you should keep your mouth shut," Han Li sneered as he rushed forward to meet it.

With that, his consciousness was transformed into a battlefield between the two spiritual sense bodies.

Both of them resembled physical entities, but given that they were manifested from spiritual sense, neither of them were able to use any of the cultivation arts that Han Li had mastered, and they were only able to strike at each other with the soul power that they had seized.

The wicked corpse soul's spiritual sense was more powerful to begin with, and it didn't take long before Han Li's soul was forced onto the back foot.

As the wicked corpse soul reached out to close its hand around Han Li's throat, Weeping Soul knew that she couldn't just stand by and watch any longer, and she arrived behind the wicked corpse soul in a flash before thrusting a palm toward its back.

All of a sudden, the wicked corpse soul's head swiveled around to face her, while its body remained completely unmoved, and it snarled, "I was waiting for you!"

A hint of alarm surfaced in Weeping Soul's eyes upon seeing this, and she immediately tried to spring back in retreat, but it was already too late, and her hand had already made contact with the wicked corpse soul's back.

A burst of tremendous devouring force surged out of the wicked corpse soul's body, and Weeping Soul could feel her own spiritual sense being sucked into its body.

Weeping Soul was kicking herself for falling for such an obvious ploy. It was clear that the wicked corpse soul had baited her into attacking, and not only had her intervention not been helpful to Han Li at all, if this spiritual sense body of hers was to be devoured by the wicked corpse soul, then there would be no way that Han Li would ever be able to defeat it.

Right at this moment, a giant, white sword formed by spiritual sense abruptly took shape in Han Li's consciousness, then came crashing down upon the wicked corpse soul.

It was a manifestation of Han Li's Spiritstun Thorn ability, and an alarmed look appeared on the wicked corpse soul's face upon seeing this, following which it released Han Li and shot back in retreat.

However, it was too late for Han Li to take evasive measures, and he let loose an agonized roar as he was struck by the sword of white light.

Even as the wicked corpse soul sprang back over a thousand feet, Weeping Soul's hand was still firmly glued to his back, and he sneered, "Look at this fool! Don't you feel ashamed following such an incompetent master, Weeping Soul?"

"Master is no fool, you're just unable to fathom his wisdom," Weeping Soul countered as a peculiar grin suddenly appeared on her face, and as soon as her voice trailed off, she made a hand seal with her spare hand before thrusting it into the wicked corpse soul's back as well.

A burst of dark red light emerged over the palm of her hand, instantly forming a spherical light barrier around the wicked corpse soul, who was initially rather taken aback by this, only to then immediately burst into laughter.

"This restriction of yours won't even be able to trap me for half a minute! Once I'm freed, I'll make sure that you suffer for your disobedience!" the wicked corpse soul sneered in a menacing manner.

Right at this moment, Han Li's voice suddenly rang out from afar.

"Well done, Weeping Soul."

With the wicked corpse soul temporarily sealed away, Han Li regained control of the entirety of his consciousness, and he sat down with his legs crossed, quickly quelling the unrest in his consciousness.

Meanwhile, in the underground space.

Lan Yan was staring at Han Li and Weeping Soul with a concerned look on her face.

In addition to the blood trickling out of her mouth and nostrils, blood had begun to seep out of Weeping Soul's ears as well, while Han Li was in an even more sorry state, with black, tar-like blood flowing out of all of his orifices.

Right at this moment, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and they were bright red in color.

Startled by this harrowing sight, Lan Yan shuddered as she reflexively sprang back in retreat.

Han Li paid no heed to her as he flipped a hand over, and a series of translucent, black chains emerged from the palm of his hand.

He slapped his hand to his own forehead, and the black chains instantly vanished into his glabella.

Immediately thereafter, he closed his eyes again, leaving Lan Yan to look on in confusion and bewilderment.

At the same time, thirty-six black chains appeared in Han Li's consciousness, and they pierced into the sea of clouds like a flight of mighty, black dragons, racing directly toward the sealed wicked corpse soul.

"Those are the Origin Separation Law Chains!" Weeping Soul exclaimed, and she finally understood why Han Li had insisted on splitting from the wicked corpse soul.

As long as their spiritual senses remained intertwined, he would be unable to communicate with Weeping Soul in secret, and he wouldn't have been able to instruct her to temporarily seal the wicked corpse soul away, nor would he have been able to gain control over his own body use his Origin Separation Law Chains.

"You think those things will do anything to me?" the wicked corpse soul scoffed, but despite his derisive demeanor, he was very quick to react, and a burst of crimson light erupted out of his body before sweeping toward Weeping Soul like an almighty whirlwind.

This body of Weeping Soul's was nothing more than a manifestation of a wisp of her spiritual sense, and it was already on the verge of fading away. Hence, it was unable to pose any resistance as it was eradicated by the burst of crimson light, evicting her from Han Li's consciousness at once, while the spherical light barrier was also eradicated.

However, before the wicked corpse soul had a chance to do anything else, Han Li let loose a loud roar, and a series of radiant, golden runes suddenly appeared over the thirty-six Origin Separation Law Chains.

"You've integrated the Spirit Refinement Technique into those chains!" the wicked corpse soul exclaimed in a stunned manner, then raised its hands to conjure up a wall of lightning in front of itself.

However, the Origin Separation Law Chains were able to pass straight through the wall of lightning with ease before piercing through the wicked corpse soul's body and into the sea of clouds below, sealing that entire area.

"No!" the wicked corpse soul roared in a furious voice, but it was already too late.

It could feel its own power being slowly sealed away, and its indignant cries gradually faded into silence.

As it turned out, Han Li had already integrated his Spirit Refinement Technique into his Origin Separation Law Chains quite some time ago, and he was planning to use it in battle as a trump card. Never had he thought that he would be forced to use it on himself.

......

Inside the underground space, Weeping Soul was seated not far away from Han Li with her eyes, doing her best to rest and recuperate.

Meanwhile, Lan Yan was constantly pacing back and forth beside them like a cat on a hot tin roof.

"Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul, why has Fellow Daoist Han still not awakened?" she asked in an agitated manner.

"Master has suffered some rather severe damage to his soul, so it'll take some time for him to reawaken," Weeping Soul replied as she opened her eyes.

"What do we do? The commotion from the battle against Holy Envoy Gui Lingzi is sure to have already drawn the attention of others. Even with the state of chaos that the temple is currently in, there will surely be more Great Encompassment cultivators arriving on the scene soon, so we have to go!" Lan Yan said in an urgent voice.

Weeping Soul was just about to respond when she heard a faint sound, and she hurriedly turned to discover Han Li exhaling as his eyelids fluttered open.

The crimson coloration in his eyes had faded away, but they were still looking a little different from before somehow.

"Master!" Weeping Soul exclaimed as she hurriedly rose to her feet.

Han Li gave her a reassuring look to indicate that he was fine.

"I knew you would overcome this ordeal, Fellow Daoist Han!" Lan Yan said in an elated manner.

"How did it go, Master? Did you manage to seal away that wicked corpse soul?" Weeping Soul asked through voice transmission.

"For now, but this is only a temporary solution, and it won't remain sealed for long. I have to advance my cultivation base and open more immortal acupoints as quickly as possible. Otherwise, a successful corpse soul severance will remain a virtually impossible feat for me to complete," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

Now that the wicked corpse soul had been separated from his soul, the longer it remained in his consciousness, the more powerful it would become, thereby making severance more and more difficult.

"At the very least, we've managed to buy ourselves some time," Weeping Soul said with a sigh of relief.

"In any case, let's focus on the task at hand first," Han Li said as he rose to his feet after taking a pill.